Chapter 1004: Face

"Your Excellency, do you think we should go?" someone asked.

Kasuyi kept silent for a few seconds before slowly saying, "Since Black Star invited everyone, this isn't a private matter, so it depends on the Arcane Church… I'm guessing we'll have to accept the invitation."

"Why should we? The Arcane Church and the Black Star Army are not friends, so why does Black Star think he's worth this much respect?" Tolaen complained.

Kasuyi shook his head. "I can somewhat guess what method Black Star is going to use. His reason is to maintain the stability of the Shattered Star Ring, and if we don't go, he'll target us afterward…"

"And we're scared of him?" someone said furiously.

"We're not, but the Black Star Army has an enormous force in the Flickering World, so the church won't want to mess with him. Furthermore, the church has to think of Psyker. He lives in the Shattered Star Ring and has nowhere to run. If Black Star wants to find someone to settle the issue, he's going to get it," Kasuyi said calmly.

Sun Hunter squinted. "But if we all respond to his summon, it will increase his reputation and influence drastically, and he's not even hiding the fact that this is his goal. There's no way the upper echelons don't know about this. Furthermore, will the Beyond Grade As of the other organizations be willing to be used by Black Star?"

"The dynasty is definitely giving their full support to this, and the federation might agree to it too," Kasuyi said.

"The Federation of Light might agree?" Tolaen doubted.

Kasuyi looked at him. "The Shattered Star Ring is, after all, the Federation's territory."

…

At the same time, the Federation of Light has received Han Xiao' invitation and immediately gathered their various allies to discuss it.

"Black Star wants to host a large Beyond Grade A meeting. His intentions are clear. Do we have to help him build his reputation?"

With his two arms crossed and two other arms placed on the table, Sierron said with a cold and disdainful expression, "Although he's a peak Beyond Grade A, isn't he overestimating himself too much? What, he thinks that everyone else has to give him face?"

He was a crucial ally of the Federation of Light, a member of the elderly celebrity group who held a very high position in the circle of Beyond Grade As. His position was equivalent to the dynasty's Milizaus or the church's Sun Hunter.

Another Beyond Grade A turned to look at Bader, the President of the Federation, and asked, "What are your thoughts on this?"

"Maintaining the stability of the Shattered Star Ring isn't a bad thing to us," Bader said slowly. "Even without the dynasty leading this, I wasn't planning to cause trouble. The development of the Flickering World is about to start, so there's no need to cause unnecessary conflict."

"So, since we never wanted to cause trouble, there's no need to respond to Black Star, right?" someone asked.

"I'm still considering it," the Chief Elder said. "From the way things are looking now, there's indeed no need to give Black Star face and help to increase his influence. This contradicts our strategy to pressure the dynasty for the past few decades."

"I think that we can help Black Star a little." This time, someone actually spoke for Han Xiao. "From what I see, the pressure we've applied all these years has been quite effective. In addition to some special reasons, the dynasty opening up the purchasing right is just a matter of time…"

Everyone turned to look at this person with different expressions on their faces.

This person's name was Hades, a relatively new Beyond Grade A. He had joined the Federation rather recently and never had any notable achievements, so his position was plain. No one expected him to suddenly express his opinion. It seemed like he had a source of intelligence unknown to others.

"You said that there are special reasons that are going to cause the dynasty to open up the purchasing rights of the totems? What inside information do you know?" Bader questioned.

"Just some trivial pieces of intelligence." It was clear that this was a perfunctory response, and Hades did not want to say anything.

Seeing this, Bader was a little unsatisfied. Knowing that continuing to ask would not result in anything, he asked, "Then, why are you saying we should help Black Star?"

"Simple," Hades said. "The Evolution Cube is the core of the Evolutionary Totem business. If the dynasty opens the totem purchasing rights one day, our demand will be met. In that case, if the dynasty is the side who own the cube, not only will we not have any chances, but the dynasty will also receive the most of the profit made by it. Comparatively, it's better to continue letting Black Star keep the cube.

"Therefore, we can help Black Star to increase his position and reputation, preventing him from breaking under pressure and giving the dynasty the Evolution Cube."

"Sounds logical, but since the totem purchasing rights are not open yet, whatever you're saying won't make a difference. Helping Black Star now is going against our strategy to pressure the dynasty and will only cause more trouble for us. If you can prove that the dynasty will definitely open the purchasing rights for the totems, tell us the inside information you have. Only then will your proposal be meaningful." The Chief Elder's thoughts were very clear.

"I have reliable sources. The information is definitely trustworthy." Hades shook his head and still did not plan to explain.

This time, Manison, who had been watching from the side and not saying anything, turned his head and calmly said, "Do what you guys want, but I'll accept Black Star's invitation."

The others were shocked. They all looked at him, many confused.

"Don't you have conflicts with Black Star that are yet to be resolved? Isn't your relationship with him not good?" Sierron asked.

"That has nothing to do with you." Manison casually waved. "I think that this is a festival, and I want to make it happen. Usually, the Beyond Grade As are all staying in their own territories. Since this rare opportunity has come up for us to gather in one Star Field, we should all meet."

Everyone sized Manison's expression up but could not see through his thoughts. They were all confused and did not understand what Manison's intentions were.

Logically, Manison and Black Star were competitors, so Manison should want to suppress him as much as possible. Why would he help him? No one knew what he was thinking about.

Looking around at the others, Manison shook his head in his mind.

He was not worried about this matter increasing Han Xiao's influence, as an increase in regular reputation would not impact their position in the Machinery Faith. The believers only cared about mechanical abilities and the result of battles between mechanics, nothing else. Therefore, he did not care if Black Star became more famous.

However, this was also not because Manison wanted to help Han Xiao. His main goal was to indirectly increase the position of all the Beyond Grade As in the universe through this event.

Beyond Grade As were already at the top of the universe, but he felt that it was not enough. In the eyes of the advanced civilizations, their value was more focused on strategic intimidation and killing each other. It had been like this for many years, and Manison wanted to improve this situation.

If all these Beyond Grade As were gathered because of this opportunity, once the advanced civilizations thought about how much power they had if they came together, the advanced civilizations would be more fearful to them. Thus, they would be more important to the advanced civilizations. This would cause some implicit impacts, but overall, there were both pros and cons. Nonetheless, there were more pros than cons to Manison—he had already looked beyond what he had now and planned to bring more benefits to the standard that the Beyond Grade As represented.

In other words, Manison was consciously increasing the ceiling of the entire industry. Of course, it was mainly for his own benefits.

He also did not mind that Han Xiao was the one leading this festival. Although they were competitors, they also had similarities with both being Mechanics. With Black Star gaining more fame, more people would be attracted to becoming Mechanics, which would be beneficial for the Machinery Faith. This way, as the man at the top of the Mechanics, Manison would also benefit from it.

Of course, if he was the one leading it, he would benefit even more. However, Manison was not a petty man. Since Black Star was the one who suggested it first, he did not bother taking that away. Furthermore, Black Star had the excuse of maintaining the order for the Star Field, while he was in no position to gather all these people.

…

Compared to the church and the federation, the Beyond Grade As of the Crimson Dynasty reacted much more positively.

Milizaus tutted. "Black Star's ways of obtaining profit are really superb."

Everyone shook their head and chuckled.

All these Beyond Grade As gathering in the Shattered Star Ring was initially a bad thing that would impact the stability of the Star Field, yet Black Star saw an opportunity and turned it into a good thing.

Everyone knew Han Xiao's goal in doing this. Not only was it to increase his reputation and influence, but it was also to confirm his position as the head of the Beyond Grade As in the Shattered Star Ring.

Also, it just so happened that the Black Star Army recently revealed a new Beyond Grade A, so Black Star could ride this wave to further solidify the position of the Black Star Army.

Another clearer and more direct influence of this would be that the Bloodshed Land's competitiveness would be reduced. The Limitless Financial Group would also be heavily affected and would no longer be able to cause any trouble to the Black Star Army in the short term.

"Black Star's methods really are creative. He must be having fun." Kant smiled. He had turned into an adorable little black pig the size of a palm. He was sitting right up with his two back legs split like a man sitting with legs closed. His two short front legs were barely crossed.

"The dynasty is publicly expressing their support. I wonder what Heber thinks about this." Beyoni chuckled.

"It's not that the dynasty doesn't care about him; he just isn't strong enough," Clotti calmly said.

…

In the Bloodshed Land, Heber and Sorokin's doppelganger sat opposite each other.

"With the Black Star Army obtaining a new Beyond Grade A, Black Star made his move as expected. He wants to completely solidify his position in the Shattered Star Ring. Sigh, this is an open and direct move. I can't do anything about it. If he succeeds, more than half of the results we achieved all these years will be lost."

Sorokin shook his head with resignation.

He knew that Black Star was not one to easily let go of opportunities. As he expected, Black Star used the heat brought by the new Beyond Grade A in his army to make a move. Due to how sudden this was, he did not even have enough time to complete the investigation on Hila, so of course, he could not counter this.

Furthermore, Black Star had invited all the Beyond Grade As this time, so the result was not something he could interfere with. The only thing he could do was watch.

Heber did not reply immediately. He stared down at the invitation envelope in silence.

"Your Excellency Heber, are you planning to reject Black Star's invitation? I don't recommend it."

Heber looked at him before slowly saying, "Reason."

"The dynasty's stance is very clear. They're supporting Black Star. If you refuse, you'd be going against the dynasty, and that's not a good choice." Sorokin shook his head. "If everyone else in the dynasty goes and you don't, you'll stand out way too much. By then, it won't matter if you go; not going will be even more embarrassing."

"I don't need you to teach me." Heber snorted. "What about you? Are you going?"

"Of course." Sorokin smiled. "After all, Black Star and I are just business competitors. We have no hatred for each other. Furthermore, I'm in no place to insult him."

He did not like to stand out; following the crowd was more beneficial to hiding himself.

Your skin is so damn thick… Heber could not help but complain in his mind.

"Sigh, it's a shame. If only you and I were the ones to lead this festival." Sorokin sighed. "Maybe us Beyond Grade As know the reasoning behind this and won't think it's a big deal, but to the outside world, it's like we all basically responded to Black Star's call. If the Black Star Army was listed, just this one event will make his market capital rocket."

As for now, me joining this festival should increase the Limitless Financial Group's market capital a little too, Sorokin thought.

Not caring about Sorokin, Heber looked at the invitation envelope again. He was not willing to watch Black Star solidify his position as the head of the Star Field.

Sadly, after the lesson he learned last time, he knew that he was no match for Han Xiao, so there was nothing he could do.

…

Among the Star Pupil Holy Race…

"He even invited me‽"

Psyker was shocked and confused.

Honestly, he did not want to accept Han Xiao's invitation at all.

But the problem was, he did not dare reject.

Black Star was too strong now. Psyker's race was right in the Shattered Star Ring. If he made Black Star lose face, what if he found a reason and charged right over there‽

Even though the hatred between the two of them was immense, Psyker had lived on with the shame and grown low profile without doing anything. He did not dare to mess with Han Xiao.

For a Beyond Grade A, this is way too shameful!

Move! I have to move house!

Psyker roared in his heart. This was the second time he had experienced a break down this month.

…

Han Xiao sending out invitations was not announced to the public, but rumors of it still surfaced.

Usually, things happening between these Beyond Grade As hardly ever got leaked. However, the various media outlets of the Shattered Star Ring somehow got the news from somewhere and sent people to the Black Star Army to ask around, wanting to follow up on the story and make it into a huge deal.

The clearest indication of that was the new scenery at the Black Star Army headquarters—a group of extremely persistent reporters who were chasing after army members to ask questions.

Han Xiao did not stop it. It was clear that the dynasty had secretly leaked this. Since they were hosting a festival, building it up was unavoidable. Only then would the impact of it be maximized.

He initially wanted to do it himself, but the dynasty did it for him and saved him some trouble.

There were still some days till the day of the meeting, and most of the Beyond Grade As had yet to arrive. Han Xiao told Sylvia to prepare for this while he paid attention to the responses of the Beyond Grade As from all organizations.

Originally, he prepared some methods to convince some Beyond Grade As. However, unexpectedly, it went smoother than he thought. Most people agreed, and it seemed like he did not have to use those methods at all.

"It turns out that without me knowing, my face is already this valuable…"

Han Xiao was pleased.

After so many decades in the universe, my face has ascended to a new realm!

Since things were going so well, he had nothing to worry about. Other than the benefits everyone knew he would get from hosting this festival, he had another goal that no one knew about.

Legendary Point!

The sources of Legendary Points were extremely complex, and one was doing all kinds of major things. Han Xiao estimated that this would most likely give him a Universe Legendary Point, and even Political Asset was possible.

Furthermore, he could use this opportunity to find out all about these Beyond Grade As and memorize the Attributes Interface of everyone!

As he thought about the plan, his room door suddenly opened. Hila walked in and immediately cut to the chase.

"It has already been five days. I've rested enough. Let's do it."

It had been five days since Hila returned. She had been looking forward to the spar, and she had gone to his room again.

"Alright, let's have a fight but not in the headquarters. Let's head into space."

Han Xiao then stood up. He had agreed to this before, and he had no reason to decline today.

Chapter 1005: Trounce

As a new Beyond Grade A and the new Vice Army Commander, Hila had been receiving a lot of attention recently. The more famous she was, the more it would benefit the army. Therefore, Han Xiao was not going to damage her reputation.

Hence, the spar between the two of them was completely private, and Han Xiao did not need to improve his reputation by beating Hila anyway.

The two of them quietly left the Black Star Army headquarters and found a desolate planet. Han Xiao then used some anti-detection devices to draw out a battlefield.

"Here will do."

The two of them landed on the lead gray surface. Han Xiao raised his hand and opened the secondary dimensional army box. Groups of mechanical soldiers swarmed out and machines spread like a tide.

With him there, he could use all his troops, which was an enormous amount. Even though he did not summon his whole army, it still quickly filled up the ground and the sky.

Psionic Prime and some of the Apostle Weapons who had returned from the Flickering World stood in a row at the front of the army.

Han Xiao then summoned a Lord's Avatar and shifted his consciousness within before sending his original body away from the battlefield.

Sparring was one thing, but he had no plan to cut his lifespan. Going there himself was to express his seriousness, and changing into an avatar was being cautious.

Hila squinted, not saying anything as she approved with silence.

Although she hoped that Black Star could use all of his strength to fight her, she knew that there was something strange about her ability, and she did not want to cause any unknown damage to Han Xiao. Furthermore, Black Star's avatar was difficult enough to deal with, as well as those Apostle Weapons on the side.

After stepping into the Beyond Grade A realm, despite the fact that Hila was very confident, she knew that the chance of her beating Han Xiao was extremely low. She mainly wanted to see how vast the difference between her and Han Xiao was.

Hila took a deep breath. Her eyes suddenly glowed like rubies as masses of blood-red death energy flew out from her body and up into the sky continuously, painting the sky scarlet. The red energy continued to expand and seethe violently like a roaring sea, matching the size and impact of the mechanical army.

"Are you ready? I'm coming."

Hila entered combat mode, and her expression became calm and indifferent.

Han Xiao closed the secondary dimensional army box, stretched the neck of his avatar and released his Mechanical Force to enhance the entire army. He then looked down at the ground he was stepping on and shook his head with resignation. "Another planet gone to waste."

As soon as his sentence ended, Hila pushed both her hands forward and attacked without saying a word!

Boom!

The death energy condensed in the air slammed down violently like the sky falling, including all the machinery at the front in its attack range!

The exterior armor of all the mechanical soldiers reflected the bloody red tide. Psionic Prime looked up, slightly raised the Psionic Prime Spear, and tapped the ground softly.

Pa!

With him as the center, a light blue psionic barrier expanded out extremely quickly and instantly shrouded the mechanical army.

The tsunami-like death energy slammed onto the psionic barrier, creating a wave of earth trembling impact!

With a blinding flash, an energy wave mixed in both red and blood swept out!

Rumble!

The earth split open, ashes shot up like fountains, rifts were created, tectonic plates slammed into each other, and mountains appeared out of nowhere. The terrain within hundreds of miles changed extremely quickly!

Hila's expression changed—she did not expect Psionic Prime to be able to fight her head on.

She thought that Han Xiao would be using strategies, tactics, and the quantity of the army to win, but she never expected Han Xiao's Apostle Weapons to have already become this strong.

Hila's eyes concentrated as she flew up the sky. She then pressed her hands down. The power of the death energy that was eroding and impacting the psionic barrier increased once again. Large cracks immediately appeared on the psionic barrier that was only barely holding on in the first place.

Suddenly, with a deafening blast, the barrier shattered into pieces of light!

After all, Hila was nothing like Kohler or Beyoni; the Apostle Weapons were still not strong enough for her.

The mechanical army suddenly split up and activated their own psionic shields, preparing to defend the impact of the death energy while raising their barrels to counterattack.

Countless energy cannons focus fired on Hila. The scorching light seemed to have slashed open space, leaving only light trails behind. Not many Beyond Grade As would be willing to take on such a powerful bombardment head on, and Hila was no exception.

Her body moved extremely quickly in midair to dodge the attacks as seemingly infinite death energy flew out from her body, forming layers of protective shields that shrouded her. Attacks from energy cannons landed on her shield occasionally, blasting open cracks after cracks.

Her death energy could be used to attack and defend—there were hardly any Beyond Grade As who had no methods to create shields.

Using the power of the [Power of the Dead] to fight a mechanical army actually placed her at a disadvantage, as most mechanical soldiers were objects and Hila's 'life steal' attribute could not be triggered, which cut off one of her crucial methods to regenerate health.

Furthermore, the psychological damage of the death energy had no use on the mechanical army, which meant that she lost another advantage.

Her Esper Ability could only live to its fullest potential when facing opponents with life.

Defense was not Hila's strong suit. After being enhanced so many times, the power of the mechanical army's attack was already completely different from the past. As soon as the army was fully utilized in the battle, Hila felt an immense sense of pressure. Han Xiao's attacks kept penetrating her shield and landing on her body. Her health bar lowered continuously, and her injuries started to build up.

However, Hila's regeneration ability was strong. Although it could not be compared with Aurora, it was still quite impressive. When her level was extremely low, she already had the [High Speed Regeneration] talent, which used the Power of the Dead to nourish her flesh. In terms of stats, it increased her usual regeneration speed by five hundred percent and her regeneration speed by one to two thousand percent when using energy.

Upon entering the Beyond Grade A realm, she had received even more regeneration type abilities. Even though her 'life steal' attribute could not be used, her regeneration speed was still extremely fast. She was one of those who looked very paper but was actually very tanky—in this respect, she was quite similar to Han Xiao.

For the time being, she could still stand the focus fire of the mechanical army.

"Not bad. Looks like she won't lose very quickly." Han Xiao smiled with satisfaction while continuing to farm his distance travelled.

As soon as the battle started, he had made his avatar activate [Charge—Endless Potential] and started to keep moving around to farm the distance moved.

As the ability would only activate on his next melee ranged attack and the distance travelled would be reset to zero once he stopped moving, he could still use his army to attack while easily farming his distance travelled all the time.

As his level was above Hila's, the combat information on the interface showed all of Hila's attributes, which Han Xiao browsed through while keeping himself at a distance from the battle between his army and Hila.

After looking for a while, even Han Xiao was jealous of how amazing these attributes were.

Compared to a 'fake genius' like him who kept obtaining talents from here and there, Hila was truly one with extraordinary talent. She had a ton of talents, and most of them were exclusive personal abilities.

After becoming stronger in the future and her basic attributes got higher, the effects of these talents would become even more overpowered. Now, however, she was far from the peak she reached in Han Xiao's previous life. Even if she finally became a Beyond Grade A, she was still no match for Han Xiao.

As Han Xiao expected, Hila's Beyond Grade A Talents were [Supreme Power], which largely increased her Esper Ability strength, and [Cell Reaction Furnace], which largely increased her energy value.

Although Han Xiao had to go easy on Hila to protect her confidence, he did not want to go too easy on her and did not want to drag this out.

Despite the focus fire of the army being powerful, Hila was not threatened by it for the time being. What really gave her danger was the group of Apostle Weapons led by Psionic Prime.

Each and every one of the Apostle Weapons was very strong individually; they were much stronger than when Han Xiao fought Ames. They were ganging up on Hila and forced her to make a lot of mistakes.

Boom!

Numerous waves of death energy beams were shattered half-way. Scarlet Flame, whose body was an artillery cannon, fired nonstop, shooting out countless dark energy beams and stopping more than half of Hila's ranged attacks directed at the Apostle Weapons.

Heaven-Suppressing Banner charged forward, swapping his weapons continuously and slashing open the occasional death energy beams that got to him, none of which were able to stop him for even a second. His body was equipped with countless high technology melee weapons. He was a weapon master, and he also took the position of the head drill sergeant of the combat tactics in the machinery civilization.

As he successfully entered melee range, he immediately rolled and jumped up, swapping smoothly between all kinds of weapons and using a set of combos like a Mechanical Pugilist. His mechanical body was extremely mobile and swift; his attacks looked so appealing to the eye that it was as if he was dancing.

Hila had no choice but to concentrate death energy on her own body and turn her body into a weapon to deal with the pressure from Heaven-Suppressing Banner. Sadly, her melee combat ability was no match for a weapon master who was proficient with countless weapon styles. It was not long before she could no longer match up to the skills of Heaven-Suppressing Banner and was only getting beat up.

Clank!

Hila's hand blocked the alloy vibrating war axe, leaving a shallow red mark. She suddenly raised her leg high and kicked the axe down. She shot a highly condensed beam of death energy from her hand and blasted Heaven-Suppressing Banner far away.

Before she could take a break, the space before her rippled, and Mad Sky Hunter appeared using teleport. He opened his mouth full of metal sharp teeth and pounced at Hila's neck.

"Go away!"

Hila reacted quickly. She lowered her head and raised her hand before turning around and elbowing behind herself.

As the tip of her elbow landed on Mad Sky Hunter's chin, death energy exploded, creating an impact wave and blew this mechanical beast away.

At that moment, a purple shadow arrived from above, covered in a special twisted force field and dragging a lightning-like energy trail. It slammed into Hila and pushed her toward the ground.

This was a muscular purple mechanical soldier filled with nano-biological muscles, covered in lightning-like energy. It was indeed Purple Sky Spirit in overclocking mode.

Hila spun like a gyroscope. She tried to stabilize her body while spraying death energy to force the Apostle Weapons back, hoping to catch her breath.

However, at this time, a little dot penetrated the red curtain and glowed before Hila's eyes.

Swoosh!

Hila hastily turned her head. This dot slashed past her cheek, leaving a shallow bloody mark.

This dot came from the tip of a spear, and the one holding the spear was Psionic Prime.

Among the Apostle Weapons, Psionic Prime was the strongest, and Hila did not have an easy time dealing with him. Furthermore, with the other Apostle Weapons also taking part in the battle, she became more and more passive.

The two sides fought intensely for a very long time. The surface of the planet had a completely new look, like an egg with a cracked shell. Lava flew within rifts, and countless plates clashed toward each other, causing violent earthquakes.

"Hu… hu…"

Blood dripped from the sky. Hila was covered in blood and looked exhausted. Her specially made battle suit had holes everywhere, showing large portions of white. Melee weapons were plugged on her shoulder, abdomen, and leg. The intensity of the battle could be seen just from the state she was in.

"How unflinching." Han Xiao tutted internally.

Hila was used to going all out when fighting. Even if it was just a spar with Han Xiao, she still fought with her life.

Han Xiao had gone a little easy and told his mechanical troops to hold back, so as to give Hila a chance to go all out. She would only be satisfied if he still beat her in an overwhelming manner in this kind of situation.

This time, Hila pulled out the weapons stuck in her body. The open wounds slowly closed up and recovered. She looked around at the group of Apostle Weapons and suddenly took a deep breath before snapping her finger.

After such a long fight, all the Apostle Weapons including Psionic Prime had fifteen layers of [Death's Erosion], and they all exploded simultaneously!

Boom!

Red light exploded from the Apostle Weapons, and they were all heavily injured.

Detonating the energy had nothing to do with life force, since at its core, [Death's Erosion] was about the highly erosive death energy. Therefore, unlike her 'life steal' attribute, this ability was effective on any target, including machines.

The death of mechanical lives meant that their tinder was extinguished, which the erosion of death energy could definitely do. However, Hila did not lose her senses during the battle, so she would not kill Han Xiao's important combatants. Hence, she did not trigger the possible death effect, only the basic effect, which wiped out a ton of health from these Apostle Weapons.

Being heavily injured, Psionic Prime and the various Apostle Weapons showed flaws. Hila took the opportunity and immediately escaped, heading directly toward the Lord's Avatar like a red meteor, blowing away all the mechanical soldiers in her path.

"This is the last attack, I see."

Han Xiao could see the combat information. He knew that Hila's health was close to zero.

Knowing that Hila could weaken regeneration, Han Xiao did not let his avatar take any of the attacks and heavily injured Hila with just his Apostle Weapons and the mechanical army. Now, however, he controlled his avatar to turn around and charge right toward Hila.

Above the demolished earth, a black and a red meteor crashed into each other!

Han Xiao did not hold back at all. [Charge—Endless Potential]'s power fused entirely into his fist and slammed onto Hila's chest.

Bang!

It was as if the sky cracked open!

A powerful impact wave exploded and blew away all the dust around.

An enormous hole appeared on Hila's chest, penetrating right through. Her organs were shattered into pieces, and all the blood had splashed out together with pieces of her flash.

Hila's eyes lost focus. She fell straight down and landed on the ground, creating a huge crater.

"Target no longer has any signs of life." Psionic Prime looked over and was a little shocked. "Lord, y-you killed her? Wasn't it just a spar‽"

Han Xiao glanced at him and deactivated Lord's Descent. His original body slowly landed beside Hila.

"D-did we go overboard?" The various Apostle Weapons quickly followed and exchanged looks. They all looked down with guilt like kids who had done something wrong.

Han Xiao did not say anything. At this time, waves of gray energy suddenly gathered from all directions and fused into Hila's 'corpse'. Her eyes immediately regained life, but the dark red glow became gray.

The next moment, her broken body recovered at a visible speed. Flash grew out, organs reappeared, and wounds healed.

Her pale face slowly became red. Hila sat up and gasped for air. The glow in her eyes suddenly disappeared, and she started coughing severely.

"Cough cough cough…"

Han Xiao had expected this. With a smile on his face, he patted softly on her back. "Does it hurt? Take deep breaths, slowly."

Hila had the [Ignore Sudden Death] talent, which he had witnessed long ago and was also clearly shown on the interface. He knew that Hila would not completely die after dying once, and she would be fine no matter how heavily injured she was. That was why he decided not to hold back and used [Charge—Endless Potential] to beat her into the state of close death.

He knew all about Hila's personality, and beating her up with full force would actually make her satisfied. She had quite the potential of having the masochism trait.

After resting for a while, Hila finally stopped coughing and had a speechless look on her face.

"You really didn't hold back at all. I was even killed."

Han Xiao raised his brows and shrugged. "Isn't this what you wanted. Don't you like it?"

Hila snorted and did not object.

Having almost been beaten to death once, Hila was not unhappy at all. Since she had gone all out, this kind of battle was exactly what she wanted. She was very satisfied with the fact that Han Xiao did not hold back.

Furthermore, through this spar, Hila had a clearer understanding of Han Xiao's strength among Beyond Grade As, and she was secretly impressed.

She did not expect to still be completely overwhelmed even after becoming a Beyond Grade A. The difference was still so huge.

Hila did not become disappointed or despondent because of this. Instead, it motivated her.

Hoping to catch up to someone like him… it isn't that easy to succeed. No matter, it's only fun when it's challenging. Hila encouraged herself in her mind.

She had always respected the strong, and she could not help but admire Han Xiao even more.

"I've lost, but it was an amazing fight. It was worth it." Hila smiled from the bottom of her heart. She did not have many hobbies; fighting was one of the few.

"Tsk, what a fighting maniac." Han Xiao shook his head and laughed. He rubbed her head and said, "Can you still walk?"

"Don't touch my head. Let's go back."

Hila tilted her head and avoided Han Xiao's hand. Then she tried to stand up. However, having just recovered from close death, she was not in a good state, and her stamina was completely drained. Seeing this, Han Xiao wrapped his arm around Hila's shoulder and helped her up.

Hila glanced at him and did not reject it, letting him help her into the spaceship. She even actively nudged into Han Xiao's arms a little.

…

After this fight, the two of them became even closer.

In the past, although they were close, they were on completely different levels. Now that both of them were in the same realm, they had much more common language. The relationship between the two of them quickly improved, and the awkwardness and distance from not seeing each other for twenty years disappeared immediately.

Hila enjoyed this a lot.

In the past, I could only look at your back. Now… I can say that I'm standing beside you, right?

Information about the private spar did not leak, so it did not stir up any storm.

One phenomenon that attracted the most attention in the Shattered Star Ring was that more and more Beyond Grade As were arriving without any signs of trying to hide themselves, leading their fleets and heading toward the Black Star Army's headquarters.

The local galactic residents of the Shattered Star Ring all focused their attention on these Beyond Grade As and the Black Star Army. They could all smell a gigantic piece of breaking news coming.

Chapter 1006: The Hidden Bloody Rule

As more and more bosses from various places arrived in the Shattered Star Ring, this Star Field became increasingly boisterous. Each and every Beyond Grade A attracted attention from countless galactic residents and organizations. They could be considered a type of idol.

Other than the things they had done, one of the other important sources of their fame was Wayne Cards. Every one of them had their own set of cards, and there were way too many people who played Wayne Cards in the universe, so they knew these bosses all too well.

On this day, spaceships circled around far away from the Black Star Army headquarters. Most of them were media reporters who had heard about the event, and about ninety percent of all the media reporters in the Shattered Star Ring were there.

The reporters had camped there for many days, witnessing the fleets of Beyond Grade As enter the Black Star Army's headquarters one after another.

"How many are already here?"

"Twenty-seven! And there are more Beyond Grade As on their way."

"So many Beyond Grade As gathering, something big is definitely going to happen!"

"Are they planning a coup d'état‽"

They were tempted by curiosity and wished they could rush into the Black Star Army headquarters to uncover the truth.

As soon as the first Beyond Grade A, Ames, arrived, these reporters were all chased out and not allowed to enter the Black Star Army headquarters. They had no choice but to linger outside and watch.

Without their curiosity satisfied, these reporters seemed to have become raging monkeys—they could not sit tight even for a second.

Although the dynasty had leaked some information, it was only ambiguous so that the sense of mystery would still remain. The reason that these Beyond Grade As had gathered in the Black Star Army was not explained so that the outside world would speculate and discuss the topic more.

It was clear that creating this kind of suspense was extremely effective. The Shattered Star Ring had already received a lot of attention from the outside world due to the Flickering World in the first place, and this became the hot topic immediately.

Everyone was filled with doubt.

About eighty percent of all the Beyond Grade As in the entire universe had suddenly gathered, why?

The circle of the Beyond Grade As was too distant for ordinary people. Without any source of inside information, there were too many questions that remained unanswered.

Among which, Black Star was mentioned the most. The interest the entire universe had in Han Xiao increased once again.

Why are all these bosses choosing the Black Star Army as the location to gather?

Why can Black Star summon all of them?

In the past years, Han Xiao had kept a low profile and did not attract much attention. Only recently did he suddenly do something this sensational. Many people wrongly assumed that Black Star had done something secretly over the years that caused his reputation to suddenly skyrocket.

It was not long ago that the Black Star Army acquired a second Beyond Grade A, and now, they were gathering about eighty percent of all the Beyond Grade As in the universe. They were definitely planning to do something big!

Almost everyone thought the same.

At this time, two more fleets arrived with hyperdrive from afar, one in front and one at the back. The exterior armor on the ships had symbols of the Mechanic Emperor and the Void Overlord. It was Manison and Kasuyi's fleets.

"Quickly, record it!"

"Even Manison and Kasuyi came. Black Star's face is so valuable!"

The two fleets passed by these media ships and headed toward the Black Star Army's headquarters. The various reporters quickly recorded this process.

Since they could not enter, the only thing these reporters could do was record the Beyond Grade As who came and waited outside for the news to be announced.

…

The two fleets flew into the army's dock. Manison and Kasuyi's avatars disembarked from their spaceships. The two of them had known each other for a very long time, so they quickly started chatting.

"You're here too. Looks like the church is also going to give Black Star face this time." Manison smiled.

"Aren't people from the federation here too?"

Kasuyi's tone was calm. His voice sounded ethereal, as if it came from the void.

"The federation is one thing, and me coming is another. My goal here is different," Manison said with an indifferent tone.

"Drawing the line so clearly, you really aren't afraid of the federation being unhappy about it." Kasuyi shook his head. "Then, what's your goal?"

"Do you remember the last time this many Beyond Grade As gathered?"

"I forgot."

"I'm thinking the three civilizations have forgotten too, so I'm helping them remember." Manison's tone was casual.

Kasuyi paused, neither agreeing nor disagreeing. "This might not be a good thing for us. The more seriously we're taken, the more we're feared. If things go wrong, it might be another Tragedy of the Pinnacles."

"The good and the bad have always coexisted. Although us Beyond Grade As belong to different organizations, we're all in the same Grade, and we've always been separated. Now that we've gathered, we've attracted the attention of the entire universe. I'm sure that the other Beyond Grade As can see how much power we have together. If we can make use of this power, we can demand and obtain more things," Manison said slowly.

"You're still the same, saying the same old things." Kasuyi's tone did not express any of his emotions. "The Ancient Ones, the Mechanical Race, the Limitless Financial Group… you have plenty of resources. Sadly… when at your level, you alone aren't enough anymore. You have no choice but to make use of everyone… So, tell me, what 'Ones' are you going to form this time?"

"Just benefitting from each other. I'm not the only one benefitting from it; all the Beyond Grade As stand to gain something. Isn't that good?" Manison smiled.

"No matter what, you know me. Unless you have a way to help me complete the final God's Trait Transformation, don't come to me for something like this." Kasuyi waved.

Manison did not mind and changed the topic. "Then let's not talk about this. The void specialties you gave me the last time are quite good. Can you give me more? Come on."

"Sure, give the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter back first."

"Are you dreaming?"

While the two of them poked at each other, the dozen or so Beyond Grade As who were waiting at the dock came over. They were mostly Beyond Grade As of the federation and the church.

These people had arrived earlier, but as not everyone had arrived, they were waiting in the army's headquarters and had already stayed there for some days. Since their 'bosses' had arrived, they went out to meet up.

There was only one exception—Sorokin, who stood outside the crow alone with a big smile on his face.

"Why did you come to us?" Manison glanced at him.

"Although this is Black Star's territory, the two of you are important shareholders in the financial group, so meeting you guys is what I should do." Sorokin's tone was sincere.

From the way this sounded to the others, his tone totally sounded like he was trying to bootlick, which suited their impression of Sorokin perfectly.

At this time, Han Xiao walked over and attracted the attention of everyone. He said with a smile, "Welcome to the Black Star Army. Follow me, the rooms are ready."

"Black Star." The Beyond Grade As turned around and greeted him, all with complex looks in their eyes.

Some of them had only heard about Black Star and had never met him personally, but after staying in the Black Star Army for the past days, they knew Han Xiao.

Most of the Beyond Grade As there did not actually want to go, and they only went reluctantly because of the order from the upper echelons of the federation and the church.

However, even though they were unwilling, since they were in someone else's territory, they did not dare act too arrogantly, or they would insult Han Xiao completely. Clearly, enraging a peak Beyond Grade A who was very capable at fighting was highly irrational.

Manison nodded at Han Xiao. "We meet again. if I remember correctly, this should be the second time I've come to your territory."

"Third." Han Xiao raised his brows. "You forgot the fight."

"Alright." Manison shook his head and chuckled. He did not mind.

Ever since that fight, Han Xiao had not made any moves for the next decade or so. Manison had already confirmed that Han Xiao had admitted loss and would not challenge his position again. Therefore, he had no problems with him.

He had already beaten a ton of Mechanics over the years. As long as the opponent admitted their loss, he would not continue to trouble them. He had to maintain his reputation as the main God of the Machinery Faith.

"This is the Void Overlord, Kasuyi. If I remember correctly, this should be the first time the two of you have met." Manison turned his head and introduced Kasuyi.

"It's indeed the first time, but I've heard a lot about you." Han Xiao smiled and extended his hand. "I'm honored to meet you, Your Excellency Kasuyi."

Kasuyi shook Han Xiao's hand and said, "I've been hearing the name Black Star a lot. You're a legend, too. Meeting you is also my honor. I heard you also have the blood of the Void Race. I think we'll have a lot of common topics to talk about."

After praising each other, Han Xiao guided everyone to their own room. After the federation and the church's people settled down, Sorokin was the only one left.

"Your Excellency Black Star, it really shocked me how big your face is. So many important people are here." Sorokin seemed like he was praising Han Xiao sincerely, but it sounded pretentious in Han Xiao's ears.

Han Xiao curled his lips. "I thought you wouldn't come."

"Impossible! I have business in the Shattered Star Ring too, and you're the top of this Star Field, so how can I not give you face? I know you have some misunderstandings about me since we have some competition in terms of businesses, but I personally have nothing but respect for you." Sorokin smiled brightly. "We might even have the chance to work together in the future."

Han Xiao knew that this guy's shamelessness could match up to his own, so he was used to it. He tutted and asked, "Didn't Heber come with you?"

"He said he's going to come on the last day. Hehe, despite being the nearest to you, he's trying to object like a kid." Sorokin sold Heber out immediately.

"Humph, got it."

Han Xiao waved and left the fake-smiling Sorokin.

Other than those allies who came because of the order from the three Universal Civilizations, everyone else had their own intentions. For example, Sorokin was probably there because he wanted to blend into the crowd, as well as to network with these Beyond Grade As. That old man Manison seemed to have other goals, too…

The Beyond Grade As who were staying at the Black Star Army could be classified into three types—the dynasty's allies and those who were on his side, like Ames and Austin; the allies of the other two universal civilizations who came because they were ordered to do so; and the Beyond Grade As from the other factions as well as neutral Beyond Grade As, most of them whom had come to socialize.

However, the goals of these people would not impact this event too much, so Han Xiao did not mind.

To Han Xiao, the main focus of this Beyond Grade A gathering was the waiting stage before the official meeting. These Beyond Grade As would be waiting for more than ten days in their rooms, which would create a platform to communicate and socialize. Usually, due to factors such as distance and their respective factions, there were no occasions as public as this to gather so many of them together.

This way, everyone could socialize together, and it would be very convenient for him to find out more about the Beyond Grade As he would be meeting for the first time. Not only him, everyone's circle would expand by quite a large extent, which would be beneficial to enhancing the relationship inside the entire Beyond Grade A circle.

Han Xiao did not just want to increase his reputation and maintain order within the Star Field; he also wanted the other Beyond Grade As to communicate and socialize. He was providing an opportunity for these people to build a good relationship with each other.

Although Beyond Grade As might have conflicts and grudges against each other, they would have no choice but to become comrades and fight alongside each other when the war of the World Tree erupted. He wanted to do something good in advance.

Furthermore, if the Beyond Grade As maintained the state of disunity, it would also lead to some very dire consequences.

"There were both natural and man-made reasons that led to the Calamity of the Supers, I hope this meeting will cause some changes…"

…

"Your Excellency President, there are already close to thirty Beyond Grade As who are now living in the Black Star Army's headquarters. The estimate of the final count is around seventy to eighty."

On the Federation of Light's mother planet, Bader listened to the Chief Elder's report with a frown on his face.

Considering the various factors, he decided to let the federation's allies attend the meeting. However, he suddenly realized that the power of so many Beyond Grade As gathered in one place was too horrifying. Even though they were just meeting each other, it was still enough to shock the entire universe and stir up storms. The impact of this had exceeded his expectations.

"There are too many Beyond Grade As…"

"That's right. In a few days' time, the Black Star Army's headquarters might be the most dangerous place in the entire universe." The Chief Elder's expression did not look good either.

"You misunderstand." Bader looked up at him. "What I meant was… there are too many Beyond Grade As in the universe."

The Chief Elder's expression changed drastically.

Bader stood up, approached the window, and looked out. "The lifespan of a Beyond Grade A is very long. Without any accidents, they would live up to a thousand years, and there are also those Eternal Lives with seemingly endless life spans.

"Even though the chance of a Beyond Grade A appearing is extremely low, compare how long it takes for their life span to run out to how long it takes for a new one to appear—the number of Beyond Grade As in the universe will only keep growing. A hundred… two hundred… One day, sooner or later, there'll be thousands of them!

"By that time, individual great power… will be uncontrollable!"

The Chief Elder's expression became extremely serious. "You're saying… to carry out a new cleansing? Like the Tragedy of the Pinnacles?

Bader shook his head. "The Tragedy of the Pinnacles was just an accident, but it hinted to us how to deal with the problem of Beyond Grade As. Although the number of the Beyond Grade As right now is still controllable, if we don't plan ahead, the day when the peak of individual power overflows will come sooner or later… Therefore, cleansing the Beyond Grade As is a must. However, I don't plan to do this during my term."

The Chief Elder nodded. "Hmm, the Flickering World is very important to the entire universe right now. It isn't the time for a cleansing."

If there were too many individuals with extraordinary power that surpassed even logic itself, order would no longer be stable. In his eyes, cleansing the Beyond Grade As had nothing to do with hatred; it was only to maintain the stability of the universe. However, this would definitely cause unrest in the short term. Therefore, it was a hot potato to any leader of the universal civilizations—no one wanted to do such dirty work during their term.

To him, this was like keeping the ecological balance of the universe. This was not eliminating Beyond Grade As but controlling the total number of Beyond Grade As, keeping the ratio of individual power to collective power at a safe standard.

In peaceful times without exterior enemies, the consequences of this ratio being unbalanced would be unpredictable.

This was not his sudden idea. In fact, many years ago, the three Universal Civilizations had developed similar plans privately. However, the Beyond Grade As had never gone out of control, so they had never executed this plan. This was a silent agreement between the three rulers of the universe.

"I wonder if Black Star hosted this meeting because of this too…" Bader thought of Manison's attitude, paused, and said with a deep voice, "Manison probably guessed the inevitability of the cleanse, so he wanted to gather all the Beyond Grade As to show us their strength. Or is he trying to improve the position of the Beyond Grade As? Tsk… these two crafty guys."

He had to admit that he did now fear the Beyond Grade As more, but there was no way to start the cleanse now, so the only thing to do was to turn this fear into showing that the Beyond Grade As were more important.

"Black Star, Mechanic Emperor… do you really want to gather the power of the Beyond Grade As?" Bader's eyes had a deep and unforeseeable look.

Chapter 1007: Meeting

As more and more Beyond Grade As arrived at the Black Star Army's headquarters, Han Xiao's territory became increasingly rowdy. Within a few days, there were already about eighty Beyond Grade As and their fleets gathered there.

The Purple Crystal Civilization, which managed this Star Cluster, became nervous and secretly deployed some forces to set up defenses.

It was not just the Purple Crystal Civilization. All the Star Cluster civilizations of the Shattered Star Ring, as well as the three Universal Civilizations' garrisons in this Star Field, started to secretly deploy troops to prepare for what might happen.

This many peak individuals of the universe would easily be able to turn an entire Star Field upside down, and they were all individuals with independent minds who carried the risk of not being controllable. These civilizations did not dare remain unprepared.

As for the Godoran Civilization, which directly ruled the Star Zone that the Black Star Army was in, all of their fleets had gathered around the Star Zone housing the Black Star Army's headquarters as if they were facing a lethal enemy.

The things going on in the outside world did not affect the mood of the many Beyond Grade As. With Heber arriving last, the meeting began as scheduled.

The meeting location was a palace in the headquarters. The ceiling with a hundred meters tall, and dozens of floating thrones formed a circle five meters above the ground.

As the gate opened, the Beyond Grade As swarmed in. The tallest was the Beast Ancestor Gorutan, and the shortest was the finger-sized Sun Hunter. There were all kinds of appearances.

They all picked a location to sit one after another. The allies of the three Universal Civilizations all sat around each other in their own corner, with the Beyond Grade As of the other factions in between them.

After they sat down, they noticed three empty seats that were next to each other. Seeing that Han Xiao had yet to arrive, they casually started chatting while sizing each other up.

While waiting, many Beyond Grade As had moved around. In the past, some of them had only heard about some of the others but had never met. Using this opportunity brought by Han Xiao, these people had finally met each other and made some new friends.

Those who were visited most were the peak Beyond Grade As who had the highest positions and the strongest organizations in the circle. That included Manison, Kasuyi, Kant, and Gorutan. Clotti and a few of the other Beyond Grade As who did not come to the Shattered Star Ring, of course, did not participate in this meeting.

At this point in time, those who were sized up the most were the new members of the circle, those who only became Beyond Grade As in the past decade or so, such as the federation's Hades, the dynasty's Silver Shadow, and the church's Tolaen.

After a while, three people walked in. Everyone stopped chatting and looked over at the gate—it was indeed Han Xiao, Hila, and Ames.

Han Xiao walked forward with wide strides, came before the mechanical throne, and sat down, facing all of the Beyond Grade A.

At the same time, Ames and Hila sat in the empty seats on his left and right.

Many looked at Hila with curiosity—there were a lot of people who were interested in this new Beyond Grade A of the Black Star Army.

Finally, the gate slowly closed.

With a smile on his face, Han Xiao looked around and slowly spoke, "Everyone is here. Pardon me for the wait. I appreciate all of you being willing to take part in this meeting…"

While saying the standard things, he observed everyone.

As he spoke, some sat tight and upright with a serious expression, some had indifferent and careless looks, some smiled to express friendliness, and some lay back in their chairs. He could see some of their attitudes.

Of the Beyond Grade As present, more than forty, including himself, were allies of the three Universal Civilizations. Most of the rest were on their own, and some were allies of the Super Star Cluster civilizations.

Many also had multiple identities. For example, quite a few Ancient Ones were there. There were also a few shareholders of the Limitless Financial Group. The Protector of the Galactic Black Market 'Beast Ancestor', 'Secret Master', and so on were here too. These were all very important people whom Han Xiao had to pay more attention to.

These people had very complicated relationships with each other. Some had good relationships with each other; some held grudges against each other; some were brothers on the surface but actually plotted against each other behind each other's backs; some looked distant but were actually close secretly.

Han Xiao had moved around during the past few days too. He had managed to talk to everyone and successfully collected the combat information on everyone present. There were only a few whose levels were higher than his whose abilities he could not fully see. Still, he had the abilities of everyone else. He had obtained quite the amount of valuable intelligence.

These people, however, had no idea that Han Xiao knew even the color of their underpants.

"No matter why you are all here, I appreciate your arrival…" Finally, Han Xiao had finished the cliche opening and entered into the main topic. "I suppose everyone has already spoken with each other, so I will save myself the saliva of making introductions."

The people all looked at Han Xiao, waiting for his next sentence.

Han Xiao softly patted the handle of his throne and said, "The reason I hosted this meeting is mainly to discuss the matter about the Shattered Star Ring with everyone…"

Before he could finish, a very intrusive voice sounded.

"Humph, can you represent the entire Shattered Star Ring?"

The look in everyone's eyes changed slightly as they looked over at the source of the voice. The person who spoke was the Federation of Light's Sierron, as well as a member of the Ancient Ones. He had a mocking expression on his face.

Without any change in his expression, Han Xiao smiled. "There are so many civilizations and organizations in the Shattered Star Ring. Of course, I can't represent the stand of the entire Star Field alone."

"Then, what right do you have to talk about this issue?" Sierron demanded. "Don't forget, the Federation of Light is the actual ruler of the Shattered Star Ring. We're the only ones who can speak for this Star Field, not you."

The other allies of the Federation did not stop Sierron. They came to give face to Han Xiao, but as competitors, they were not going to make this too easy for him. Causing trouble was unavoidable. Even if they were not going to stop him, they did not want him to achieve his goal too easily.

"I cannot agree with that," Han Xiao said slowly. "I'm a local of the Shattered Star Ring, and I'm stationed here on behalf of the dynasty. Also, I'm the strongest Beyond Grade A of this Star Field. Although I can't represent the stand of this entire Star Field, I'm sure I have the right to speak for it personally. Furthermore, I'm not announcing some kind of order. I'm just here to discuss certain matters with all of you today."

"The strongest Beyond Grade A of the Shattered Star Ring? Are you sure?" Sierron sneered.

Han Xiao raised his brow and slowly opened his arms. "Are you questioning my combat history?"

"Don't worry. I won't deny that you've defeated Heber, Psyker, and Ames. As for Hila… she's new, so she probably is no match for you."

Heber's expression was not looking too great. He did not like the fact that his defeat was mentioned by an outsider in front of so many Beyond Grade As.

Psyker coldly glanced at Sierron before glaring at Han Xiao. He was not happy about it either.

Ames, however, did not mind, and Hila's expression was like a rock, as if she did not hear anything.

"Then, what's the issue?" Han Xiao asked.

"Simple, there's still one person who you've not defeated, the Magus, Austin!" Sierron shook his head. "He's just too low profile, but it's not certain he's no match for you. Without defeating him, you can't solidify your position as the strongest of this Star Field."

Austin was stunned. Why mention me out of nowhere?

Then, he understood it immediately. Sierron wanted to put him on the spot, which might be an act to stir up disagreement. Although Sierron probably knew that he had quite a good relationship with Black Star, there was no harm in trying. After all, as long as the relationship between the two of them was tainted even a little, Sierron would benefit from it.

"I admit Black Star's the strongest in this Star Field. I'm no match for him." Austin curled his lips. This was the only thing he could say. It was not like he could spar with Han Xiao right there.

Hearing this, Han Xiao nodded at Austin before asking Sierron, "Do you have any other objections?"

"Nothing else." Sierron saw that Manison had given him a look, so he closed his eyes and did not say any more.

Han Xiao looked around. Seeing that no one else had a problem, he said with a deep voice, "Alright then, since everyone agrees that I have the right to speak for the Shattered Star Ring, let's get back to business… As the opening of the Flickering World is near, I can understand why all of you have come to the Shattered Star Ring to wait. However, I believe that everyone here knows that this many Beyond Grade As gathering in one Star Field will create a lot of unstable factors. As the peak of the Shattered Star Ring Supers, I have something to say. Please do listen.

"I grew in the Shattered Star Ring, so of course, it's my responsibility to maintain the stability of this Star Field. I welcome all of you to the Shattered Star Ring as guests, but I have but one small request… I hope that while you're all here, you won't destroy the order of the Shattered Star Ring. If all of you are willing to give me face for this, I'll be very appreciative."

This time, Han Xiao's tone changed into a much deeper and more serious one.

"However… if anyone ignores my request, I shall see it as a personal challenge to me, and I will absolutely not let it off easily. Remember, there's still a long time till the date of the opening of the Flickering World. I hope to not have any conflict with anyone."

The atmosphere suddenly became tense. The people had different looks on their faces—indifference, approval, seriousness, and many others.

Although Han Xiao said it in a very nice way, the main purpose of this sentence was to serve as a threat and a warning, and its meaning was very straightforward.

I don't care where you're from—this is my territory. If you mess with me, you're not going to get away with it easily.

If you want to cause trouble in the Shattered Star Ring, you'd better weigh the consequences of messing with me!

Everyone there was a boss of an area, and there were quite a few who could speak for their Star Fields too, so many felt that these words were rather sharp.

However, with the position and strength Black Star had now, he already had the right to say something like this, so no one felt it was out of place.

This time, Austin smiled and said, "I'm a local Beyond Grade A of the Shattered Star Ring too. I also don't want the Star Field to become chaotic. I agree completely with what Black Star said."

"Humph, me too," Heber said reluctantly.

Ames and Hila also expressed their agreement. Seeing this, Psyker had no choice but to do the same.

This time, all of the local Beyond Grade As of the Shattered Star Ring had supported Han Xiao, expressing their intent to maintain the stability of the Star Field together. In a way, they had indirectly approved of Han Xiao's position as the leader.

Han Xiao paused for a few seconds, saw the reactions of everyone present, and suddenly smiled. "Of course, if you're willing to give me face on this matter, I'm willing to have a partnership with you guys in the development of the Flickering World. Currently, the Black Star Army has the most territory in the Flickering World. I believe I can provide quite a lot of help."

Many people's eyes sparkled.

Everyone knew that the Black Star Army had a huge force in the Flickering World, and the Flickering World was their goal. If they could receive Han Xiao's help, they would naturally have an easier time over there. Before they arrived, they thought that Han Xiao was just going to intimidate them. Never did they expect Black Star to be willing to provide opportunities for partnerships. This came as quite a surprise.

"We will remember what you said," Manison said calmly. "The federation doesn't want to see people causing trouble here."

Seeing that Manison had expressed his stance, various Beyond Grade As spoke as well.

"Since both Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor say so, then nobody will cause trouble in the Shattered Star Ring."

"Peacefully wait for the opening of the Flickering World. There'll be plenty of time in the future."

"Whoever dares cause trouble here shall be all of our enemies."

"Black Star, I shall give you face for this. Remember your promise."

Han Xiao smiled. "I'm glad we could come to an agreement."

At this time, Manison suddenly changed the topic. "Black Star took the lead in hosting this meeting for the sake of the Star Field's stability. It's a respectable act. However, you did not just gather all of us here for something this trivial, did you?"

Han Xiao's eye sparkled for a split second. He turned to Manison and said, "If you have anything to say, please do."

"Okay, then I shall get to the point."

Everyone looked at Manison with curiosity, not knowing what he meant.

Manison pondered for a moment before speaking. "The advanced civilizations make use of us, and we make use of the advanced civilizations. Everyone here works for various factions. We kill and fight with each other, which is very normal. However, I think that we should not be limited to the differences between factions. That's the game made by these advanced civilizations. Sometimes, we should jump out of their game and make plans for ourselves."

Everyone's expression changed slightly, and the room became silent.

This had always been a sensitive topic. No one expected Manison to talk about this at a meeting about regional stability, not caring about those present who were direct members of the advanced civilizations.

From the moment they stepped into the territory of Beyond Grade A, everyone was in the same Grade. Even though they belonged to different factions, this could not be changed.

Manison looked around and continued. "You guys know that the advanced civilizations both need us and fear us. They don't want us to have too many private relationships. An opportunity like today is very rare. As all of you have seen, we're only having a meeting, yet it stirred a storm in the universe. There are definitely countless fleets aiming their cannons in our direction, and you all know I'm not exaggerating."

"You don't need to emphasize the situation we're in," Kant said with a frown. "I don't think this is the time to discuss this topic. It's too early.

"Preparing early is better than not preparing at all," Manison said coldly.

"So, why did you mention this? Do you want all of us to form an alliance?" Gorutan said.

"Just a reminder, us forming an alliance will be the same as starting a coup d'état," Kasuyi said. There was one thing he did not say, which was that pillars of the three Universal Civilizations such as him were basically safe, so he did not want to concern himself at all.

Everyone spoke one after another, expressing their opinions and discussing the matter intensely. There were hardly any opportunities to discuss something like this usually, so this event hosted by Han Xiao became a platform to exchange opinions.

"Don't worry. It's not time yet. What I want is just a silent agreement…" Manison then looked at Han Xiao and said with a curious tone, "You're the host of this meeting. You've just been listening for quite a while and did not stop us, so what are your thoughts on this?"

Everyone turned to look at Han Xiao. Han Xiao's position was quite high in the circle, so his opinion was relatively important.

Han Xiao shrugged, shook his head, and said, "I have no other suggestions. I just feel there are too few Beyond Grade As…"

"That's right, too few." Manison sighed.

Han Xiao glanced at him.

I'm pretty sure the 'too few' we speak of means different things.

Chapter 1008: Version Start

"Like the Mechanic Emperor said, it's not time yet. Waiting is what we should do," Sorokin said with a smile.

"Yes, we need more new blood." Manison nodded. He then looked around at the new Beyond Grade As present and made his mechanical host send a virtual emoji. A smiley face popped up above his head in a bubble.

This old man actually knows to act cute quite well, Han Xiao thought.

Hila turned and looked at Han Xiao, wanting to say something, but in the end, she did not.

She did not expect these Beyond Grade As to gather and discuss such a major topic.

This meeting gradually headed in a magical direction. To Hila and the other new Beyond Grade As, the topic these Beyond Grade A bosses were talking about was way too vast. They could only listen and had no right to speak at all.

Will there be trouble discussing topics like this in our own territory? Hila was worried.

Noticing Hila's expression, Han Xiao gave her a look to not be worried at all.

Ames noticed that the two of them were giving each other looks, so she knocked on Han Xiao to make him look over and quietly said, "You actually had the same goal in mind when hosting this meeting, didn't you? Otherwise, you wouldn't have let Manison use your territory to say something this big."

"Everything is within my calculations." Han Xiao raised his brow.

After the people discussed for a while, someone finally made an important remark.

"Although we can't form an alliance, our circle indeed needs a closer relationship," Kant said with a deep voice. "The communication between us needs to be more frequent."

"The Flickering World will be a suitable reason for that," a neutral peak Beyond Grade A slowly said. "In the past, due to the limitations of factions and areas, the interactions between us were limited. Now, however, all our organizations will enter the Flickering World. This Star Field will become the platform for our communication so that the limit we had before is surpassed to a certain extent. Therefore, we need a bridge, a messenger."

Hearing what this person said, everyone subconsciously turned to look at Han Xiao.

In the known universe, Beyond Grade A organizations were not allowed to expand as much as they wanted to. They were restricted by the advanced civilizations and all kinds of rules. However, in the future, everyone would be able to enter the Flickering World, which had a very deep meaning. Even though the Beyond Grade A civilizations would only be building divisions there, they would have much easier access to one another to a certain extent. This would aid in the communication between all the Beyond Grade As and the unite of this circle, presenting an opportunity for everyone's strength to be completely united.

This needed a bridge to act as the center of the transmission of information and resources for the Beyond Grade As in the Flickering World, putting everyone together like glue.

The one who could do this had to have a strong foundation in the Flickering World, and the Black Star Army was the largest force in the Flickering World other than the dynasty…

The best candidate to build the bridge was none other than Black Star!

When more than seventy Beyond Grade As stared at one person, even though they had no hostility, the pressure was still quite terrifying. Han Xiao took a deep breath and smiled.

"If you guys need it, I'm happy to do this."

In fact, this was one of Han Xiao's goals to begin with. Although the process was a little different, he still obtained what he wanted.

Part of the reason Han Xiao had been making the Black Star Army build such a strong foundation in the Flickering World was indeed to obtain this position.

Since he was an individual with peak strength, he had to face this problem. Although the butterfly effect he triggered changed the storyline, regardless of whether the World Tree War happened before or after the Calamity of the Supers, he had to make preparations for himself in advance.

If he could be the belt of the Calamity of the Supers, he would have more power.

As pinnacles of individual power, unless one was the ruler, there was no such thing as absolute loyalty to a collective power. Ever since the start, the relationship between these two sides had always been making use of each other. The Great Mechanic Han had never even thought of giving his all to an organization. Even kids knew that eggs should not be all placed in one basket. He had to prepare to ensure his own safety.

Interests between different levels of society could never be truly unified. Unless one was willing to be used like a chess piece, these complicated questions would never be simplified.

The relationship between friends and foes changed regularly; the interests shared within a level of society were the most reliable agreement.

"Your Excellency Black Star, you really are a responsible man."

Everyone nodded at Han Xiao and smiled.

"I want to achieve a kind of silent agreement between us all." Manison looked around and said seriously, "When that day really comes, as long as someone sends a signal, I hope everyone can respond to it."

"That's reasonable," Kasuyi said calmly.

Everyone nodded and achieved an agreement.

They would not be forming an alliance. In usual times, they would still fight for their own factions. However, when the time came, they were willing to step up.

…

They then chatted about many things for a whole two days and two nights. Only then did the meeting officially end. The various Beyond Grade As took their leave and departed from the Black Star Army.

Manison walked with Kasuyi together toward the dock and chatted softly.

"The content of this meeting will definitely spread to the three Universal Civilizations, yet you didn't hide it at all. Aren't you afraid of enraging the Federation of Light?" Kasuyi asked.

Manison smiled. "Even without this meeting, fear will still exist, so I might as well give them some pressure to add on to our chips… With Black Star, the federation can't lose me, and vice versa. The difference between factions limits us, but it also restrains them."

"Everything is possible." Kasuyi shook his head. "When a tool starts to have other thoughts, no matter how useful it is, it might still be abandoned anytime."

"We're no tools." Manison's tone was calm. "Remember this, we represent the peak power an individual can achieve. Every single one of us is a treasure of this universe. Not only are we entities of violence, we're also precious special gene data banks. We represent the infinite possibilities of evolution itself, and we are never to be controlled or toyed with. If they want to abandon us, there will always be a price to pay."

"I got it. This is why you're in such a hurry, to protect yourself." Kasuyi glanced at him. "Have you finally realized that your forces are too strong?"

Manison did not reply. He paused before sighing. "Sadly… EsGod is no more. Although he isn't the same as us, he was still somewhat useful. If he doesn't stand against the three Universal Civilizations, God knows how much help he is to us."

Kasuyi's tone was strange. "You know his life span was already not long, don't you?"

"…What are you trying to say?"

"Hehe, nothing. It's just… he definitely knows about his life span more than anymore." Kasuyi smiled.

…

After the meeting ended, days passed one after another. The outside world gradually noticed a very strange phenomenon. All the Beyond Grade As who attended the meeting were keeping a shockingly low profile and did not have any conflict with each other.

Initially, with so many Beyond Grade As gathered, instability seemed inevitable. Everyone expected this to affect the order of the Star Field and thought that there would be some Beyond Grade As fighting once in a while. However, they controlled themselves and made sure the Shattered Star Ring remained orderly.

The entire universe was shocked, triggering a wave of speculation.

The reason behind this definitely lay in the meeting that Black Star hosted.

What did Black Star say to make this many Beyond Grade As so disciplined‽

The rumors kept spreading. Finally, Han Xiao arranged to have someone leak some inside information. Black Star gathered all the Beyond Grade As, representing the Shattered Star Ring, and asked all of them not to cause trouble in order to maintain the order of the Star Field.

As soon as the information was out, the entire Shattered Star Ring was amazed!

The countless local galactic residents felt touched!

Look, how responsible is Black Star? In order to maintain order, he took the risk of gathering this many Beyond Grade As in his very own territory. He's basically the agent of peace with great love in his heart!

A Beyond Grade A who's willing to speak for us, what a responsible man!

Furthermore, Black Star's action was clearly extremely effective. All the Beyond Grade As were somehow convinced and did not cause trouble, which clearly proved that Black Star's influence was extremely strong.

To have someone like this in our Star Field, it's a blessing for us!

With this, Han Xiao's reputation in the Shattered Star Ring rocketed in a short period of time.

Having done something like this, the countless galactic residents did not mind having Black Star speak for the entire Shattered Star Ring at all.

The power and position as the leader of the Star Field was now finally approved by even the galactic residents.

To the Black Star Army, this meeting was like a promotion event which increased their fame.

This meeting itself was also a noteworthy event more than enough to be written into the history books.

On the internet, more and more people felt that this was a signature event before the opening of the Flickering World, and they gave it a nickname… [Meeting of the Gods]

…

You have received 2 Universe Legendary Points.

Universe Legendary Point: Representative of the Shattered Star Ring—You have been recognized by this Star Field. In the future, you have the right to represent the Shattered Star Ring!

Universe Legendary Point: Initiator of the Meeting of the Gods—After many years, the many Beyond Grade As have gathered once again. As the initiator of this event, you've been written into the history books!

"Meeting of the Gods? How about just calling it 'Martial Arts Tournament'?"

In the headquarters of the Black Star Army, Han Xiao could not help but snidely comment on that name after looking at the notification on the interface.

Other than the name, he was quite satisfied with everything else. Two Legendary Points was quite a good reward.

The mission given by the Crimson Dynasty to maintain the order of the Star Field was also completed, giving him a few billion EXP, as well as a decent amount of the Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points.

Now that Hila had become a Beyond Grade A, he had reasons to purchase Ultimate Knowledges of the Esper class from the dynasty, so he had new ways to spend the Contribution Points. The more Hila owed him, the easier he could keep Hila in the army.

After the dynasty's mission was completed, Urranrell personally made a call to compliment him but refused to speak about the other matter… Nonetheless, no one intended to hide it.

Of course, the three Universal Civilizations knew about this. Since she did not say anything, Han Xiao understood the dynasty's stance on this. They knew that questioning their allies would do nothing, so they had an understanding with each other.

"There won't be any problems over here in the Shattered Star Ring now…" Han Xiao played around with a palm sized pet robot. "Now I'll just have to wait for the dynasty to blow the horn of the new era."

…

With so many Beyond Grade As already making a stand, the other organizations did not cause trouble either. Everyone waited patiently and peacefully for the Flickering World to open.

What Han Xiao did was make the Star Field stable. Everyone focused on making preparations as days passed.

After a few months, the day finally came.

On this day, the dynasty officially announced the opening of the Flickering World. The Inter-Star Field Stargates leading to the Flickering World were all activated!

At the same time, a notification about the start of the new version popped up on Han Xiao's interface as well—the players had finally come online!

Chapter 1009: Online

At the border of the Shattered Star Ring, Inter-Star Field Stargates with the dynasty's symbol stood in the cosmic space in a row, extending outward. The dynasty's fleets were stationed between each of the stargates. It looked like a necklace with sapphires.

On the other side of the stargates were countless fleets with symbols of different organizations, almost filling up every inch of one's sight. The sheer quantity of these fleets was a rare occurrence.

It was the day that the dynasty would open the Flickering World. These were all spaceships waiting to enter. Other than civilizations and organizations from the various Star Fields, there were also many galactic residents who could not wait to enter the Flickering World. Some were going for sightseeing purposes, some who were looking for adventure, and there were also some who wanted to search for opportunities and earn a fortune.

The time when the dynasty would announce the opening of the Flickering World got closer every second.

Seconds felt like years. Finally, the dynasty's announcement sounded from the area communication channel and on every single spaceship present.

"It's time. On behalf of the Crimson Dynasty, to the entire universe… the Flickering World is now officially open!"

The next moment, all the stargates were activated. The vortexes at the centers of these stargates started spinning, forming blue wormholes.

All the spaceships moved, forming a queue that seemed to extend infinitely, entering the various stargates one after another. It was marvelous.

Not far from these civilian stargates were VIP military stargates for the dynasty's allies.

Black Star's ride was in the queue. The various officers stood in the command room, looking at the person standing before them.

With his back turned away, Han Xiao looked through the porthole at the seemingly endless sea of ships not far away and softly asked, "Did you guys hear that?"

"Hear what?"

"The sound of the new era breaking through its shell."

Han Xiao chuckled softly.

In his eyes, the interface was hovering before him, notifications were popping up one after another.

Version 4.0 Activated!

Fetching data… Fetching data complete!

Player forum opened.

Welcome to Galaxy Version 4.0—[Flickering World]!

This day has finally come… Han Xiao took a deep breath.

This was an important turning point version. In Version 4.0, the players would officially enter the stage of the fight within Galaxy. They would interfere with history and achieve notorious names such as Cancer of the Universe and The Fourth Calamity.

The strength the players controlled would truly cross a limit, allowing them to enter a standard where they would have a completely different influence on the universe. With the Lv.150 level limit of the version, the players would have a consistent strength of Grade B+!

Once the tinder of anarchism was ignited, it would engulf the entire universe.

At this time, Sylvia seemed to have received some kind of report. She took out her communicator and looked at it. Her pupils then constricted, and she said with a deep voice, "Army Commander, those immortals of the army have appeared again."

Han Xiao finally turned around, looked at everyone, and nodded slightly.

"Bring all of them over."

…

At the same time in the Black Star Army headquarters…

Before the version update, many players logged off in the Black Star Army headquarters. Once they logged in again, with countless flashes of white light, the empty hall suddenly became crowded, boisterous, and noisy like a wet market.

"Galaxy, I'm back!"

"I've already bought ten cans of Blue Bull, brothers!"

"Did the new version repair the bug that causes us to not be able to go naked?"

"There they are! I knew it! Those 'No-Pants-Supporters' never left!"

"By the way, are there any new functions added? Since this is already so close to reality, why not add a function to reproduce? Creating offspring is the soul of a social system!"

"If we could really reproduce, this would be the most god tier game ever created."

Countless players cheered in excitement. Meanwhile, at the edge of the crowd, a group of professional players logged in one after another. The members of the four biggest clubs of China were basically all there, as well as Frenzied Sword, Maple Moon, Bun-Hit-Dog, and so on.

"Yo, the maximum level of the new version has increased to Lv.150." King Admiral looked at the interface and smiled.

"The difference in the cost of leveling up is way too huge." Second Prince could not help but twitch.

"The Black Star Army's faction interface is still here. The army did not shut down." Frenzied Sword checked the faction interface instantly.

"How could the Black Star Army shut down so easily?" Maple Moon softly murmured.

The players in the other Star Fields would have to worry about the faction they were disappearing after the version update, meaning all the Contribution Points they had farmed before that would go to waste. This was why stable factions were the most popular.

The players in the Black Star Army, however, had no such worries. After three versions, they already had complete faith in their faction leader, Han Xiao.

At the end of the previous version, the army's position was already stabilized. The Arcane Church lost, EsGod was defeated, and they obtained a super business called Evolutionary Totems. Even the players knew that the army would not shut down easily.

At the start of the new version, the most important thing was finding out what happened during the version update as well as what the situation in the universe was now. This had already become the players' habit.

Many players took out their communicators to look at the calendar and were met with shock.

"Wait, it's Galaxy Calendar Year 729 now‽"

"It was year 709 when we logged off, right?"

"This means that the duration of this version update is twenty years‽"

"I thought the Version 3.0 update duration was long enough, but Version 4.0 doubled it!"

Frenzied Sword exchanged looks with Maple Moon. A tint of excitement flashed across both of their eyes.

Twenty years!

That's not a short time.

How much will the Black Star Army have grown?

While exciting thoughts flashed across their minds, the notification sound from communicators suddenly appeared one almost simultaneously in the hall. Every player received a new message sent by the internal program of the army.

They quickly opened it. Virtual screens expanded before them, all showing Han Xiao's face and playing the same recording.

In the recording, Han Xiao sat up straight, only showing half of his body as he spoke with a very formal tone.

"Comrades, I'm Black Star. In the past twenty years, we have obtained countless achievements, especially in the Flickering World. The army now has ten Star Systems as its territory, thanks to the effort of each and every member that helped to achieve the glory we have achieved today.

"Now, the Flickering World will be entering its fourth exploration phase and will be officially opened to the public. People from the entire universe will swarm into this Star Field. This is a new era; we need to grab the opportunity and charge forward… I hereby send a recruitment order to all army members. The army needs you… The Flickering World needs you!"

The short recording ended here. The pupils of the players gradually enlarged as they received a huge chunk of information from this message.

It's now the fourth exploration phase? I seem to remember the first phase not having ended when we logged off!

The army has ten Star Systems as its territory in the Flickering World? What's going on with that‽

What did the army do in the past twenty years‽

Everyone was extremely intrigued.

What they did not know was that this recording was a 'cutscene' Han Xiao had specially made for the players to help them understand the situation quickly.

This time, Hao Tian suddenly realized one thing. "Wait, if it's now the fourth exploration phase for the Flickering World, is our main storyline mission still there?"

The various professional players realized this too. Their original main storyline mission was still in the stage of the first exploration phase. Due to the version update directly skipping twenty years, would their missions be canceled?

If it was gone, it would be quite a loss.

They hastily opened the interface before relief flooded through them. The main storyline mission of the [Flickering World] was still there. The mission requirements had just changed into developing the Black Star Army's territory as well as exploring the few Star Clusters of the fourth exploration phase.

"Although it's changed, it's still exploration."

Many players shook their heads but were not excited, a little disappointed even.

They were curious about the information given through the recording, but they were not very interested in the Flickering World's mission. This was because the army players had already tried this mission in the previous version. Although the goal had changed, the way to do the mission looked the same to them.

Pioneering new Star Fields was fresh indeed, but it lacked opportunities for battles. In the previous version, many players were tired of doing the Flickering World mission and preferred to do hiring missions in the Shattered Star Ring.

This was actually quite common, as the Flickering World main storyline the players experienced in Version 3.0 was actually just half of what it was supposed to be. The dynasty was the only organization pioneering, so of course, it lacked battles.

At this time, they were suddenly stunned upon realizing one thing.

Did Black Star say… the Flickering World is now open to the public?

So, the organizations from the other Star Fields are entering?

Then… what about the players of the other Star Fields?

Frenzied Sword immediately went online to do some research and confirmed the legitimacy of this information very soon. Not only that, the organizations of the various Star Fields were also recruiting Supers on a large scale to go to the Flickering World.

The biggest impact this had on the players was that the inter Star Field channels were now completely open!

Compared to the last version, the players had a method to cross between Star Fields!

The people quickly logged into the forums.

As expected, all of the forum boards were frenzied by this information!

Frenzied Sword understood immediately. With his eyes sparkling brightly, he yelled, "This is… a world server!"

All the players in the various Star Fields would finally be able to come to the same stage, gathering in the Flickering World!

What did this mean?

National wars!

The speculation that Galaxy Times had made about crossing between Star Fields became real!

All the players in the hall were astonished and thrilled!

"Holy, it's the world server!"

"Hahaha, I knew this day would come!"

"Finally, national wars! I can't wait!"

The next moment, they realized something else. The Flickering World would be the world server of this version, but as the members of the army, they had already entered in the previous version in advance.

How much of an advantage would that be‽

The players were overjoyed!

"Oh my god, we have already marked our territory in Flickering World in the last version. We're one entire version ahead!"

"I'm crying! I felt that the exploration was too boring and went back to the Shattered Star Ring to do hiring missions!"

"With such a big advantage, we'll have a blast this version!"

The players who had gone to the Shattered Star Ring from the Constellation Corridor in the previous version all felt relieved. Had they not followed the Black Star Army back then, how could they have gained such privileges‽

On the other side, the players of the other Star Fields were in an uproar.

In Version 1.0, Black Star led some players in the universe in advance. Okay, we'll put up with it.

In Version 2.0, the Black Star Army became the guiding faction, making the Shattered Star Ring players ahead of everyone else again. Alright, we'll put up with it too.

In Version 3.0, the Black Star Army had a Beyond Grade A, leading to it being connected to a Universal Civilization before everyone else. Well, we will put up with it. Sooner or later, our day will come.

But now, in Version 4.0, the Black Star Army is god damn one step ahead again‽

Are you guys dogs‽

Why are you always the ones enjoying the most benefits?

What happened to the law? What happened to the rules‽

Do you fu*king… still need more members?

Only then did they realize that Black Star had already built a foundation for them in the previous version, and they saw what an advantage they had gained from this faction!

The various army players could only praise how amazing the game experience was.

With such a reliable faction, the players of the other Star Fields and countries could only be jealous.

This was the only one in the entire universe!

Now, the army players' interest for the Flickering World was never higher.

Initially, many felt that the exploration game style was too boring. Now, however, as the Flickering World became the world server for the players, it would become the most chaotic and exciting Star Field in the entire universe. There would be countless and never-ending conflicts. This was the full experience of the [Flickering World] main storyline!

Having this thought, Frenzied Sword and the others quickly went to research about what the Black Star Army had done in the past years, wanting to know what advantages their faction had exactly in the Flickering World.

As soon as he opened the Black Star Army's records, Frenzied Sword's eyes opened extremely wide.

He had made a lot of speculations, and he was mentally prepared too. However, the first thing he saw was completely different from what he imagined, and it stupefied him completely.

"What the hell? Old Black became a god‽"

Chapter 1010: World Server, Start of Revenge

The records clearly stated the major events that the Black Star Army had been through during the twenty-year update. Frenzied Sword filtered it to be between the years 709 and 729, arranged from the earliest to the latest.

And this highlighted record was the first thing he saw.

'Galaxy Calendar Year 710, Black Star became a Mechanical Deity!'

This term blew Frenzied Sword's fragile mind. There was only one thought in his head.

Black Star has become a God!

This name was very intimidating, but Frenzied Sword calmed down and did some research. Only then did he understand that 'Mechanical Deity' had a different meaning to what he expected. It was the nickname of Divine Throne Mechanics, which meant that Black Star had become a peak Beyond Grade A.

"That startled me. I thought Old Black was going to ascend above."

Slightly relieved, Frenzied Sword continued to browse through, noticing another few major events in the same year.

Firstly, when the first exploration phase ended, the army received seven Star Systems as its territory and became the biggest armed organization in the Flickering World. Secondly, the Germinal Financial Group was formed, starting its fight with the Limitless Financial Group in the various commercial industries. Thirdly, the plan of building Super Academies was executed; the Black Star Army had already built tens of thousands of Super Academies in the Shattered Star Ring, raising countless Supers, some of which were chosen to become members of the army.

In the same period, after Black Star became a Mechanical Deity, he had fought the Tyrant once again, beating him with just an avatar. This confirmed his position as the strongest individual in the Shattered Star Ring. Not long after, the Mechanic Emperor invaded, and conflict erupted, which was ended by the dynasty interfering to force the Mechanic Emperor away.

Frenzied Sword could almost feel how intense things were back then from just the words.

After that, the army entered into a low-profile development period. Black Star no longer featured in the top news as often and quietly remained in the Flickering World. Then, in the year 716, the war with the Kunde Race erupted. This was the first sub-Star Cluster native civilization that was eliminated.

However, the records of this period of history were very sparse and vague. There was only a rough conclusion, and nothing could be found online. The only valuable clue that Frenzied Sword had was that the Black Star Army was now responsible for the transformation task of the Kunde Race, which had been going on for thirteen years.

After the Kunde Race war, the army remained low profile during the second and the third phases as well. Everything had been peaceful and calm until only recently, when the army revealed its second Beyond Grade A, someone they were familiar with.

"Hila has become a Beyond Grade A‽" Seeing the name, Frenzied Sword's eyes widened in shock.

No players born on Planet Aquamarine were unfamiliar with Hila. Be it when she was the villain 'Crimson Snake' in the Germinal Organization or when she fought on their side during the Mutation Disaster of Version 2.0, these impressions were all deeply rooted in each and every player of Planet Aquamarine… mainly because Hila's astonishing beaty made the deepest impression.

All the old players knew that Black Star and Hila went way back, from Planet Aquamarine to the universe. She was an old friend who appeared very long ago.

Frenzied Sword had worked hard for four versions in the army, so the army was his home faction. Now that his own faction had another person to rely on, no words could describe how pleasantly surprised Frenzied Sword was.

Suppressing his excitement, Frenzied Sword turned to the last bit of the records—the 'Meeting of the Gods' that Black Star had hosted just recently, where he summoned more than seventy Beyond Grade As to gather in one place.

Seeing the shocking influence Black Star had, even his heart skipped a beat. After twenty years, how had Black Star's position in the universe already achieved this standard‽

"My god…"

Before Frenzied Sword could pull himself out of the shock, loud laughter exploded from beside him, startling him.

"Hahaha! Nice!"

Bun-Hit-Dog guffawed into the sky with his hands on his hips. His mouth was opened so wide that it almost looked like it was going to crack. His smile was like the smile of an evil hound.

Frenzied Sword covered his ears. "What are you laughing about?"

"Look at this. During the twenty years of the version update, look at how much has happened to the Black Star Army. This is all material for videos. This is a treasure!"

Bun-Hit-Dog was exhilarated. With so much material, he would not have to worry about having nothing to make videos about for quite some time.

He planned to include all the things the army achieved during the update, to help the army players know about the army's history. Just thinking about it made him certain it would be popular, and he was sure he would probably go viral again!

With that in mind, Bun-Hit-Dog took a look around and realized that many people were looking at their communicators and browsing through the history of the army. He could not help but open the forums. He used his talent as the number one reporter and uploaded the army records. At the same time, he gave the post an attractive title—'Shock! The Army's Glorious Twenty Years!'

At the start of a new version, countless players were exchanging information on the forums with excitement. As soon as this post was uploaded, it attracted a lot of attention in the Shattered Star Ring panel.

Army Commander's Big PP: "Old Black is fierce as always!"

Fulliron Alchemist: "Old Black has been like this ever since the first version. He's undoubtedly a legend at starting from zero. Is there anyone in the entire universe more amazing than him?"

Stupid Cat: "The ID of the brother above…"

Magnet Link: "I didn't expect Hila to become a Beyond Grade A too. By the way, do you guys remember Black Star's origin? He started as a traitor of the Germinal Organization, and Hila was a member of the Germinal Organization too… Tsk, what an organization."

Mysterious Man: "Germinal doesn't die; it only hides!"

While Frenzied Sword was deeply drawn to the stupid comments, he was suddenly dragged by Maple Moon toward the dock.

"Stop reading, let's quickly go to the Flickering World, as soon as possible."

With someone taking the lead, the players of the entire Black Star Army headquarters started moving and swarmed toward the dock.

…

The forums, which had been quiet for quite some time, suddenly became extremely boisterous. After the army players scattered around various places understood what was going on in this version, they immediately headed to the nearest army base and boarded a fleet toward the Flickering World. No one wanted to miss out on the world server.

As members of the Black Star Army, since they had such a huge advantage, they were not going to waste it. Every second counted.

In the eyes of the foreign professional clubs, the exclusive faction advantage the Chinese players in the Shattered Star Ring had was just about the worst news they could receive. The guilds of the various countries hastily started private meetings to discuss the matter.

"Things are not looking good. The main storyline of this version is way too good for the Chinese players. The world server is right beside the Shattered Star Ring, and they've already been there. When our guilds enter the world server, it will be very difficult for us to compete with these top Chinese guilds such as Dynasty and Long Sky. We will certainly be at a disadvantage in Guild Wars, which will very likely affect the growth of our professional players."

"In the previous season, three teams out of the top four teams were from China. We can't keep letting them have such dominance over us no matter what this season."

"It's going to be tough. The Black Star Army is basically going to be the locals in the world server, and it's backing the Chinese players up. Are we going to join the Black Star Army?"

"It's very difficult for the professional players and the guild top players to join other factions on a completely different side, or all the effort spent in the previous versions will go to waste."

"That's right. Even if we do change factions, we can't compete with what the Chinese players have built up in the Black Star Army over several versions."

"Let's observe how things go for now, see how the Chinese guilds respond to this. If it's not ideal… we might have to unite the clubs from the other countries."

Although this was just the first day of the start of the new version, the situation had already made the clubs from various countries agitated.

After all, the faction advantage for the Chinese players was way too huge. While the Americans, Frenches, Koreans, and Japanese were feeling indignant, they all had thoughts of forming an alliance.

…

"So, all the players have moved…"

Han Xiao smiled after hearing Phillip's report.

With the opening of the Flickering World, the traffic of this Star Field would explode. There would be demanded businesses everywhere, bringing opportunities. It would be like the age of digging for gold. The advantages the Black Star Army had been building for so long would now finally show their effects.

To him, this was not the stage of exploration but the stage of harvest!

With the territory he had, it basically meant he could just sit and watch while others brought him profit.

Countless organizations would be competing there, so the players would have plenty of mission resources and countless ways to gain EXP, as well as no shortage of opportunities to fight.

However, it's not that easy to harvest EXP at the start of the new version, Han Xiao thought.

The players' current main goal was continuing to level up, so most of the EXP they earned would be spent on levels. It was not time to harvest yet.

In order to quickly level up, Han Xiao had to wait for the players for a period of time.

However, Han Xiao was in no hurry. Quite a number of new items had been added to the army's store. No matter how petty the players were, he could make the players open their wallets. The efficiency of getting EXP from this still far exceeded him doing missions himself.

His level, which had remained stagnant for so long, could now finally increase rapidly!

Players from various nations swarming into the world server was an opportunity to enlarge his farm. For the Black Star Army to attract outside players now, Han Xiao no longer had to do much. The advantages he had obtained over the versions and his positive name were the core appeals.

The bigger the advantage the army players had in the Flickering World, the more attractive the Black Star Army would be. However, due to exactly this reason, Han Xiao could guess that some foreign clubs might get together to fight the Chinese players. Therefore, helping the army players was a must.

In his previous life during Version 4.0, the clubs from the various nations kept forming alliances and betraying each other in all kinds of ways that made things almost look like they were in the 'Romance of the Three Kingdoms' era.

His plan was to use the army's territory as a base to provide resources while helping the army players become stronger in Version 4.0. At the same time, he would use the players' power to create trouble, attacking the enemies while protecting their own forces, attracting more players, and satisfying his need to level up.

"Modo Civilization, Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy…" Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

It would still take the players of the various Star Fields some time to arrive at the Flickering World. Other than the players, these two matters were what he needed to deal with the most.

The Kunde Race's mission required him to take revenge against the Modo Civilization. Back then, the dynasty told him to only fully execute the plan when the Flickering World was completely open. Now, the Modo Civilization's troops had also entered the Flickering World. On his turf, Han Xiao had a hundred ways to make life hell for the Modo Civilization.

The mission reward was the [Proof of Leadership] talent, which was extremely useful for the leader of a huge organization like him. Han Xiao had waited more than ten years, and he could finally make a move.

The moment when the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy appeared would also soon arrive, and there would probably be quite a number of organizations who would fight for it. Han Xiao had already sent troops off toward the location marked in EsGod's heritage.

He had also researched its owner in his previous life. If he remembered correctly, it should be an ordinary person called Evans. He already had the location of Evans, who was also in the Flickering World and under his surveillance.

If there was no one under his command that could control the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, he would find the owner from his previous life, who would definitely be able to control it.

While pondering, Han Xiao told Phillip, "Search for the current location of the Modo Civilization's fleet… I shall send them a huge 'gift' to begin."

Chapter 1011: I'm Going to Beat You Up. What Are You Going to Do About It?

The Flickering World's Dawn Star Cluster was an area completely controlled by the army. It was also the first station after entering the Flickering World. As the fleets of countless organizations swarmed in, this Star Cluster became countless times more boisterous, gradually turning this place into part of the galactic society.

There was profit to be found everywhere in the Flickering World at this time; all of the Star Clusters had demands that were not met. The outside organizations mainly had to choose where to set foot.

The transit stations at the entrances of the Star Field contained huge profits. Many organizations and galactic residents scattered and headed right toward the transit stations as soon as they entered the Star Field, while more organizations went other ways to the further Star Clusters to look for opportunities.

Among which, the Modo Civilization was one of the organizations that headed to the further Star Clusters. Their goal was to develop the territories of the third and the fourth phase.

The reasoning was simple—the further the Star Clusters were, the less they had been developed, which meant that not only would there be more holes to fill in the various industries, but the dynasty's control would also not be as strong compared to the earlier Star Clusters. And this was extremely important to Super Star Cluster civilizations.

The Super Star Cluster civilizations knew very well that the dynasty would definitely not let them develop comfortably. Therefore, almost all the Super Star Cluster civilizations gave up on the first and second phase territories.

Even an ordinary person could see that the few Star Clusters that were about to be explored in the fourth phase would become crucial stages of competition for the external organizations.

Inside the main ship's command room, a tall man stood before the command post, looking up at the star map. His face gave off a cold and tough vibe, and his expression was solemn.

He was Roddick, Senior General of the Modo Civilization, currently the commander of the 'Expedition Fleet'.

'Expedition Fleet' was the name of this fleet, a new fleet the Modo Civilization had built just for the Flickering World. They had gathered a large number of elites, among whom Roddick stood above all and took on the responsibility of commanding this crucial fleet. Clearly, the upper echelons of the Modo Civilization had high hopes for him.

A member of the Modo Race who was wearing a government official uniform asked, "Commander, how long till we cross the first and second phase areas?"

This man was a senior officer of the Modo Civilization. His name was Lagos as translated into the universal language. He was given the position of the inspector of the Expedition Fleet, responsible for monitoring Roddick.

Lagos did not have much power in his hands, so he could not interfere with Roddick under normal circumstances. His main job was to report the situation to the upper echelons, as well as contact the temporary stronghold the Modo Civilization had built in the Shattered Star Ring. He also managed the resources and manpower.

Hearing the inspector's question, Roddick stared at the Star Cluster and replied without turning his head. "The time spent in the first and second phases was the longest. The Crimson Dynasty and their allies had already built full sets of long distance portals long ago. Travelling was very convenient, so it should only take about seventeen days to arrive at the third phase territory. Most of the time will be spent on the area between the stargates."

Then, Roddick squinted and added, "Actually, the quickest route is through Garu. The Black Star Army's territory is connected in one line by the stargates, so the transportation there is even easier. But, as you know, the risk of that is too high, so we have no choice but to take a detour."

"Well, I can only say that's karma," Lagos said with resignation.

The Modo Civilization knew very well that they had already insulted the dynasty because of what happened with the Kunde Race, so they knew clearly that the dynasty would target them in the Flickering World.

The best route toward the further Star Clusters was through the Black Star Army's territory, but Roddick did not dare go close to the Garu Star Cluster, so they could only take another route that was not as popular and convenient.

Lagos shook his head and said, "The dynasty might send people to attack us. Stay vigilant."

"I know. The military equipped us with such a strong defensive force because of exactly that. There are plenty of armed fleets and high Grade Supers. The Expedition Fleet's size is sufficient to even participate in a galactic war."

"Hmm, you're right… But the dynasty will definitely not send their official army to attack us in the Flickering World. Even if someone does come for us, it'll definitely be the dynasty's ally," Lagos said.

Roddick frowned. "Usual enemies are not a problem, but a Beyond Grade A would be very difficult to deal with."

"Don't have to worry about that. The upper echelons have already made private agreements with some Beyond Grade As to provide us with help." Lagos smiled with confidence.

"Who are they?"

Roddick, however, was not surprised. Super Star Cluster civilizations making short-term deals with Beyond Grade As was nothing new. This was also a form of business for some Beyond Grade As.

Given how important the Flickering World was, it was impossible for the Super Star Cluster civilization to not make any preparations. They all brought out tons of resources to hire top-tier combatants, which led to some Beyond Grade As earning quite the fortune. Many of them also accepted jobs from multiple civilizations at the same time.

"Those Galactic Black Market people with Beast Ancestor and Secret Master in the lead, as well as some neutral Beyond Grade As… Oh, some of the Beyond Grade As of the federation and the church have also made deals with us privately… Hehe, they were probably given orders by their leaders to use us to attract the dynasty's attention." Lagos could not help but sneer.

The federation and the church's intentions were as clear as day, but the Super Star Cluster civilizations did not mind being used, as they would benefit from it temporarily as well.

"Even though we have allies, that'll only help us when we pass through the first and second phase territories. I'm worried the dynasty might attack before that," Roddick said with a deep voice. "After all, most of the organizations are taking the Black Star Army's route. There aren't many allies who are taking a detour like us."

"One of the hired Beyond Grade As is coming behind us just to protect us. The upper echelons convinced him to make a detour."

"Who?"

"The Blackhole Edge's neutral Beyond Grade A, Garoze, nicknamed Leader of Colossuses."

"That Summoner? I've heard about him."

Roddick operated the star map for a while, marking the location of Garoze's fleet, which was not far behind the Expedition Fleet.

This made him feel less worried.

"This way, we won't have to worry about someone attacking us," Roddick said coldly. "With our armed forces, as long as the dynasty dares to send someone here, they'll see that they might not be the stronger side."

At this time, a communication request came. It was from one of the Three Kings of the Modo Civilization.

The two of them immediately straightened their backs and put on serious expressions. They then accepted the communication request, and people appeared on the virtual screen.

The two of them saluted. "Your Excellencies."

"What's the situation now?" one of the Three Kings asked.

As leaders of the civilization, asking about the situation this soon after the Expedition Fleet entered the Flickering World seemed too impatient, but the Flickering World was way too significant to the Super Star Cluster civilizations. This was an opportunity to completely overthrow the situation they were stuck in; no amount of attention seemed too much.

Furthermore, they had angered the dynasty not too long ago. Now that their forces entered the dynasty's territory, the Three Kings were even more on edge.

"We're still on the way," Roddick answered formally.

"Have you encountered any problems?"

"Everything is normal."

"Hmm, no matter what happens, focus on protecting the logistics team," the leader of the Modo Race said.

The armed fleet existed to protect the logistics team, which carried all kinds of necessary resources and devices to develop a Star Field. The armed spaceships could be depleted, but it would be extremely problematic if something happened to these important resources. Although they would still be able to resupply from their temporary stronghold in the Shattered Star Ring, it would tremendously slow down the speed of the development.

All the forces in the Flickering World were competitors. Every second wasted meant profit lost, which would then affect the Modo Civilization's strategy.

Roddick nodded before speaking with a serious tone. "Your Excellencies Three Kings, don't worry, I won't let our enemies…"

Boom!

Before his sentence even ended, the entire main ship trembled. The crew in the command room fell to the ground!

Roddick staggered, too. He grabbed the table to regain his balance.

"What's going on‽" He was shocked and furious.

"Commander, many unknown ships are approaching at a high speed and have attacked us."

The radar showed that fleets appeared from every direction, surrounded them, and fired at them.

Furthermore, the alarm also mentioned that the opponent had deployed a large number of Space Stabilization Anchors in the area. This meant that they had charged right into a trap, and their hyperdrive was completely stopped, which was what caused the trembling. Even the stabilizing device inside the spaceship could not fully resolve the shock from suddenly stopping at such a high speed.

"We're still some distance away from the next stargate. Is this an ambush?" Lagos was stunned.

They were just discussing the fact that there might be enemies, and speaking of the devil…

"What's the enemy's identity?" Roddick questioned.

"I—I don't know. The spaceships they're using are general models. There are no symbols on these ships, so we don't know which organization these belong to," the observer said with a nervous tone.

The communication from the Three Kings had not ended yet. They all saw this and frowned.

The leader of the Modo Civilization said with a deep voice and a grave expression, "Roddick, I'll leave this to you. You must defeat the enemy."

"Understood." Roddick had a decisive look on his face. He immediately started to command the fleet and gave out orders one after another.

The Expedition Fleet responded quickly. It shrank its formation to protect the logistics team while firing back. Neither fleet was huge. In fact, the Modo Civilization's fleet was a little larger.

Roddick showcased his excellent commanding talent, and the Modo Civilization firmly stood their ground.

Although they were ambushed, Roddick did not choose to break away but remained in place.

His confidence came from both the fact that his armed fleet was stronger and the Beyond Grade A Garoze who was not far behind. As long as Garoze arrived at the battlefield, he would be able to fight back using the strength of a Beyond Grade A.

Roddick's style was tough and unbending; he was one to always take revenge. He was furious about being interrupted out of nowhere while speaking with the Three Kings. Compared to escaping, he would rather defeat the enemies.

"I'll let Garoze join the battle immediately." Lagos hastily took out his communicator to call for backup.

"Okay, do it quickly." Roddick sneered. "No matter who they are, they're not leaving easily."

…

At the same time, Garoze's fleet, which was not far away, noticed the situation as well.

"Someone really attacked them? I thought they were paranoid."

Inside the command room, Garoze murmured to himself.

This was not his first time accepting a job from a Super Star Cluster civilization. As a neutral Beyond Grade A with no background, this was a key source of income for him. He had also accepted jobs from seven other organizations to protect their fleets.

Everyone knew that due to the competition in the Flickering World, this place would very soon become a heaven for mercenaries. Even many Beyond Grade As had joined in.

"Your Excellency Garoze, what do we do? Should we go over and help?" his assistant asked.

Garoze nodded. He was hired, so he had to do his duty.

However, just as he was about to make the order, the sound of a communicator ringing suddenly appeared in the room.

Beep beep beep!

Garoze looked down and was surprised.

It was his private communicator!

Who would call at this time?

As he took out the communicator to take a look, Garoze's pupils constricted.

The caller was shockingly Black Star!

The two of them did not have much interaction in the past, they had only met during the Meeting Of The Gods and exchanged their private numbers.

I wonder why he is calling me…

Suppressing the doubts in his mind, Garoze walked to the side, picked up the communication, and asked carefully, "Your Excellency Black Star, what is it?"

"I have one thing I need your help with." Han Xiao's voice came out of the communicator.

"Please do tell."

"I need you to do nothing."

"Do nothing? What do you mea…"

Initially, Garoze did not understand, but then, it suddenly occurred to him.

"The fleet that attacked the Modo Civilization, it's…"

Han Xiao interrupted him and asked calmly, "Can you do that?"

Garoze was extremely troubled. With the Black Star Army's interference, this matter was no longer simple. The Modo Civilization would most likely be devastated, and from the depths of his heart, he did not want to take part in this.

However, he was right beside the battlefield. If he did not take action, his reputation would definitely be tainted.

Garoze looked a little troubled. "Your Excellency Black Star, I've already accepted the job from the Modo Civilization. If I don't do anything…"

With an expressionless face, Han Xiao coldly said, "If you don't want trouble, back away. This is not something you can interfere with."

Then, he hung up without waiting for Garoze's reply.

In my territory, you listen to me! Han Xiao did not even bother with bullsh*ting with the Modo Civilization. I'm going to beat you up, that's all!

What, you're not happy? Sure, don't come to the Flickering World then!

The army was now the biggest organization in the Flickering World after operating there for so long. If he did not act like a menace, who had the right to‽

Garoze's face became stiff as he was secretly shocked. In his mind, Black Star was a very friendly person who made friends everywhere he went. He did not expect Black Star's tone to be this firm.

Looks like this is more serious than I thought. If I interfere, it probably won't turn out well for me.

Also, if I ignore Black Star's threat, won't I follow the steps of that seven-eyed dude?

Garoze trembled uncontrollably.

The assistant came over and said, "Your Excellency, Lagos is already hurrying us. Are you going to give the order?"

Garoze hesitated for a few seconds before suddenly waving his hand. "Don't help, just watch from here."

The assistant was stunned, but seeing how firm Garoze was, he could only tell the fleet to standby at the edge of the battlefield.

"Sigh. This is a big loss." Garoze smiled bitterly in his mind.

He was just an ordinary Beyond Grade A. There was no way he could mess with someone like Black Star. Be it in terms of his strength or organization, he was far inferior.

It was shameful to be forced away by just a few words. Garoze had his pride too, and he did not want to be a coward.

But, facing Black Star, how could he not back down?

After having been a Beyond Grade A for so many years and still not having improved much, Garoze knew long ago that he could not mess with the peak Beyond Grade As. He was just a neutral Beyond Grade A without any background. If Black Star wanted to kill him, there would be nothing holding him back at all!

Furthermore, during the Meeting of the Gods not long ago, Black Star had taken on the task of maintaining communication between all the Beyond Grade As. He had to give Han Xiao face even just because of this.

…

As time passed, the Expedition Fleet and the ambush fleet fought intensely.

In the main ship's command room, after Roddick gave a few orders and finally had a little bit of time, he immediately turned around and yelled at Lagos.

"What's going on with Garoze? Why isn't he here yet‽"

Lagos was covered in sweat. "They just stopped there. I've already hurried them many times, but they refuse to join the battle no matter what. I—I don't know why either!"

Seeing their reinforcements back away right before them, he was stupefied and utterly confused.

"Outsiders are not reliable at all!" Roddick was furious. He slammed the table and said, "We're not going to wait for him! All units, listen. Change the strategy and charge toward the enemy's formation!"

However, before the order was sent out, a sudden change occurred!

Unrest suddenly erupted in the logistics fleet that was protected behind multiple layers of armed fleets.

The logistics spaceships suddenly pushed away the armed spaceships in all directions, instantly causing chaos on their side!

"What's happening‽"

Roddick's expression changed drastically.

"R-report. The operating artificial intelligences of these logistics spaceships were infiltrated and have gone out of control. We've lost contact with the crew!"

Like he had just awoken from a dream, Roddick clenched his teeth filled with rage and squeezed out the words from between his teeth.

"God damn it, it's a Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanic!"

Chapter 1012: The First Shot in the Flickering World

The logistics fleet was made up of mainly transport ships, cargo ships, and industrial ships, which were all rather large. Although they were also equipped with weapons and shields, their mobility and firepower could not match up to the combat spaceships with the same technology level. Therefore, they hid in the center of the formation, protected by the armed fleet.

At this point of time, some of the logistics spaceships were virtually hacked, bashing at the guard ships, instantly tearing up the Expedition Fleet's formation. And these ships' weapons were put to use, too, firing continuously at the back of the guard ships.

As the exterior part of the armed fleet did not put much energy into their rear shields, they were immediately damaged. Many divisions burst into panic.

"Control these spaceships, hold on! Other spaceships, strengthen the artificial intelligence firewall immediately, and increase the system self-check frequency!" Roddick did not have time to think about anything else. He quickly commanded the fleet to deal with this sudden situation.

Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanics had always been weapons of mass destruction in galactic wars that no fleet would want to face.

The most direct solution would be to turn off the artificial intelligence on all of the spaceships, but in that case, the chain of command would collapse, which would be no different from suicide.

Currently, controlling the spaceships and their communication with the quantum network was the best method. Although other methods such as magic or biological systems existed, they had more shortcomings.

For example, magic could be used to modify spaceships into an organism, but the cost of doing so would be many times more expensive, and the efficiency in controlling such spaceships was much lower than the quantum network technology, not to mention their vastly inferior communication distance and efficiency. Also, they would not be as secure as the firewall of the quantum network and would just be as fragile when facing Mages or Psychics.

All the civilizations in the universe had methods to prevent Virtual Intrusion, but whether it would work or not depended on how strong the opponent was.

Facing Han Xiao, who was now a peak Beyond Grade A, the artificial intelligence defense measures of the Modo Civilization clearly could not last; it could only stall for time until the other spaceships were hacked but not truly prevent Han Xiao from intruding. No matter how much they struggled, their lines of defense would still be penetrated one after another.

As for the spaceships that Han Xiao had already gained control of, taking them back was an almost impossible mission.

In the battlefield, the Expedition Fleet was being attacked from both sides. They had no choice but to send a part of their fleet to turn around and contain the panic caused by the haywire spaceships. The situation became very chaotic, and the Modo Civilization fleet was slowly losing their grip.

Some of the out of control spaceships penetrated the formation and were obtained by the attacker. The rest launched suicidal attacks not just on the guard ships around but also on the other logistic spaceships that had yet to lose control.

To prevent more damage, Roddick had no choice but to order the destruction of some logistic spaceships. Watching those logistic ships with key resources turn into fireworks in the cosmic space, his face was almost twisted.

There were people everywhere in the Flickering World. Although this route was unpopular, there were still people who passed by. The impact created by this battlefield spread out and very quickly attracted the attention of quite many fleets that passed by.

Most did not want to get dragged into this mess and hastily left.

But there were also some organizations that cautiously moved closer to watch from afar. Seeing the symbol of the Modo Civilization on the fleet, they chattered in the public communication channel.

"The Modo Civilization's fleet has been attacked?"

"Who did this? Who dares mess with a Super Star Cluster civilization and still seems to have the upper hand?"

"We've just entered the Flickering World, but this attacker already has such a large fleet, so it can basically be confirmed that the attacker is from the dynasty."

"The attacker hid their organization symbol, so we don't know who it is."

"Tsk, the very reason they hid their identity is to make sure not to leave any evidence. Watch what you say, and don't get into trouble."

Although these organizations that were passing by were gossiping, none of them would interfere—no one wanted to get into trouble.

As the intense battle carried on, Roddick made his fleet keep moving while fighting. The battlefield kept moving closer to the location of the next stargate station.

There were dynasty fleets stationed at the stargate station. Although Roddick knew that the attacker definitely had something to do with the dynasty, the dynasty could not attack the Modo Civilization publicly, or the negative impact would be too big. Not only would that affect the dynasty's promise to open the Flickering World freely, it would also be a stain on their politics.

Growing up in a Super Star Cluster civilization, he knew all too well about what the three Universal Civilizations were like. In his eyes, not only were the three Universal Civilizations bullies, they also wanted to maintain a good image so that their position as rulers would be approved.

With such a large crowd watching, Roddick knew that the stargate station's dynasty fleet had to reinforce him. Therefore, as long as he could move close enough to the stargate station, he would be able to force the attacker to retreat.

After the battle lasted a while longer, the attacker finally stopped the attacks and backed out of the battlefield. The fleet then entered hyperdrive one after another, turning into streams of light and disappearing.

"They've run away." Seeing this, only then did Lagos' uptight body relax. He said with hesitation, "Shall we chase them?"

"We can't. This isn't our territory."

Although Roddick was furious, he did not lose his senses. He clenched his teeth and said, "Clean up the battlefield, and calculate the losses."

The losses were very quickly calculated. The aide-de-camp walked to his side, not daring to look into Roddick's eyes, and cautiously reported.

"Sir, we have lost eight percent of the armed guard ships. Twenty-nine percent of the armed guard ships suffered various extents of damage. They're currently being repaired. The logistics fleet has lost thirty-seven percent of its spaceships, fifteen percent of which were captured by the enemy, mainly transport ships…"

Roddick almost fainted.

The logistics fleet had lost more than one third of its spaceships all at once. This ambush had caused seriously heavy losses!

"Unbelievable!" The Three Kings' expressions were as furious as could be. The communication did not hang up throughout, and they had witnessed the entire process of the Expedition Fleet being heavily damaged.

The three of them had high hopes for the Expedition Fleet and Roddick, yet they had suffered such a huge loss so soon after entering the Flickering World. The Three Kings' disappointment and anger at Roddick was clearly expressed in their tones and expressions.

"Sorry, this is a dereliction of duty on my part." Roddick hastily turned around, clenched his teeth, and accepted this as his fault.

As the commander, there was no way Roddick could get away from being blamed for this. It was not like he could blame the enemies for setting up a trap there. No matter what justifiable reasons he had, a huge loss was a huge loss, and not being able to protect the logistic fleet was a fact. If he still tried to reason, it would very easily give the Three Kings an impression of him 'making excuses'. Therefore, no matter how justified this loss was, he could only put up with it and accept the loss.

"We let you lead the Expedition Fleet because we trusted your abilities, but your performance is making us doubt if this was the right decision," one of the Three Kings growled.

Roddick did not dare talk back to his leaders at all; he could only stand there, take the scolding, and promise that he would definitely keep in mind in the future.

After giving Roddick a scolding, the Three Kings of Modo then told him to quickly settle the following issues before ending the call.

Roddick finally stood up. He was about to explode with rage.

He knew that he had left a bad impression on his bosses because of this. If he could not make up for it, his future would undoubtedly be filled with darkness.

The room was filled with a cold atmosphere. Everyone present looked at Roddick while shivering. Roddick was supposed to give the next order to the fleet, but no one dared get on his nerves now.

Lagos coughed, having no choice, and said, "The dynasty only has so many Beyond Grade A Mechanics. Although the enemy used Virtual Intrusion, he did not appear. According to the enemy's Virtual Intrusion speed, I'm guessing it's most likely Black Star."

"You don't have to guess. It's him!" Roddick's tone was cold and filled with rage.

"Sadly, we don't have any evidence. He…"

"So what if we do have evidence‽" Roddick interrupted him and ground his teeth.

Even though they knew that the attackers were almost definitely the Black Star Army, it was no use. The Flickering World was their territory. With the forces he had here, messing with the Black Star Army would basically be suicide.

Earlier, Roddick had tried to board the enemy ships and capture the opponent's crew as evidence, but the attackers kept their distance and did not allow him to do so. To him, even if there was evidence, it would not affect the Black Star Army much if at all. In the Flickering World, the Black Star Army could do almost whatever they wanted!

Although the Modo Civilization was a Super Star Cluster civilization, their base was in the Primeval Star River, which was far from the Shattered Star Ring and the Flickering World. No matter how strong their forces were, there would be nothing they could do to the Black Star Army. Furthermore, they were not universal civilizations, which had a ton of Beyond Grade A allies, so there was nothing they could do to Black Star personally.

So, they knew who the attacker was, but there was nothing they could do. They had no choice but to watch themselves get targeted.

Roddick took a few deep breaths, suddenly turned around, and glared at Lagos. "Contact Garoze. I want to question him personally about why he didn't join the battle!"

He had no choice but to vent his anger on someone. Nonetheless, Garoze was indeed partially responsible for not joining the fight despite being so close. Roddick had no idea what the hell was wrong with Garoze. His rage was reasonable.

Lagos then contacted Garoze again. The call quickly got picked up, and Garoze appeared on the screen.

"Give me a reason!" Roddick yelled furiously.

Garoze frowned and coldly said, "Watch your tone."

When facing Black Star who he could not mess with, his attitude was full of respect. However, when facing Roddick, he immediately found the pride of a Beyond Grade A.

There was just one word to describe him—pragmatic.

"Why did you watch on the side?"

"I'll cancel the job with your boss." Garoze did not explain himself and immediately hung up the communication.

When he accepted the hire, he thought that the mission would just be to deal with the competition with other outside organizations. Never did he expect to have to deal with Black Star. Hence, this job became unprofitable, so he did not want to do it anymore. Even if he would incur some losses due to breaching the contract, it would be better than getting involved in the conflict between the Modo Civilization and the Black Star Army.

Since he was about to cancel the job, of course, he was not going to expose Black Star. It would be idiotic to offend both sides. Since he had chosen to be on one side, he was going to stand by it.

Furthermore, he did not want to admit that he was afraid of Black Star, so he did not want to tell any outsider the reason.

However, this arrogant and superior attitude made Roddick's blood pressure, which had just decreased a little, skyrocket again!

Oh, so you think that my position is not even high enough for you to give me an explanation‽

"*ssholes!"

Roddick was trembling with rage, and his fists were clenched tightly.

"We have lost a lot of devices and resources, so we can only turn to the supplies in the stronghold in the Shattered Star Ring, which will definitely slow us down. This will have way too big an effect on our plan," Lagos said with a frown.

All the organizations were competing. By being behind others from the start, how much potential profit would they lose? Lagos did not dare think too much about it.

It could be said that the Modo Civilization's plan in the Flickering World was completely shattered by this attack!

At this time, the dynasty's patrolling fleet that was responsible for maintaining order finally came. They sent a communication request, and a dynasty officer appeared on the screen.

"We have detected energy reactions of a battle. What happened here?"

Roddick took a deep breath and explained what had happened with a long face.

The dynasty officer nodded. "We understand the situation and will immediately send out men to track the attackers. We will notify you as soon as we find anything."

Then, the dynasty's patrol fleet turned around and scattered in the attacker's direction.

It looked like they were sincere, but Roddick and Lagos both knew that this would certainly not lead to anything at all.

…

At the same time, some of the attackers stopped in a certain area and entered stealth mode. They then gathered the seized logistics spaceships together and started moving the resources in them.

The captured Modo Civilization crew members were all chased into a spaceship with its communication signals cut off, and all their devices were confiscated. These captives looked around at the armored warriors with panic.

This time, an armored warrior stepped forward, took off his helmet, and exposed his childish face. It was Nero.

Seeing him, the crowd immediately made a fuss. Some of them had seen Nero's data before, so they instantly knew that the attackers were from the Black Star Army.

Nero looked around and tried his best to make a serious expression, which only made his childish face more adorable.

"Now, there are two paths ahead of you. First, death. Second, give up your freedom in exchange for your life and work for us forever."

The crowd went silent. At this time, a voice sounded.

"Are you not afraid of us betraying you?"

Nero squinted. "Who's talking?"

A short man walked out and softly said, "I'm the vice logistics manager of this fleet, also the leader of the engineering technical team. I'm a high-level engineer."

Nero's eyes sparkled.

It seems like we captured one of their high-level technical officers.

"You don't have to worry about that. You won't have any chance to come in contact with the outside world. You'll forever become the shadows of the army," Nero said slowly. "Those who are not willing, we won't force you. The hatch is right there; jump into the cosmic space yourself. Make your choice now."

"Looks like we don't have a choice," the vice logistics manager said with resignation.

The people exchanged glances. Without much hesitation, all of them chose the second option.

Very soon, Nero picked out the technical personnel. They were all useful people who would be secretly working for the army to make use of their remaining value.

As for the other crew members, following Han Xiao's orders, they would be sent to the Kunde Race's planet. Whether they became slaves or were torn into pieces by the Kunde Race, it made no difference. One way or another, they were tools for the Kunde Race to vent their anger.

Since these people had taken part in the Modo Civilization's expedition, they were mostly soldiers. Maybe they did not know about the Kunde Race incident, but they were definitely not innocent. Whatever their civilization owed, they would be the ones paying for it. Being soft hearted did not exist in the process of revenge.

…

Han Xiao, who was heading toward Black Star Palace, received Phillip's brief report. He nodded with satisfaction.

"Now it will be even more difficult for the Modo Civilization to develop in the Flickering World."

Han Xiao had ordered a fleet to hide their identity and attack the Modo Civilization's expedition team. As long as they did not leave any conclusive evidence, even if the Modo Civilization knew that he was behind this, he would not be affected.

He did not plan to wipe out Roddick's fleet—he could not completely annihilate the Modo Civilization's hope.

He would only be able to carry out long-term revenge if the Modo Civilization continued to put resources into the Flickering World. If they really decided to give up on the Flickering World, he would have to go to their territory in the Primeval Star River to deal with the Modo Civilization, which would be way too troublesome.

Cutting meat with blunt knives was the most torturous…

According to his memories of his previous life, the competition between external organizations would only become more and more intense. There would be many more incidents where people hid their identities to attack other organizations.

Today, this is me firing the first shot in the Flickering World…

A flash of light sparkled in Han Xiao's eyes.

So, just you wait. This is only the beginning. There's plenty more to come.

Chapter 1013: What a Good Man!

Beep beep!

While Han Xiao had these not so righteous thoughts in his mind, his communicator suddenly rang. It was a call from Tarrokov.

As he picked it up, Brother Tar's old face appeared on the screen full of smiles. Without any formal greeting, he immediately started praising Han Xiao.

"Black Star, amazingly done. I love it when you're this decisive."

The external organizations were not sure who was really behind the organization that attacked the Modo Civilization. The dynasty, however, of course knew it was the Black Star Army.

"So, you don't love me otherwise?" Han Xiao looked calm but chuckled in his mind. "Don't forget to keep your promise and give me the resources we agreed on."

Taking revenge on the Modo Civilization was also the dynasty's request. The dynasty planned to make an example out of them.

Since the dynasty doing things themselves was not suitable, they borrowed Han Xiao's forces. Of course, they were not going to let the Black Star Army work for free and had signed a contract long ago. The Black Star Army would be responsible for educating the Modo Civilization with violence, and the Crimson Dynasty would compensate them with resources.

To the dynasty, they were hiring allies to strike enemies. To Han Xiao, he was taking the dynasty's money to do his own missions while also earning some favors, which really was pretty nice.

"Don't worry, we've never not kept our promise." Tarrokov smiled before asking, "What do you plan to do with those captives of the Modo Civilization?"

"I'll keep some of them in the army as secret manpower, and the rest will be thrown to the Kunde Race."

Old Tar nodded and reminded Han Xiao, "No matter what, make sure to take away all of their means of contacting the outside world."

"The chances of them breaking through the measures I put in place to block their communication is infinitely close to zero. You don't have to worry about that."

"You're right. You're a Virtual Mechanic after all. I'm overthinking it." Old Tar chuckled. "Actually, that was pretty much the only reason I called, just to remind you… Anyway, please go harder on the Modo Civilization. I shall hang up now."

He then ended the communication. Han Xiao tutted in his head.

To disturb him for something this trivial, it was most likely a form of hinting, saying that the dynasty knew the movements of the Black Star Army. This was basically to tell him not to mess with anyone other than the Modo Civilization. The Meeting of the Gods might also have been a factor that affected this.

"Tsk, making me read between the lines again."

Han Xiao put the communicator away and placed this matter at the back of his mind.

All the players were heading toward the Flickering World. The Shattered Star Ring was the closest Star Field, so it would not take long for the army players to arrive at the Flickering World.

As the version had just started, the players would need some time to get used to it before things got on track.

In his previous life, the players fought their own factions. Other than some famous national war incidents, the usual reasons behind fights were mission conflicts and resources. In an environment like this, the solo players' lives became tougher and tougher. Gathering in groups became a trend, and more and more players started to create guilds.

According to the official statistics, the number of player guilds increased exponentially during Version 4.0. The more time passed, the more guilds there were. There was one famous event that caused the number of guilds to increase explosively in a short term. With a few large American professional guilds in the lead such as the Devil club, they formed a formal organization that became recognized by the outside world. They then obtained an extremely rare opportunity that other players had been trying to obtain for a very long time, which led to them being officially recognized.

After that, guilds became even more important to the players. They started to gather in large groups, and guilds started to form alliances and official organizations recognized by the outside world. They then formed partnerships with other organizations in the universe through business and diplomatic means using their organization.

With that, the benefits of guilds were extremely clear, as they would be able to obtain plenty more resources compared to ordinary players.

This function had existed in the previous few versions too, but it only showed its true potential in Version 4.0, leading to a turning point in the players' careers. The main reason was the increase in the players' strength in Version 4.0. Their influence throughout the universe was on a completely different level, which was why the organizations they built were taken seriously.

"Now, because the faction benefits that I'm giving to the army players are too useful, the players of the other Star Fields might work together to suppress the army players' advantages. When everyone gets used to the new version, the army players are bound to suffer some losses. After all, there are too many who are against us."

Since the army players had the advantage, he did not mind pushing it further so that the army players would always be in the lead.

Initially, all the players would have to take some time to get used to the version before entering the stage of forming guilds and organizations on a large scale, so Han Xiao wanted to let the army players enter that stage in advance.

This needed some adjustments in the system that would encourage this behavior.

Han Xiao thought about it for a while before summoning Phillip. He thought of a new system that would only be targeted at the players, which meant the Immortals.

_____________________

Those who are promoted to high positions through making contributions, or farming Contribution Points, and have reached Grade B or above will be allowed to create a new type of combat team. The team shall consist of two or more members with no upper limit of number of members. The division name can be chosen freely. After forming such a team, they can report it in the army. Every month, according to the missions completed and total Contribution Points obtained by all the members, they will receive special Team Merit Points.

Team Merit Points can be used to purchase large amounts of resources, including equipment, knowledges, and abilities. They will also have a crucial use—to purchase the positions to manage the various businesses of the army on behalf of the army, as well as to bid for certain special projects, or exchange for the mining right of some resource rich planets.

Not only that, but with enough merit points, they can choose to become a subsidiary organization under the Black Star Army and be considered semi-independent. For those teams, the merit points can be used to request the army's reinforcements, use the army's name to execute legal strategic actions, or submit a request to have both sides work together for a certain matter. They will basically be semi-independent organizations that are partners of the Black Star Army.

_____________________

"This should be about it…"

Han Xiao then looked through the main structure of the new system a few times and nodded.

This system would 'legalize' the players' guilds.

Originally, guilds only existed between the players and were not recognized by the galactic society. For example, the NPC had no idea the Temple of Gods Guild existed, nor did they know who the members were. This system would make the players' guilds be recognized in the army's systems, so they would become official organizations with proper documentation.

This way, the players' guilds would become organizations that actually existed in the universe.

The use of the Team Merit Points would encourage the army players to create guilds without needing to get used to the version. There would no doubt be many who tried this out, especially those official guilds of large clubs.

During Version 4.0 in his previous life, there were always players who left NPC factions to create their own. With this new system, however, it would at the very least tremendously reduce the players' need to do so.

The price, of course, was that with the independence granted to the player guilds, the army would suffer a certain amount of unrest. Nevertheless, at times like this, giving the players more freedom was the path that had to be taken.

With more strength, the way to treat them had to be improved too. Han Xiao was no evil boss; he gave the players enough benefits even though he would also gain every benefit he could from them.

Version 4.0 was the turning point for the players. From here onward, the players would truly be difficult to control. They would start to spread the seed of anarchism everywhere. There was no way he could control the players as much as he did in the previous versions.

He planned to change that long ago, to give the players opportunities to grow their guilds and provide more resources to them. Only then would he be able to make the players continue to work for him willingly despite their growing strength.

At the same time, this system would also attract foreign players.

It was killing two birds with one stone.

"Master, hum… Are you sure about implementing this new system?"

Phillip, who was like a little fairy, sat on Han Xiao's collarbone with his big eyes sparkling and looking up at Han Xiao's cheek. His two tiny legs waved left and right in midair.

"Announce the preview first." Han Xiao planned to officially implement this system only after all the players arrived at the Flickering World.

Before that, he wanted to let the players have time to prepare and gather their friends.

"Okay, hum…"

Han Xiao paused, suddenly thought of something, and said, "Some time ago, I studied Risda's logic structure and had some new ideas. I'll give you some updates in a few days' time to increase your speed."

Hearing this, Phillip's eyes sparkled, and he flew up to Han Xiao's face, hugging onto Han Xiao's nose and staring into his eyes.

"Phillips loves my master the most, hum!"

"Stop acting cute." Han Xiao raised his brow and flicked Phillip away from his nose.

…

The news about the Modo Civilization's significant loss spread in the Flickering World. Many organizations talked about this privately. The other Super Star Cluster civilizations heard about this too.

Many Super Star Cluster civilizations had a meeting immediately.

"The dynasty is most likely the one who attacked Modo. We didn't expect the two of them to start fighting this soon."

"Could this be the first step of the dynasty's plan to target us Super Star Cluster civilizations?"

"Doesn't look like it. It seems to be a private matter between the dynasty and Modo."

"Hmm, after we pass the areas of the first and second phase, we should help Modo when we can. We can't let the dynasty beat them up too badly."

As they knew the three Universal Civilizations would not let them comfortably develop in the Flickering World, most of the Super Star Cluster civilization had already formed secret alliances to fight against the three Universal Civilizations' hostility together.

As Modo was attacked, according to their alliance terms, the other Super Star Cluster civilizations all decided to provide help when suitable.

Although this did not seem to have anything to do with them, the Super Star Cluster alliance did not want to give the dynasty the chance to break them one by one. Although the Modo Civilization was their competitor, fighting against the three Universal Civilizations' pressure was the top task in the eyes of the Super Star Cluster alliance. Therefore, they did not mind helping their competitor. Only then would they be able to break through the three Universal Civilizations' control of the new Star Field.

…

With assistance from the army and the dynasty, no witness discovered the attackers. After some days, the Black Star fleet that had attacked the Modo Civilization finally rendezvoused and returned to the Garu Star Cluster through a secret route. The selected captives were then sent to the Kunde Race's planet in the Odoran Star System.

With help from the Black Star Army, every colonial planet now had plenty of cities. They were not short of resources.

The Kunde Race had been peacefully resting for more than a decade. Although they had yet to recover from the wounds of the war, many chose to enjoy the peace and new life.

In the past, the communication from all these colonial planets toward the outside world was blocked. The residents of the planets could only log into their planet server network. Therefore, they had absolutely no idea what was happening in the outside world. It was like they were stranded on an island in the universe.

The army and the dynasty had control of all the media channels and did not allow the existence of civilian media corporations. The Kunde Race members could only accept the cultural transformation from the dynasty in the form of literature, music, and entertainment. The various entertainment sources would slowly change their ways of thinking.

Living so peacefully and not having any chance to resist, they could do absolutely nothing even if they were furious. Many people could only accept their fate with resignation.

Today, however, the official channel that had been playing cultural transformation shows every day suddenly announced a piece of news that made countless Kunde Race members thrilled.

His Excellency Black Star kept his promise back then to avenge the Kunde Race, and he had now captured the captives of some of the people behind their tragedy. These people would be sent to the Kunde Race colonial planets very soon.

This piece of news immediately caused a sensation!

The Kunde Race of this generation could not resist, but they did not forget their hatred. Compared to the dynasty, they hated the people who used the Kunde Race back then even more.

As the date approached, countless members of the Kunde Race arrived early at the designated dock and looked up at the sky, waiting for the arrival of these captives.

Whoosh!

More and more spaceships penetrated the atmosphere and quickly landed on the dock.

As the hatches opened one after another, batches of Black Star Army warriors escorted the unarmed captives out.

The captives that were sent there were all filtered, so no strong soldiers were present. They all wore the same prison uniform, and all their possessions were confiscated. They carried no threat at all.

The Kunde Race around them were innumerable. As the many captives saw so many ferocious looking creatures surrounding them, they became uncontrollably nervous, and their bodies started to stiffen.

"What planet is this? Why were we sent here?"

"What are these creatures? Beasts?"

"They're wearing clothes. They're intelligent."

"Why are they all staring at us? It's a little horrifying."

Using the Kunde Race was a secret only the upper echelons knew, of course, these normal soldiers had no idea. Many did not even recognize this species at all. They were lost and had no idea why these intelligent beings were staring at them.

At this time, a stone suddenly flew out from the crowd and landed on a captive's head.

Pa!

This captive grunted and quickly covered his head.

Before his other friends could respond, countless objects flew out from the crowd and were thrown at all these captives.

Whining and wailing sounded immediately. The captives were bleeding everywhere. The Black Star Army warriors watched coldly from the side. After they had been attacked for quite some time, they finally activated their shields to block all the flying objects. The floor was quickly covered in random objects.

Although no lives were lost, the captives were still frightened.

"Why are they hitting us‽"

"Why did the Black Star Army send us here?"

They were making a fuss. As they looked around with terror, they finally understood the look in the members of the Kunde Race's eyes around them—they were filled with hatred and rage.

At this time, an army warrior snorted and coldly said, "They're the Kunde Race, a native civilization of the Flickering World. During the second exploration phase, the Modo Civilization secretly used the Kunde Race and provoked them to fight the dynasty, causing the Kunde Race to be eliminated. All of you are their enemy. Stay here and pay for your sins."

After hearing this, the captives went silent with their eyes widened.

Sending us to the territory of the people who hate us… You're using us for them to vent their anger!

We were promised to live, but this is worse than dying!

W-we're done for!

The captives were filled with negative emotions. They did not dare look up as they were pushed forward onto the land transports toward the prisons.

The land transport slowly departed from the dock. From start to end, the Kunde Race around had always been staring at the captives.

The crowd did not dissipate. After some time, someone finally spoke.

"Black Star promised to bring us justice back then. It's actually true…"

"Black Star has been keeping his promise."

"I misunderstood him. Turns out he's someone so noble."

Many Kunde Race felt the same way.

In the past decade or so, the Black Star Army had managed the planet and provided them with countless resources. Together with the promotion in the media, the Kunde Race was already quite familiar with the army.

In terms of emotions, the Kunde Race did not have much hatred for the Black Star Army, but not many of them believed Han Xiao's promise back then.

After all, the Kunde Race was just a group of 'prisoners' who could not fight back; why should Black Star waste his energy to bring them justice? After more than ten years, they thought that he had already forgotten this.

However, Han Xiao had proved to them that he was not joking with results.

In the eyes of the Kunde Race, Black Star immediately became the only hope to bring justice for their race.

While shocked and surprised, a sense of appreciation grew in the hearts of the Kunde Race, together with more hope.

Black Star, what a good man!

Chapter 1014: Picking Up the Old Profession

The stargate tunnel built by the Black Star Army was the top choice for countless external organizations. It had become the most popular and most convenient route. There were countless spaceships passing by every second.

One reason was that the Black Star Army's territory was huge, including border Star Systems at two different directions with direct stargates, so it would save a lot of time.

Another was that Han Xiao's edge of knowing the star map well was taking effect. Within the territories he had chosen, there were a ton of transport hubs and strategic points, which had been the most prosperous locations in his previous life. Now, they had the same importance as in his previous life. These financial groups who invested in the Black Star Army were also starting to get their returns. Han Xiao promised to give some of the businesses in his territory to these investors to manage; now, there were countless financial groups operating in the army's territory, quickly filling up the businesses.

More than half of the outside organizations chose to take the Black Star Army's route. Han Xiao, of course, would not provide free services. A huge number of spaceships were entering the Garu Star Cluster every single day, and the profit from that was exploding.

Countless streams of light escaped from the entrance stargate, turning into blurry silver rainbows that lingered in space.

This time, spaceships with the Black Star symbol flew out from the stargate one after another, following the crowd and slowly moving forward.

"So, this is the entrance of the Black Star Army's territory."

There were plenty of army players on every one of these ships. They were all squeezing in front of the porthole and looking outside with curiosity.

When Planet Black Gate entered their sights, compared to the deserted image the players had of it, the Planet Black Gate now could not be more boisterous. Countless spaceships landed on and took off from it, so the traffic flow was very dense. The surface of the planet was filled with buildings. The countless lights shrouded the planet like a curtain made of jewels.

On its side, a silver stream of light extended in the cosmic space all the way to the end of their sights. This was made up of the flame trail of the countless spaceships entering the border. These spaceships passed through in hyperdrive like meteors, and as it was too frequent, these trails did not dissipate for a very long time. It was like someone used a silver pen to draw a line that could not be erased along the entire stargate route. It had almost become the guide for the route.

"Planet Black Gate, belongs to the Black Star Army, a large border entrance transit station landmark of the Garu Star Cluster." Maple Moon read the data shown on the communicator.

"It's so boisterous. It's completely the opposite of how it was last version," Frenzied Sword commented.

He could only feel how dreamy the change was after arriving at the army's territory.

Frenzied Sword was the earliest player to follow Black Star. He experienced every single step of Black Star's rise. It was hard for him to imagine how his own faction really grew to this point and have such vast territories.

Just the size of the territories was equivalent to ten Star System civilizations, which could even match up with some Star Cluster civilizations. It was stunning.

In his eyes, Black Star became even more dependable.

While he was still deep in thought, Maple Moon said, "The Flickering World is the world server, we've arrived earlier than the players of the other Star Fields, so this time advantage is very crucial. Do you have any plans?"

"Don't worry, the guild will be going to the army to register as a subsidiary organization. We will then follow the guild to do things. We should be going to the fourth exploration phase's area to grab the opportunities before others," Frenzied Sword said.

"I didn't expect the army to announce such a revolutionary system. This is almost as if he's letting the guilds split from the army. This will completely change the way we play the game… Of course, it's a good thing for us, but from Black Star's perspective, I have no idea what he's thinking. Why is he willing to give up power?" Maple Moon mumbled. Even though it had already been a few days, she was still surprised.

"This means my speculation in the past was correct, of course. As the Grade of us players increases, the influence we have on the universe will increase too. Seems like this version will be the turning point of that." Frenzied Sword had a smug look on his face.

Originally, many players were lost about how to make full use of their advantages in the Flickering World. However, the new system Han Xiao announced not long ago immediately showed all the army players a clear path.

The Team Merit Point system was almost specially made to aid in the growth of guilds. Almost every known Chinese guild decided to register as an official organization in the army. At the same time, this had also created a trend of creating guilds. Just during the time they travelled there, countless army players had already called up their friends to create guilds. Han Xiao's plan was proven to be very effective.

The fleet flew for some days before arriving at the Black Star Palace. This was the first time the players had seen this new main base built during the version update. Its magnificence amazed many players.

This group of players who arrived first came to the most outside base and gathered in a hall. Phillip had summoned them here to have them be inspected.

After just a short wait, two people walked in. The players all looked over and were excited to see who they were.

It was the Army Commander, Han Xiao, and the second Beyond Grade A of the army, Hila.

"Wow, Hila has become even more beautiful."

"The face! The body! The aura! Please let me die here!"

"Save the nonsense, it's no use."

"Ah, how I miss the feeling of being killed by Hila. Maybe this is what love is."

"No, this is being a pervert."

"Woman? Boring, strong men like Black Star can make you hard to breathe."

A big group of players rushed toward them with their desire to farm favorability written all over their faces. Hila was surrounded by even more people than Han Xiao.

Han Xiao complained about sexism in his mind. Before Hila started to slaughter everyone out of impatience, he repelled everyone away, saying with a deep voice, "Silence. I have serious matters to announce."

The players gradually quieted down and looked at Han Xiao with curiosity in their eyes.

Han Xiao cleared his throat and slowly said, "Currently, the Flickering World is open to the outside world. With the outside forces entering, the exploration of the new Star Field has entered a new stage. The peace that once existed is no more. In the future, countless conflicts will erupt surrounding the resources in the new Star Field. And we, the Black Star Army, have to adapt to this change.

"I believe everyone already knows that the army announced a new system recently. This is the first step of the change. You're all from my home planet and my comrades who grew alongside the army. The term 'Immortals' has a very important meaning to the army. You've all made a lot of contributions. Therefore, I've decided to give you more independence, and I hope you can make full use of your talents to achieve great things."

As soon as his sentence ended, shock appeared on many players as they exchanged looks. They were very surprised.

This seemed to be the first time Black Star had called them Immortals.

Before this, although they were working for the Black Star Army, they did not feel like they were very important. Although the outside world called them Immortals, their Army Commander did not seem to have said anything about this in any public occasions and had always been treating them like the normal members.

In Version 1.0, the Germinal Organization had studied the players, and similar situations still existed. All the players knew the fact that they were immortal might pique the NPCs' interest, but to most people, this was just a way to improve the sense of realism. They did not pay too much attention to it.

Now, however, having suddenly heard what Black Star said, the players present all had a strange feeling as if something they had ignored for a very long time had resurfaced again—the fact that they were really special. In their eyes, Han Xiao's image became more alive.

Other than this strange feeling, the players were also glad to hear their faction leader Black Star personally saying they were important to the army. Many people were very motivated and felt a subtle sense of achievement and belonging.

Han Xiao looked around and saw the expression on everyone's faces. He suddenly smiled and said, "You don't have to be shocked. Although both Hila and I are Beyond Grade As now, you're all my people from the same mother planet. In this cold universe, we're on the same side. Therefore, you don't have to be too cautious in front of me. I have high hopes for you. Remember, the Black Star Army will always have your back."

Everyone was thrilled to hear this.

From the same mother planet… that's right, how could we forget that? We and Black Star have this bond!

Seeing Han Xiao's attitude, everyone felt that Han Xiao had become more friendly.

Inside the crowd, Maple Moon quietly poked Frenzied Sword's waist and softly said, "Why do I feel like Black Star seems to have changed?"

"Changed? Haha, you're wrong. He's not changed at all!" Frenzied Sword was filled with excitement. "This is the Han Xiao in my mind, not that cold and beyond-reach important Black Star!"

His voice was so loud that many professional players around looked over.

"He's right. How long has it been since Black Star has had close contact with us?" Second Prince murmured.

"With Black Star becoming stronger and stronger, it has been very difficult for the others to come in touch with him. To think that he's still as friendly and down to earth as he was in Version 1.0. Looks like he really sees us as one of his own." Sleepy Winter smiled.

Many people were discussing this quietly, while Bun-Hit-Dog focused on recording this moment with joy on his face.

Han Xiao very discreetly glanced at him shortly and nodded in his mind.

In the previous versions, with the rapid increase in his position, the opportunities for the players to come in contact with him had constantly decreased. After two versions, his image had already become cold and beyond reach.

However, in Version 4.0, as the players would become much more useful, Han Xiao decided to be more down to earth and close the distance between him and the players. This would strengthen the players' emotional attachment to him, which was a key factor in influencing the players other than profit.

After all, he was a player himself in his previous life. How could he not know what the players liked?

Seeing the players were filled with joy, Han Xiao coughed and spoke again, finally getting to the point.

"The competition in the Flickering World has become very intense. I will be deploying some fleets toward the fourth exploration phase's area to compete with the external forces. You can choose to participate. As long as any member of a registered subsidiary organization participates, the organization will receive more Team Merit Points depending on the number of members participating and will be allowed to build strongholds on the planets in the army's territory. At the same time, they will all enjoy a thirty-percent discount in the military supplies store for all items."

As soon as he stopped speaking, a faction mission popped up on the interfaces of the players. Many players' eyes instantly brightened.

Not only would there be a massive scale faction main storyline mission but also thirty percent off in the faction store. They would even be allowed to build official guild strongholds in the army's territory…

Black Star really is the same old Black Star—a walking bag of profit!

Seeing that everyone was excited, Han Xiao called an end to the meeting. The players scattered almost immediately and headed right to the military supplies store to shop. They still had the money they saved from the last version, most players had a lot to spend, their purchasing power was ample.

The thirty percent off was a promotion method to encourage the players to spend. Although the players were focusing on leveling up, with such a big discount, they would definitely be influenced. This was to harvest the players' experience.

Han Xiao had stockpiled Mission Completion Cards for twenty years. He was now LV 307, so he would be able to go through his Promotion as long as he reached LV 320.

The few Star Clusters in the fourth exploration phase would be where the competition would be the most intense, as well as the main stage of the conflict in the World Server between the players. This move also served to encourage the players to secure their advantages before going to the fourth exploration phase area, helping the army players keep their lead so as to avoid them being bullied by the foreign players working together.

Allowing these guilds that had registered as official organizations to build guild strongholds was also a profit bundle.

With their homes in my territory, the cost of them leaving my faction will be even higher.

All ploys and tricks, I'm such a bad man…

Han Xiao shook his head and chuckled.

He led Hila out of the hall, and the two of them walked in the army while chatting. This time, Hila suddenly said, "Black Star, I plan to go to the fourth exploration phase area too, to take part in the army's exploration in the front line."

"Are your hands getting itchy?" Han Xiao glanced at her.

"Hmm. I'm not you. You can remote control your avatar while being at home. I want to fight with more Beyond Grade As, and now is a good opportunity." Hila nodded.

After reaching Beyond Grade A, her motivation did not disappear at all. Knowing that the difference between herself and Han Xiao was still vast, she wanted to become stronger.

Shattered Star Ring was not suitable for sparring. Now that they had reached the Flickering World, it was a good opportunity to improve herself.

"Alright, you shall take the position as the commander of the fleet. Just a reminder, dozens of Beyond Grade As will be fighting in the fourth phase areas. For a very long time in the future, that will probably be the most dangerous place in the entire universe. If you meet anyone you can't deal with, tell me. My avatar will be following the fleet at all times," Han Xiao said.

All these Beyond Grade As were not there to sightsee; they were all there to fight for the profits in the new Star Field. Without Han Xiao's restraint in the Flickering World, these people would have fought all the time. Not just Hila, Han Xiao planned to let his avatar be stationed there for a long term as well.

After splitting up with Hila, Han Xiao walked to his room and opened the player forums, browsing the movements of the players in the various Star Fields and enjoying the nonsense of the idiotic comments and posts.

While he browsed the posts and relaxed, a new post was suddenly pinned.

Han Xiao looked at it and his eyes sparkled. It was the first episode of Galaxy Times since the new version!

"After more than half a month, it's finally here, huh?"

Chapter 1015: The Great Mechanic Han's Control from Behind the Curtain

Han Xiao clicked into the post, and as soon as he opened the video, the two new hosts appeared on the screen, still one male and one female.

"Players and friends, good evening, I'm Ah Wei," the male host said.

"I'm Flower," the female host said.

"This is the Galaxy Times, dedicated to sharing first-hand gaming news. Your gaming career is our top priority."

After the usual opening, the two hosts started the show with the usual awkward conversation.

"It has been more than half a month since the start of the new version. The players of the various nations are all trying to adapt to it. Compared to Version 3.0, 4.0 comes with a lot of changes. Just a preview, the content we have today is very rich. We're going to tell everyone about the way to play this new version."

"Speaking of the new version, that reminds me of something. I have a friend…"

Before he finished, Flower interrupted him and said, "I got it. That friend is you. Please carry on with your performance."

"… That friend of mine had a ghost-related incident happen to him recently."

"Where did it happen?"

Ah Wei replied, "On this one day, when my friend returned from working overtime, it was already late night. His family was sound asleep. He washed up then went straight to bed hugging his wife to sleep. Then, at midnight, he suddenly heard footsteps outside the door, and he…"

Flower suddenly interrupted again and said with a strange expression, "Wait… what does this have to do with the new version again?"

"Ahem, I was just looking for an excuse to start the topic. Don't mind these details."

"… Go on." Flower rolled her eyes.

"I… My friend and his wife were the only ones in that house, so he thought a thief had broken in. He quickly got out of the bed to turn on the light, only to realize that there was no one else, and the gate was properly closed. So, he went back to sleep. However, when he woke up the next day and went to work, he realized that the gate was open slightly, but nothing was missing from his house. He thought that he had only dreamed about the previous night, so he woke up his wife to ask her if she had heard anything last night, to which she replied no. Don't you think that's scary? It's definitely a ghost."

"Eat more greens and vegetables in the future; it improves mental stability," Flower replied.

"So, what would you do if you really encountered a ghost?"

"I'd beat it to death, of course. Do you think my materialism aura is fake?"

After this interaction, the two hosts successfully pulled the players' excited mood back to regular standards, all turning from thrilled to poker faces.

As Han Xiao listened through the awkward conversation stage, the two hosts finally entered the main theme.

"Back to business. It has been more than a half month since the start of Version 4.0 [Flickering World], and the uniqueness of this version is already showing… that's right, it's the world server!" Ah Wei said.

"Yes, after three versions, the players from all nations can now finally gather in one place and interest in the same Star Field," Flower continued. "This is a major play style revolution. We can see that this version will be exceptionally boisterous. There's the possibility of national wars happening, so it will be a giant battleground for the players from all nations."

"Speaking of what might happen, I recall the speculation we made in the last episode of Version 3.0. Back then, we speculated that Version 3.0 would fully open the function of cross Star Field traveling. Now, our speculation has proven to be half correct, only that we did not guess the opening of the world server."

"Due to the appearance of the world server, the Shattered Star Ring players now have two natural advantages. One is their geographical location, as these two Star Fields are next to each other, which means the Shattered Star Ring players can arrive in the world server earlier than the players from the other Star Fields. Another is that the Shattered Star Ring players have exclusive faction advantages."

"That's right. Among the factions that the players are able to join, The Black Star Army is the only one that made contact with the Flickering World in the previous version. The players followed the army to participate in the first exploration phase of the Flickering World and built their foundations."

"Not only that, the Black Star Army has already become the strongest force in the Flickering World in this new version, apart from the dynasty. I can still remember the Black Star Army being the guiding faction for the Shattered Star Ring players in Version 2.0. Now that they have grown to become such an enormous organization, they will provide tremendous help to the Shattered Star Ring players in the Flickering World, giving them exclusive advantages."

"Nonetheless, I feel that there are two sides to everything. The Shattered Star Ring players who have such clear advantages might become the joint target of the players from all the other Star Fields."

"As for the play style of the world server, there have been many posts analyzing it across various boards. According to our conclusion, the competition in Version 4.0 might revolve around guilds. The players without guilds will have more freedom and more choices, but the efficiency in obtaining resources will not be comparable to guilds."

"The source of this is the system the Black Star Army recently announced…" Ah Wei suddenly paused, hesitated, and said, "Speaking of which, how many times have we made version speculations based on the Black Star Army's actions?"

As soon as this was said, the players who were watching the show started a rampage. Countless comments flew across the screen.

"Too true. Everything starts with the Black Star Army. Without the army, the Galaxy Times wouldn't even know how to do their shows."

"Ah Wei: Making speculations is easy, just see what the Black Star Army is doing."

"Trash show. Completely reliant on the army :)"

"Black Star: That's right, I'm the most handsome man in the Shattered Star Ring."

As the viewers started to joke around again, Han Xiao smiled.

This compliment feels quite good. The benefits I've provided all along to guide the versions didn't go to waste.

Flower coughed and said, "Alright, back to the main topic. The Black Star Army is indeed an important factor when it comes to predicting version development. The core mechanism of the new system they announced some time ago turns guilds into official organizations in the universe and allows the players to become somewhat independent."

"The independent playstyle has always been unpopular in the previous versions, mainly because the conditions had yet to mature. However, in Version 4.0, with the increased maximum level, the influence the players can have as independent organizations has increased. This playstyle might become very important."

"The Black Star Army has led this playstyle, and according to what they have done in the past, this will very likely become the mainstream play style of Version 4.0, encouraging more people to create guilds."

"However! Attention to all players! Becoming independent through normal processes will require you to leave your original faction. As of this moment, the Black Star Army is the only faction that has a system of semi-independence. This means that only the army players can be independent while still getting to keep their identities as members of the Black Star Army! This is another unique and exclusive advantage!"

"We still don't know if this is one of the specialties of the Black Star Army. If the factions that the players in the other Star Fields are in don't have this system, I feel that many foreign players will join the Black Star Army… Therefore, here comes the problem. If they become players in the same faction, will national wars still happen?"

Quite accurate analytics, Han Xiao thought.

This was a good thing for him. It would help to promote how superior his system was so that the players would better understand how amazing the army was, increasing the appeal of the faction.

The show went on to analyze the possibilities of the world server in detail, as well as what was happening to the players in the various Star Fields. Han Xiao watched from start to end, mainly to see the movements of the players of the other Star Fields.

Unlike the Shattered Star Ring, the players in the other Star Fields did not have a unified faction. They belonged to many different factions and were on their way to the Flickering World with their factions. There were also many solo players who quit their factions, mainly Americans and Europeans. After all, the love for freedom was in their blood and bones.

The exterior factions that had players were worth paying attention to, but they were mostly small organizations.

Small organizations were nothing to worry about. The Flickering World had way too many powerful organizations. The methods of joining them in Version 4.0 would increase drastically. The players would not be able to resist the temptation to join bigger organizations.

Furthermore, some might even sell out their old boss in exchange for Contribution Points from the new boss.

Han Xiao could recall many examples where players deliberately used small organizations' names to mess with enormous organizations. They would then betray the small organization while bringing the small organization an undefeatable powerful enemy, which led to their doom. Afterward, the players would then join the new hostile faction with a higher position and salary, and this was the definition of completely shameless anarchism.

To many players, virtue was complete horse sh*t. Small organizations were unattractive and weak, so players would not miss them or be attached at all. A large faction like his, however, would mostly be treasured by normal players, and they would not cause such trouble.

Other than medium and small organizations, there were also foreign players who worked for powerful organizations such as the Limitless Financial Group, Galactic Black Market, Extinguish Army, and some Star Cluster or even Super Star Cluster civilizations. Depending on the location, they had differing numbers of 'Immortals' from different nations working for them.

"Especially that piece of sh*t Sorokin. He recruited quite a number of players and even tested the army players in the past. He might poach my people in the Flickering World." Han Xiao curled his lips.

The Limitless Financial Group was mainly recruiting in the Sea of Star Spirits, which mostly included Japanese and Korean players. The Extinguish Army was a key faction for the Americans. The players under these organizations should be the highest in numbers other than the Black Star Army.

Speaking of the Extinguish Army, Han Xiao was reminded of Beyoni. Beyoni was the leader of the Pyre Demon Tribe, while the Extinguish Army consisted mainly of the Ice Demon Race, so the two of them were considered enemies. Beyoni controlled the Land of the Fire Core, while the Extinguish Army controlled the Land of the Ice Core. Even their race treasures were similar.

While thinking about that, Han Xiao suddenly felt something and opened up his attribute interface. His EXP gauge was increasing at an astonishing speed.

"Hehe, my promotion is working."

…

The top tier professional clubs such as Dynasty, Temple of God, Long Sky, and so on had all registered as official organizations in the Black Star Army. Their organization names remained unchanged and could be used as their guild name.

Having been ordered to do so by Han Xiao, Phillip quickly processed the procedures of guilds becoming official one after another. The organizational structure of the army players changed drastically as they officially became recognized subsidiary guild organizations and had documents in the army.

After the registration, these guilds immediately told some of their members to take part in the main storyline exploration mission so that they could receive the many discounts Han Xiao had mentioned. To these large guilds, they could also use these discounts to attract many players who did not have a guild yet to join them. It was a win-win.

Through the hard work of the logistics department in the past twenty years, the various models of equipment in the army were all the latest, while the items the players had were all abandoned models from twenty years ago. They needed to upgrade. Plus, with the thirty-percent discount, their desire to spend was at the peak. A shopping spree started in the military supplies store very soon.

To the Great Mechanic Han, the Enas earned from the players now was just small profits. What was important was EXP. He had added EXP price to more items in the faction store and introduced a new system. The players could choose one of two purchasing methods—Enas or EXP. If they had no money in their pockets, they could use EXP to buy things.

In the eyes of other army members, this would look a little strange, as if equipment were given out for free. However, Han Xiao did not have to be as careful about the way he treated the players as he was before, given how strong he had become. All he had to do was say that the Immortals had privileges, and no one would ask any more questions.

The result of that was the explosive increase in the efficiency of harvesting EXP. EXP was a special type of currency only belonging to the players. Currently, only the Black Star Army had the service of using EXP to buy things; the other factions would not be able to do it even if they wanted to.

Millions of army players arrived at Black Star Palace over several days, while the players from the other Star Fields were still on their way. According to the schedule of these players, the players that would reach the world server the second-fastest should be the Southeast Asian players in Blackhole Edge, mainly Thais, Vietnamese, Indonesians, and Singaporeans. However, that was still many days away. The Chinese players had more than enough time to exploit their advantages.

As deployed by the Black Star Army, many players were split into mostly two directions. One group followed the fleet led by Hila toward the area of the fourth exploration phase, ready to interfere with the competition between the outside forces. The remaining players were mainly guild members who made use of the benefit Han Xiao promised and went to build guild strongholds in various locations of the army's territory. At the same time, they used Team Merit Points to purchase resource points and the operation rights for various businesses, starting to build stronger foundations for their guilds.

With Han Xiao's control behind the curtain, all the army players had moved. This was developing according to the path he had pointed out. The mainstream play style proven by what happened in his previous life was expanding his lead in the world server step by step.

At the same time, the fleet led by Hila arrived at the area of the fourth exploration phase together with other organizations.

Chapter 1016: Gorutan's Provocation

The exploration area for the fourth exploration phase was four Star Clusters. They were considered as the center of the Flickering World in terms of geographical location.

Opening the new Star Field to the outside world was the dynasty's way of splitting the cost of construction. The third phase areas were basically properly split and highly controlled, so they were considered areas with high security. These four Star Clusters, however, were areas for all the forces to compete freely. The dynasty did not restrict the outside organizations from fighting for territory, so they were low security areas.

The external organizations would choose one or more Star Clusters to explore while at the same time fighting for their territories. At the initial stage of the exploration, these organizations focused on occupying their territories first before slowly exploring the further unknown areas.

It had not been long since the countless outside organizations had arrived there, so the exploration area was still limited to the edges of the four Star Clusters. However, the situation was already looking complex and chaotic. If there was a star map that marked the territories the various organizations now occupied in detail, that would be the most complicated star map in the entire universe.

Most organizations had already foreseen the intensity of the competition and formed various alliances here and there. Roughly speaking, the main factions that were active in the free competition zones could be classified into the following categories.

The first category comprised the 'local snakes', consisting of the dynasty and its allies. They all had some territory at the edge of these four Star Clusters, so their position was quite above the others. After all, most of the outside organizations did not want to fight with them, and the organizations belonging to the dynasty did not put too much effort into exploring as well, so they did not participate in the intense competition.

The second groups had alliances of different civilizations, among which, the Super Star Cluster alliance stood at the top. The rest were the Star Cluster civilization alliances of various Star Fields. They had been expanding ruthlessly and occupied plenty of areas that were close to each other. These alliances were strong contenders in this free competition zone.

The third category covered the financial groups, who mostly had mercenaries under their command, mainly focused on making money. The territories they occupied were quite scattered. The fourth group included the external Beyond Grade A organizations, which were also very strong contenders, but there were not many of them.

The last was the civil organizations from all over the universe. This group had the most complex composition and the most scattered territories with the most conflicts that often changed ownership in the previous life.

As for the federation and the church, they were both keeping a low profile in their corners and did not seem to intend to expand. They were only letting their allies take part in the competition freely.

The three Universal Civilizations had the silent agreement of giving the stage to let the other organizations fight and compete.

Currently, although there were occasional conflicts in the free competition zones of the four Star Cluster, there had yet to be any large scale armed conflicts. The exploration had only just started, so there were still plenty of unknown areas. Everyone was exploring further from the edges of the Star Cluster; the organization structure was far from saturation.

Currently, these organizations mainly feared the dynasty's stand on this, but the fight would start sooner or later. With the Black Star Army firing the first shot in the Flickering World, this process would be sped up tremendously.

In one of the free competition zones of the fourth phase within the Emerald Star Cluster, the enormous Black Star Army exploration fleet rode out of the dynasty's military stargate and arrived at the border of the Star Cluster.

Inside the command room, Hila stood before the operation console with a poker face, carefully looking at the holographic star map before her.

She had changed her clothes and was wearing a combat suit made of nanomaterials that Han Xiao had specially made for her. It was a black uniform with two rows of buttons. Its style was the luxurious version of the army officers' military uniform, skintight, showing her beautiful curves. The army's symbol was on her collar, and there was also a wide high-collar cape behind here in the color of black and gold with magnificent patterns. The inside of the cape was red. This set of clothes suited her unique vibe and elevated her aura.

The combat suit's model was 'Crimson Snake—First Gen', Beyond Grade A equipment. It consisted of tons of top-notch technology. Its usual mode was like a piece of normal clothing, but when in combat mode, it would showcase its powerful performance as a Beyond Grade A mechanical suit.

This combat suit was not built at the last minute. In fact, Han Xiao had made this equipment long before Hila returned. When Hila received this gift, although she did not say much on the surface, she had been wearing it since. She clearly liked it a lot.

"Deputy Army Commander, where are we going now?" the female aide-de-camp beside her asked.

Hila pressed on the holographic star map and zoomed in on one area. This was a planet at the edge of the Emerald Star Cluster called Planet Phiri. Its location was a little rural, so no one had occupied it yet.

"Here, to build a bridgehead," said Hila.

She was now the commander of the exploration fleet. Han Xiao had given her a lot of freedom in terms of making decisions, only limiting the army's exploration target to be the Emerald Star Cluster. The details would all be controlled by Hila.

The reason Han Xiao had chosen the Emerald Star Cluster was that this was also the main exploration target of the Modo Civilization, as well as a relatively prosperous area in his previous life. He remembered that there were also some hidden factors in the region. There was the wreckage of an old civilization that was discovered in this Star Cluster, and it was quite an advanced civilization with plenty of technical information. It caused conflicts between countless organizations in the previous life, but he did not know the exact location of it.

Most importantly, the Emerald Star Cluster was one of the locations where the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy might appear in.

According to EsGod's heritage, there were many coordinates the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy might appear at, and Han Xiao could not judge which one was real. Since EsGod did not die in his previous life, this information was not leaked, and he had secretly secured the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy without attracting the attention of the outside world. Even the players did not know much about it.

Nonetheless, Han Xiao had always been secretly monitoring Evans' whereabouts. This man who was the owner of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy in his previous life found a job after he was freed from prison and became an ordinary member of a financial group's exploration fleet, responsible for cleaning and repairing spaceships. The fleet he was in had come to the Emerald Star Cluster.

Therefore, Han Xiao was quite sure that the Emerald Star Cluster was where the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy would appear. After all, after the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was defeated by EsGod, it had definitely found an owner nearby, so the area where Evans was in had the highest possibility.

Of course, Hila did not know about any of that yet. She casually issued orders and commanded the fleet to head to Planet Phiri.

Meanwhile, some player guilds did not follow the main fleet but spread out on their own.

These guilds that had completed their registration had the authority to move on their own. In order to obtain their own stronghold, they did not want to move together with the main fleet. This was approved by Han Xiao silently. Furthermore, he even prepared quite a number of missions just for the players in the army interface, which had rich rewards. This was to encourage the guilds to move on their own and expand their lead.

…

Somewhere in the Emerald Star Cluster, Beast Ancestor Gorutan's fleet was stationed on one planet, building a bridgehead.

Although Gorutan was the protector of the Galactic Black Market behind the curtains, he also had his own organization. If there was anything special about this organization, it would be that most of its members were his offspring.

Gorutan stood at the peak of a mountain, looking down at the ground that was slowly being covered in metal. Above him was the dark galaxy, and northern lights flew in the sky.

His muscular and fearsome body was completely nude. The lion-like fur all over his body swayed with the corrosive wind, and dots of light surrounded his body, each of which was made of highly condensed Pugilist flames.

As a peak Beyond Grade A Pugilist, his training method had ascended from purely training his body. He had to use every inch of his body to feel the way the universe operated; it was very mysterious. Gorutan had stopped taking baths in Fixed Stars like Heber long ago.

This time, numerous meteors flew over from the sky and landed behind Gorutan. They were all Calamity Grade officers, and there were more than forty of them.

Everyone lowered their head and spoke with respect at the same time.

"Father!"

These officers were the Beast Ancestor's offspring, and they all had different appearances as if they were different species.

Gorutan really lived up to the 'ancestor' in his nickname. In fact, he had a more down to earth nickname among the civilians—Seed Spreader of the Galaxy.

After he evolved to become a Beyond Grade A species, he had obtained a very powerful reproductive capacity. His genes had extraordinary adaptability. He could have offspring with most species, and his way of expanding his race was brutal and simple. He captured females of different races for mating to give birth to all kinds of hybrid species.

If there were any outstanding mutants in his offspring, he would then turn that offspring into his mating machine to breed even stronger offspring. This way of doing things contradicted the ethics of some races, so Gorutan was disliked by quite many civilizations who felt he was like a savage beast. However, many races did not care about it. After all, the ethics of every race were different.

Gorutan turned around, not minding the fact that he was fully nude in front of his offspring, and said with a deep voice, "What is it?"

An offspring stepped forward. This offspring had the appearance of a spider-like insect but had a human-like face. His six pedipalp-like arms held a communicator at the same time to express his respect to Gorutan. "Father, Sorokin is looking for you."

Gorutan took the communicator, and Sorokin's hologram appeared before him.

"What's this about?"

Sorokin smiled calmly. "Remember my plan for the Black Star Army? It's time. When the Limitless Financial Group firms its ground, we will start to target the Black Star Army's businesses in his territory. Before that, we need to restrain the army's exploration."

"And you need my help?"

"That's right. Right now, the Black Star Army's exploration is heading to Planet Phiri, which is not far from you. I hope you can occupy Planet Phiri in advance. Their leader is Hila. Test her depth. Best to force the Black Star Army to retreat and delay their exploration progress while damaging their reputation."

"Why not do it yourself?"

"My original body isn't in the Emerald Star Cluster. Plus, I can't beat Hila." Sorokin smiled.

"Humph, we made a deal with you because I don't want to deal with the Black Star Army personally, but now you're asking me, the employer, to help. Why is that so?" Gorutan snorted. As a peak Beyond Grade A, he was not afraid of offending Black Star. He just did not want to work for free.

"My abilities are limited; I only have some strengths in terms of operating a business," Sorokin slowly said. "If you don't help me, I won't be able to restrict the Black Star Army's exploration. By then, don't blame me for not giving Black Star enough pressure… Also, I can leak this information to you; the federation and the church have plans to get rid of Hila."

"Oh? Are they not afraid of enraging the dynasty and starting another Tragedy of the Pinnacles?"

"Well, the fact is, Hila belongs to the Black Star Army; she did not agree to join the dynasty. So, killing her will only enrage Black Star. Hila becoming a Beyond Grade A is an unforeseen issue, but it has also shown us a new way to damage the Black Star Army."

Gorutan squinted. "Have you forgotten what Black Star said during the Meeting of the Gods? There are too few Beyond Grade As. Anyone dying won't be beneficial to us."

"Haha, is that really the case?" Sorokin smiled. "The Mechanic Emperor is extremely ambitious. He hopes to gather all of the Beyond Grade As to obtain more things, but when you think of it, aren't we being used by him? My thoughts happen to be the complete opposite of his. If there are fewer Beyond Grade As, those who are left will be safer. They'll be more important to the advanced civilizations."

Gorutan frowned. "Are you betraying the shared battlefront of the Beyond Grade As?"

"There has never been such a thing as betrayal. What have the others got to do with us? Is the situation the Beyond Grade As are in now not good enough?" Sorokin did not care at all. "When we plot to obtain things that don't belong to us, this kind of ambition will only lead to our demise."

"Don't ever say something like that to me. I'll take it as if I didn't hear what you just said." Gorutan waved his hand impatiently. "For the sake of our relationship, I'll help you this time. I'll visit Planet Phiri, but double my dividends for the next quarter, or there's no deal."

"Okay." Sorokin smiled.

Gorutan ended the call and looked back at his many offspring. "Prepare the spaceships and follow me."

This time, one offspring could not help but ask, "Father, for us to mess with the Black Star Army in the Flickering World, is it really worth…"

"You think Sorokin is the first person to have asked me to do this?" Gorutan snorted. "Hehe, in the Flickering World now, there are all too many organizations that want to deal with the Black Star Army…"

…

In the middle of their travels, the Black Star Army exploration fleet suddenly received a piece of information.

The female aide-de-camp hastily rushed into the room. "Your Excellency Deputy Army Commander, there's a situation."

Hila who was meditating opened his eyes, frowned, and said, "What is it?"

"Planet Phiri was occupied by someone before us. It's Beast Ancestor Gorutan's fleet. S-should we take use another planet as our stronghold?"

"Gorutan?" A tint of coldness flashed past Hila's eyes. "We did not hide our whereabouts, so the outside world knows our target, yet he deliberately snatched Planet Phiri. This is a provocation to the army! If we take a detour, it will damage the reputation the Army Commander has put a lot of effort in to build."

"But Gorutan is a peak Beyond Grade A. Y-you…" The aide-de-camp did not dare continue.

"Your Army Commander is also a peak Beyond Grade A. There's no reason to back away!" Hila stood up and said with a deep voice, "Advance at full speed!"

So what if it's a peak Beyond Grade A? It's not like I haven't been beaten by a peak Beyond Grade A before!

She was not someone like Garoze, who had already reached his peak. She was not afraid of challenging someone strong.

She believed that only fighting with strong people could stimulate her own potential.

…

At the same time, Han Xiao, who was counting his EXP with a grin every day in the Black Star Palace, received Phillip's message too and was slightly surprised.

"Gorutan? When did I offend him?"

Han Xiao scratched his head and was a little speechless.

Although he did not know the reason behind this, he was not a nobody anymore. There was no reason to back away.

Well, since you've decided to cut short your life span, it has nothing to do with me.

Chapter 1017: Pinnacle Tier Pugilist

Streams of light flashed across the universe, stopping not far from the planet. It showed itself as the exploration fleet of the Black Star Army.

"Deputy Army Commander, we're here."

On the bridge, Hila gazed at Planet Phiri through the porthole and saw Gorutan's fleet docked in orbit, facing them directly.

"Open the wide-area communications and contact them." Hila decided to be show manners before they acted.

The signaler sent out the message, and after a while, the communication call popped up on the screen.

After connecting, a bestial humanoid's picture appeared on the screen. It was a Calamity Grade Officer.

"I'm Gorragon's, the son of the Beast Ancestor. I pay respects to Your Excellency Hila."

"What is the meaning of this?" Hila frowned.

"Lord Father hopes to invite you for a meeting in Planet Phiri, and he's waiting for you on the surface right now."

"Discuss what?"

"I do not know of Lord Father's thoughts. The issue here is, do you dare to come?" Gorragon aggressively replied.

"Alright, then clear the path for my fleet to land. We can talk after."

"Apologies, but Father has mentioned that he will only allow you to proceed. The rest of the fleet must remain."

"Then ask him to scram," Hila immediately replied in a decisive manner. "All battleships, heed my order. Advance forward, and annihilate any that dare to block us."

At this moment, the communicator's screen flickered, and Gorutan's figure appeared.

Facing someone of the same level, appearing completely nude would be too impolite, and thus, he had put on a simple, sleeveless tunic, standing with his arms crossed and an impassive expression.

"Not bad. It seems like the Black Star Army has a tough Deputy Army Commander."

Seeing this, Hila immediately raised her fist, stopping all orders. She narrowed her eyes. "Gorutan, I'm very curious. The Black Star Army and you have no conflicts, so why are you provoking us?"

"Do you want to know why? If you meet up with me, I'll tell you," Gorutan replied. "Depending on whether you have the courage, I'll be waiting on the surface of the planet with the answer."

As he spoke, Gorutan's fleet took the initiative to shift away from Planet Phiri, putting the planet in between both fleets. Right now, Gorutan was left alone on Planet Phiri.

Hila thought for a moment before turning to address the vice fleet commander. "Activate a full scale detection of Planet Phiri and its surroundings to check if there are hidden vital signs or energy sources."

The commander nodded and sent down the order. He came back moments later with a report. "The surroundings are clear, and there's only a life signal on the planet representing Gorutan. How about it? Should we fire?"

Before his superior could give any orders, this vice commander was already thinking of ambushing and getting rid of Gorutan.

"Since he has shown such sincerity, I want to hear what he has to say. Wait on standby and keep the weapon system on alert mode. The moment the enemy's fleet shows any abnormal reactions, just fire straight at them."

Even if her fleet attacked, it would not deal much damage to Gorutan. Since he dared do such a thing, he was definitely prepared for all consequences, so Hila could only meet with him since she could not guess his intentions.

Maybe Gorutan wanted to set the battlefield to attack her, but she was not anxious. This was what she wanted; even if she could not beat a Pinnacle Beyond Grade A Super, she still had the confidence to block their attacks for a period of time.

Hila sat in a small spaceship and rapidly descended the atmospheric layer of Planet Phiri, stopping at a high altitude.

Shua!

The hatch opened, and Hila stepped out onto the air, looking down on the surface of the planet.

Within the rugged barren plains, Gorutan sat on a boulder, with his elbows placed on his knees. He looked up at Hila as he slowly spoke.

"As an Esper, the fact that you dared come so close to a Pinnacle level Pugilist shows that you have courage."

The sound that came out from his mouth seemed to cause the air in their surroundings to oscillate, spreading out far like the echoes of thunder.

Hila did not land, choosing to remain floating in the midair as she replied, "Get straight to the point. What did you want to meet me for?"

Gorutan stared at Hila before explaining, "I don't know how people will look at this, but in my eyes, you have the most potential among this batch of new Beyond Grade As."

"So?" Hila raised a brow.

"Someone with your talent will rise to a higher realm in the future. There's no need for you to remain as someone's subordinate. Moving out as an independent entity would suit you better." Gorutan drily spoke.

Hila's eyes flashed dangerously, and she coldly snapped, "Who are you representing in trying to drive a wedge between Black Star and me? The three Universal Civilizations?"

"I'm only representing myself and the Galactic black market's Management Committee. You can just take my words as a sincere suggestion."

"Don't you think that you're meddling too much?" Hila snorted.

"I can see that you're someone who is extremely stubborn and does not like to heed the commands of others. There will be a day when you'll eventually choose to be independent." Gorutan had a look of interest in his eyes. "When that day comes, I'm willing to give you an invitation to become one of the members of the Galactic black market."

Not only was he sowing discord, he was also trying to poach her.

However, Hila showed an expression of indifference. "My communicator is on. Black Star can totally hear your words."

"So what if he hears them?" Gorutan did not mind it. "You have the freedom of choice; you're not his slave."

"I'm not interested in your invite." Hila remained unmoved. "Are you done? If so, you can take your troops away, and we'll take it as though this provocation did not happen."

"I don't think this is provocation. Planet Phiri does not belong to your Black Star Army. It's a free competition zone, not your territory. No one stipulated that others could not occupy the planet that you guys are interested in." Gorutan shook his head.

"You long had the intention to occupy this planet, but you chose to wait for us to make our choice before you took it for your own. If this is not provocation, then what is?" Hila said.

"Don't be too overbearing, little kid." Gorutan grinned. "It's first come, first served, so it's you who needs to leave. Go find another planet. This is my stronghold now."

The moment he spoke, the atmosphere became tense as both people faced each other.

He had been entrusted with this by others, no matter what Hila's reaction was, but he would not have given way either. His goal was to force Hila's hand so that he could test out her skills.

In his view, this mission was very simple. He just had to fight with Hila, allowing the Black Star Army to suffer some losses. Then he could decide if he wanted to withdraw or not.

While this type of conflict and provocation would draw Black Star's ire, it would not be to the point of wanting the other party dead. He was certain that just as he did not wish to make an enemy out of Black Star, Black Star did not wish to make an enemy out of him. Both sides were not so easily provoked.

Hila's expression turned frosty. Gorutan was right. The Black Star Army was being unreasonable. However, if they retreated, the other party would not only not praise them for being reasonable, but they would treat them as weaklings.

If all problems could be solved through reasoning, there would be no need for disputes and wars.

Since neither side wanted to retreat, the only solution left was to use force.

Looking at Gorutan's expression, which bore no good intentions, Hila fell silent for a few seconds before she suddenly moved!

Boom!

A tremendous death energy storm swept through, turning into a tornado as it blasted downward!

"Pretty scary." Gorutan twisted his neck a little before stepping down hard.

Bang!

The earth cracked, and he stomped upward, leaving a huge ring-shaped crater on the ground, scattering dust everywhere.

He seemed to have turned into a comet, slamming into the torrential rain of death energy. The dark-brown Pugilist flame wrapped around his body, revealing a wild, arrogant temperament.

Bang!

Before Hila could react, the fist wreathed in pugilist flames landed squarely on her stomach.

The shield surrounding the battlesuit was shattered, and there were even cracks on her outer armor. Hila was slammed outward like a bullet, her speed breaking the sound barrier.

"Insane strength, insane speed…" Hila's expression slightly changed.

The shock absorption properties of the battlesuit could not withstand such a strong impact, and Hila could only feel that her internal organs seemed to have been flattened by this blow. The pain was overwhelming, and she only managed to stabilize her body in midair after much difficulty.

Both Gorutan and Black Star were at the pinnacle of Beyond Grade A, but the feeling she got from crossing blows with Gorutan was completely different from Han Xiao.

Han Xiao had displayed a complete suppression, where he was without weaknesses, controlling the battle from start to finish as though he could just adapt to anything. However, Gorutan's battle style was complete savagery, just like the invincible rampage of a beast.

Hila's impression of Beyond Grade A Pugilists mainly came from Heber, but fighting pinnacle level Beyond Grade A Pugilists was a totally different ball game, and they could not be seen as being on the same level.

Be it speed, strength, or energy intensity, there was a qualitative change. Objectively speaking, one Gorutan was enough to pummel three or four Hebers to death!

Only upon reaching the SS tier would someone be considered at the pinnacle of Beyond Grade A, and this battle strength was nothing to be joked about.

After his hit, Gorutan did not pursue her but rather remained floating, his head lowered as he observed the death energy eroding his body.

Because of his tanky body, the majority of the attacks were blocked purely by his body's strength. The damage done to the body was small, and only a few layers of Death's Erosion had stacked.

"A corrosive energy related to vitality… It seems like the rumors were true. You used such a method to gravely injure Tolaen. The more you accumulate, the stronger the power."

Gorutan glanced at Hila before covering himself with a jet of energy. It shattered the Death's Erosion stacks, directly dispelling them. As Pugilists relied on their bodies, they naturally had many skills to dispel negative statuses.

"This is going to be tricky…" Hila gritted her teeth, but her eyes lit up.

She found that Gorutan's combat capability was overwhelming, but this did not make her back down, instead increasing her fighting will.

The next moment, Hila took the initiative to start another round of attacks, and the death energy surged like a wave, attacking while wrapped around her.

The tsunami-like crimson wave surged over, and Gorutan launched himself into it. In an instant, an invisible shock wave was generated and exploded in midair, enveloping the incoming death energy.

Boom!

The vibrations echoed around the entire space. Gorutan's lunge was actually a skill, which caused the particles in the space in front to oscillate at high frequencies, collapsing the layers of incoming death energy.

"It seems like your strength is unworthy of your attitude."

Gorutan's expression remained indifferent, and his figure disappeared suddenly as he started to move at full speed.

Whoosh!

The difference in their speed was too great. Before Hila could react, he had already arrived beside her, and his leg containing great power whipped and slammed hard on her back.

Boom!

Her entire body arched like a bow from the impact, shooting up like a cannonball all the way out of the planet's atmosphere.

"Cough cough… I cannot fight him in melee battles." Hila felt as though dozens of bones were broken just from that kick, and she immediately changed her strategy.

When faced against Tolaen, she could still rely on her vampiric abilities to hold on, but comparing him with a pinnacle level Beyond Grade A, her attributes differed too much, to the point that she could not even see his figure!

In melee battles, a pinnacle level Beyond Grade A Pugilist was nigh invincible, and forcibly going head on with them was just asking for death.

"In a one-to-one battle, I have no way to retaliate. I need to complicate this battlefield."

As Hila thought about the possible battle tactics, the built-in communicator rang, and Han Xiao's voice came from it, with a tone that seemed as though he was smiling.

"How is it? Have you felt the power difference? Do you need help?"

"No need." Hila shook her head. If she always relied on Black Star for help, how could she grow?

"But you're not his opponent. If you can't do it, just let me take over."

Han Xiao raised a brow. He had known long ago that Hila would not be able to cope against Gorutan.

During the Meeting of the Gods, he had collected the attribute information of Gorutan, and there were a great deal of question marks. Even he himself might not be able to beat Gorutan head on, so Hila would have it worse. If a pinnacle Beyond Grade A could be dealt with so easily, there would be no need to use them as deterrents.

But he knew that even if Gorutan could not be beaten, Hila would not be the one at a disadvantage, so he did not interfere to allow Hila to gain more experience.

"Humph, wait till I'm almost beaten to death before you help."

Hila stabilized her body and turned around. While using her death energy to attack and contain Gorutan, she tried to increase the distance between them.

This was not even considered a struggle, merely a unilateral beating. If not for Gorutan deliberately slowing down the offensive to force out Hila's abilities, she would probably have already been beaten up. The high speed and strength he possessed was enough to break through most methods.

But truth be told, Gorutan did not have it easy either. After suffering from the repeated attacks of death energy, he felt a slight fear toward it.

"What a strange ability. If I couldn't forcibly crush it with my strength, her abilities would put me in a lot of danger…"

Just as he knocked Hila back with yet another punch, he discovered that Hila had tweaked the direction of her knockback, flying toward his troops.

"She actually took the initiative to fly toward my troops? Isn't she afraid of being besieged?"

Gorutan stopped in shock, but this time, Hila suddenly made a different gesture, and a sudden surge of mental energy burst out.

The world before his eyes warped and turned into an inky black space.

Lowering his head, all he saw were the grudges of countless creatures.

[Abyss of the Dead!]

While Pugilists would also temper their minds, their Psychological Resistance was not high to begin with, so Gorutan easily fell into the mental attack, freezing on the spot.

Taking this chance, Hila accumulated her death energy and ran straight through the shield established by the Gorutan fleet, rushing right into the fleet formation.

"What is she trying to do?" Gorragon, who had previously spoken with Hila, stood in the command room of one of the spaceships, looking confused.

Before he could take any action, Hila raised both her hands, and the death energy exploded, enveloping the entire fleet.

"What‽"

Gorragon got a shock, immediately commanding the fleet to retreat and avoid it.

However, his command had yet to be sent out when the dark red energy encompassed his entire sight.

Gorragon's eyes widened.

Bang bang bang!

In a flash, countless battleships were chewed up by the death energy like biscuits, and countless children of Gorutan were reaped.

With the [Vampiric] effect, she obtained enough vitality to recover her HP.

Just that short exchange previously made Hila clear that she was far from being Gorutan's opponent if they fought head on. With her own HP, she could not sustain the battle for a long time, so the only way was to enhance her endurance by turning it into a group fight, absorbing more vitality for herself.

Her combat capability in a large group fight was much higher than in single target battles!

Hila ran rampant within the fleet, killing wantonly, and her status quickly picked up even as countless screams were drowned in the explosion.

At this time, Gorutan finally got rid of the mental attack from [Abyss of the Dead]. The moment he returned to his senses, he was greeted with the image of Hila slaughtering his descendants, His expression warped in fury.

In his view, Hila was killing his descendants to vent her anger!

"You dare‽"

Chapter 1018: Confrontation

The death energy ravaged the fleet, eroding and penetrating the outer armor of every spaceship. They burst apart like fireworks as Hila's figure sailed through.

Uncountable troops on Gorutan's side were killed by the mixture of physical and mental damage. The death energy sapped their vitality, supplementing Hila's HP instead, and their soul fragments were absorbed by her to enhance her powers.

After receiving this attack, the fleet was in chaos for a short moment, but they quickly retaliated and fired a volley at Hila. However, most of their attacks were evaded or blocked by her death energy shield, and only a small portion caused damage.

In front of Hila's highly efficient vampirism ability, those injuries were healed in the blink of an eye.

Gorutan's eyes seemed like it was about to spit fire, his anger reaching extreme heights. He suddenly raised his speed, almost instantaneously breaking through the death energy barrier surrounding Hila. This time, he did not show mercy, raining blows on Hila's body, pummeling her.

Boom boom boom!

Bursts of compressed air blasted out from his fists, shattering Hila's internal organs and bones. The angered pinnacle Beyond Grade A pugilist's fists exuded great killing intent, as though he wished to beat her up into a ball of flesh.

However, Hila had received stolen plenty of vitality from the people she had just killed, so her HP constantly dipped and soared, barely supporting her through the intense attack.

Hila continued to dodge the blows as much as she could, and she even opted to retaliate at times, trading injury for injury.

"You're seeking death!"

Gorutan's fury knew no bounds, and as he pummeled Hila, he gazed with killing intent over at the Black Star Army's fleet.

Since Hila had dared to kill his subordinates, he could do the same to 'pay respect' to the Black Star Army.

But his eyes soon narrowed, as he saw that within the Black Star Army's fleet, a mechanical troop flew out from within one of the spaceships, standing at the very forefront. The lead mechanical soldier gave off frightening energy fluctuations. It was likely that Black Star had chosen to descend as an avatar.

Han Xiao's mechanical army remained in position, without any intention to save Hila, but Gorutan knew that if he were to attack the fleet, then it would become a two against one scenario.

There's only one of me, and I can't even summon an avatar. If I attack Black Star's fleet, I'll have to face off against him. Hila will then be able to freely slaughter my subordinates.

As this thought flashed through his head, Gorutan could only dismiss the thought of attacking the Black Star fleet, becoming even angrier in the process.

He was a dignified Pinnacle Beyond Grade A, so why did it seem like he was being forced to train the enemy?

Black Star, do you think that I really won't kill your subordinate‽

Good! Since you are not going to act, I'll beat your Deputy Army Commander to death!

From the time Hila began to slaughter his men, the degree of conflict had escalated, and Gorutan no longer held the mentality to test out her skills but rather had the intention to kill…

I shouldn't provoke Black Star? So what! We're both Beyond Grade A pinnacles. Does Black Star think that I'm afraid of him? This daddy here also has a temper!

Gorutan immediately stepped up his offensive, bombarding his opponent in front of him.

Such a mad attack would mean that he was more prone to vulnerability. Hila was bleeding all over, but she ignored the pain and kept calm, staring at the increasingly intense death energy on Gorutan's body. Her eyes flickered with an unknown light.

At this time, Gorutan's fist swirled with a violent aura, and after utilizing his skills, the power surged. Space seemed to warp around his fist.

Swoosh!

The fist passed through Hila's chest, as though piercing through it, separating the red ocean of death energy surrounding her.

But Gorutan's eyes narrowed. He did feel as if he had hit something concrete.

Hila's body dissolved into a mass of death energy, and disengaging from Gorutan's arm, the ocean of death energy took on the shape of a humanoid, reshaping into Hila's body.

[Advancing in the Dead Sea]!

Hila could turn her body into an energy life form and perform teleportation in any area filled with death energy with just a short cooldown. This was one of her few displacement skills.

Gorutan frowned. After beating his opponent for such a long time, he had assumed that she had no ability to teleport and dodge.

Just as he was about to pursue her, Gorutan felt his fist sinking. In that instant, Hila had commanded the death energy to wrap around his fist, releasing a huge attractive force that was forcing his arm to sink in the ocean of death energy.

At the same time, the [Death's Erosion] stacks on his body soared from ten to fifteen stacks!

[Extradition of the Dead]!

Hila's method of superimposing the [Death's Erosion] stacks was not just based through general attacks. She had the ability to stack multiple Death's Erosion instantly onto a target, and this skill was one of them.

She had initially been hiding her skills, all for this sudden blitzkrieg. She covered all fifteen stacks on Gorutan in one swoop before detonating them using [Reaper of Souls].

She had only attacked Gorutan's fleet to activate her vampiric effect, creating a battlefield that was conducive to herself to improve her endurance, as well as to attract hatred.

In her point of view, only by using a decoy and provoking Gorutan's anger would he reveal flaws for her to obtain the opportunity to attack. As long as he stepped up his offensive, the energy spent toward defense would weaken.

Hila's eyes were calm, and the moment the skill came into effect, she did not give Gorutan time to react, seamlessly connecting it with [Reaper of Souls], detonating all fifteen stacks.

Boom!

Gorutan exploded with a dazzling red light!

Hila took the opportunity to back away, distancing herself.

However, a dark brown pugilist flame wave burst out from within the explosion right after, evaporating all the death energy along its way as it slammed directly into Hila. It pushed her all the way toward Planet Phiri.

The brown ray of light penetrated Planet Phiri like a toothpick going through an orange.

The next second, the light fully pierced through both ends of the planet and began to expand rapidly, revealing the red glow of the planet core.

Buzz!

Everyone's eyes were greeted with an expanse of white, forcing them to subconsciously close their eyes. If the battleship porthole did not have the function to automatically adjust spectrum and brightness, this level of light would have been enough to burn the eyes of the majority present.

"Warning! Warning! High energy reaction detected! Reaction output level: Planet Annihilation!"

A harsh alarm sounded on every ship, and when everyone reopened their eyes, the huge planet had disappeared as though it had never existed.

All that remained were some bits of dust floating in its place. The entire planet had been collapsed and annihilated, and Hila was nowhere to be seen.

This moment, the death energy from Reaper of Souls collapsed, revealing Gorutan's body, which was covered in corrosive wounds and slowly healing.

Because his level was too high, the judgment of death was unsuccessful, but he had still lost twenty percent of his HP from that one blow!

Ever since he had stepped into the pinnacle level of the Beyond Grade A realm, Gorutan had rarely suffered such a serious injury. He had expected it to be a simple matter to deal with this newly born Beyond Grade A; he did not expect to suffer from such a loss.

In this fury, Gorutan had activated one of his aces, his self-created pugilist technique [Beast Ancestor Style—Light of Annihilation]. This was not just a pure Pugilist skill but also contained the laws of the universe that ran through his body.

On the surface, it seemed to just be a pugilist flame beam, but it actually stirred up the space around it, creating a terrible radiation energy to amplify its damage. Hitting the planetary core would cause a chain reaction to occur, resulting in planetary obliteration.

Hila's HP was not full to begin with, and with this blow, it was likely that she would have been instantaneously killed.

Gorutan's murderous eyes turned toward Black Star in the distance, the aura around him rising exponentially.

Having killed the Deputy Army Commander in front of him, Gorutan did not think that Black Star would remain unmoved, so he began to prepare to face this formidable foe.

However, much to his surprise, Han Xiao and his mechanical troops did not rush over as expected but rather turned to watch the smoldering wreckage of the planet.

Just as he was feeling puzzled, specks of gray shone around the wreckage of Planet Phiri and gathered to form a whirlwind. Hila's spiritual body was within that whirlwind, and this also attracted Gorutan's gaze.

The next moment, Hila's body reformed within the whirlwind, and the death energy draped around her like a cloak, only revealing a face that was deathly pale.

One of the mechanical soldiers threw out an Army Emblem, which Hila activated, turning it into countless nanoparticles that formed a Crimson Snake battlesuit around her body. Immediately afterward, the life potion of Aurora that was built within the suit was injected into her, and Hila's sluggish state after defying death quickly vanished, her HP recovering to more than half.

"Not dead‽" Gorutan's eyes narrowed, his expression sinking.

If he had not intended to kill Hila, that would have been all good, but since he had already revealed his killing move, this only made Gorutan feel even more humiliated.

But Black Star had already intervened, so continuing his attack was out of the question. Gorutan frowned, choosing to rearrange the formation of his fleet instead. In his view, since Hila did not die, Black Star definitely had to give him an explanation.

On the other side, Hila flew back to Han Xiao's avatar, and Han Xiao glanced at her with a slight smile on his face, "How is it? Do you want to continue being beaten up?"

Hila shook her head. "I can't beat him, but I managed to give him something to remember."

She felt that this battle was quite rewarding, allowing her to accumulate more experience and lessons on dealing with other Beyond Grade As. At the same time, she had harvested a lot of the opponent's troops, and her ability strength was slightly enhanced.

In particular, there were several Calamity Grades who had died by her hand, so the bonus provided was quite impressive, better than the beasts she had slaughtered during her training.

As she spoke, Hila suddenly paused and said with some uncertainty, "This time… did I cause trouble for you?"

In order to reverse her disadvantage, she had attacked the other party's fleet. This sort of combat method made it too easy to incite hatred, so Gorutan would probably have a deeper hatred against her.

Of course, Hila had no intention of apologizing to Gorutan at all. The moment she entered a fighting state, the enemy's life was nothing but a mere blood bag in her eyes. She would only apologize to Han Xiao.

My character seems to make enemies easily. Perhaps staying in the Black Star Army is the wrong decision…

Hila could not help but think that way, pursing up her lips.

She was still the same Goddess of Death who treated life like weeds. This could be a characteristic brought by abilities. The only thing that was better was that she would not kill ordinary people indiscriminately, and her cruelty was only aimed toward the enemy.

Han Xiao knew that Hila was not good with words. She spoke her mind frankly, and expecting her to stay her hand was impossible.

Han Xiao shook his head, answering with an unquestionable tone. "We'll talk more when we return. Just go and rest. I'll deal with the rest."

Hearing this, Hila opened and closed her mouth repeatedly, but in the end, she nodded quietly and boarded the spaceship.

Han Xiao controlled his avatar to move slowly toward Gorutan's troops.

Upon reaching the center of the two fleets, the troops threw out a multitude of compressed orbs, which transformed into a small floating sanctuary of around a thousand square meters. The door of the base opened wide, and Han Xiao made an inviting gesture toward Gorutan.

The latter narrowed his eyes but flew into the base. The sanctuary was full of fresh air, and in the middle was a long conference table, with a high seat at both ends.

Han Xiao sat on one of the seats, nodding toward Gorutan.

"Please sit."

Gorutan plonked down on one of the chairs and grumbled, "Black Star, your Deputy Army Commander is really brave. I haven't seen such a Beyond Grade A who seeks death so readily. Does she think that she can do as she pleases with you as a backer?"

"Haha, what sort of words are those? She has always been bold, and it's nothing to do with me." Han Xiao shook his head.

"I don't want to continue talking nonsense with you." Gorutan waved his hand. "I'm giving you face by not wanting her life. But she killed my descendants, and this debt must be settled. Let's discuss how to solve this."

"I think it's simple." Han Xiao controlled the avatar to stroke its metallic chin. "You take your troops to leave this place, and I won't pursue the matter any further. How about that?"

"What did you say‽ Say that again!" Gorutan glared furiously, his pugilist flame raging around him.

"Don't get too agitated." Han Xiao waved his hands to placate Gorutan. "I don't think Hila promised to challenge you, so who is to blame for this? And I think you probably discovered it, but she attacked your fleet not to vent her anger but rather to show her abilities and create a favorable battlefield for herself. After all, she's not your match, so of course she needed to utilize her surroundings. From my perspective, it seems like it was your entire fleet facing off against her. Isn't that more unfair?"

"I've not come into contact with you much before, but it seems like your reputation really precedes you. You're every bit as shameless as the rumors say." Gorutan coldly laughed.

"Is that so?" Han Xiao clicked his tongue. "A pinnacle Beyond Grade A bullying a newly born Beyond Grade A, is that very glamorous? I have no grudges nor hatred with you, yet you choose to provoke and bully my Deputy Army Commander. Of course, she is not your opponent, but you actually didn't even allow her to create a favorable environment for herself. If that's not bullying the weak, what is?"

Gorutan's words were stuck in his throat, and he finally growled in a deep voice, "No matter what, many of those killed were my descendants, and some were even Calamity Grades that I'd painstakingly raised. She attacked my fleet first, so this matter was incited by her. I won't let this go!"

Han Xiao laughed in response. "Wasn't this entire thing started by you? Why is it now our problem? Furthermore, you actively provoked me first, and now you're saying that my subordinates have gone too hard on you. I feel that you're more shameless than me."

Bang!

Gorutan slammed the table heavily as he stood up, the fury apparent in his expression.

"Black Star, watch your attitude!"

"Alright, let's say that you make sense. Then, what do you want us to do?"

"Of course, I want compensation!" Gorutan coldly replied. "I won't force you to repay a life with a life, but I want you to compensate me and make Hila apologize to me."

"Oh, sounds reasonable." Han Xiao smiled. "But I refuse."

"Black Star!" Gorutan smashed the table between them into smithereens, bellowing, "You wish to make me an enemy‽"

At this moment, Han Xiao's pleasant tone turned cold. "You think you're the only one who's angry? You bullied my old friend and even wanted to poach her. I haven't settled this with you! And also… what sort of mistaken notion makes you think that I cannot afford to make you an enemy‽"

The Lord's Avatar slowly rose up, floating until it came before Gorutan. The two of them stared straight at each other, and their gazes looked as though it could wipe out planets with it alone.

Han Xiao slowly spoke.

"It's far from your turn to manage my people!"

As he spoke, he raised a hand, poking at Gorutan's chest as his voice grew steely.

"You people come and test my patience and limits every day. You think that I'm without a temper? This daddy here has killed your people! You want to play with me? I'll play to the end with you. Can you even afford that‽"

Chapter 1019: Shortened Lifespan, Dark Clouds

The moment he spoke, the atmosphere turned sharp like drawn daggers.

The anger in Gorutan's eyes almost condensed into reality, and his energy fluctuations continuously rose, exuding huge pressure on their surroundings. The surrounding metal walls gradually cracked as they vibrated from the high frequency.

"Want to attack?"

Han Xiao's eyes crackled with electricity, his whole body flickering with blue-gold electrical serpents, producing harsh popping sounds.

This stalemate continued for another ten seconds or so before Gorutan suddenly collected his energy outburst, and the pressure in the room drastically lessened.

The rage on his face quickly faded, and he coldly said, "Black Star, you really gave me quite the surprise. You're really unyielding."

Han Xiao crossed his arms and replied in a level tone, "We can speak more of whether I'm unyielding in the future. Right now, what do you intend to do?"

Gorutan remained expressionless, only wagging a finger toward the avatar.

"I'll remember the matters today. We still have scores to settle."

He turned and strode away, leaving the sanctuary and flying toward his own fleet.

"You're really good at spitting vicious words. I really thought that you would take action just now." Han Xiao shook his head. He walked to the door, watching as Gorutan led his fleet and vanished from sight.

This minor conflict had ended with Gorutan's retreat, so Han Xiao withdrew his machinery, controlling the Lord's Avatar to return to the main flagship. Hila had been waiting for him the whole time.

The moment he entered the command room, Hila came up.

"What sort of conditions did you promise him, or did you force him to retreat?"

Han Xiao shook his head. "It was nothing like that. He left on his own."

"Gorutan had eaten such a loss. Could he even swallow his anger?" Hila was suspicious.

"At least on the surface, he has not taken a loss. He has annihilated the planet we chose and delayed our exploration speed. We have no choice but to change our target and find another planet, and you have killed some of his subordinates in return, so we should be considered even."

"Will he take this lying down?" Hila frowned.

"Of course not. We've already formed a grudge with him, and he will not leave things be."

Hila slowly spat out a breath, whispering, "I increased the conflict between us and got a new enemy for the army. I…"

"Don't blame yourself. You did what was necessary."

Han Xiao interrupted her as he waved his hands in dismissal. "Gorutan's challenge was a kind of test. Just like how the winds howl around the highest peaks, the number of people who wish to test us are numerous. Behind Gorutan might exist even more organizations and forces. If we are not tough and vicious to them, every organization will think that we're easy to provoke. Furthermore, the strength between both of you is too vastly different, and he challenged you to bully you. Thus, there's no need to feel bad since you got beaten up by him, or else the prestige of the army would have fallen."

Hila stared at Han Xiao, her eyes shining with a weird light as she tilted her head.

"So, you don't care if I make more enemies?"

"The part I like about you is your ferocity," Han Xiao casually replied. "So what if Gorutan was just testing you out? Are you going to obediently accompany him to put on a show, then let him leave after patting his butt? Remember this, he actively sought us out to make enemies of us; it was not you who sought him out. If one is not vicious, they cannot stand firmly in their territory. I brought you over to the competition area not to let you be a softie but to crush through all that blocks your route."

Right now, the status of the Black Star Army was different from before. It possessed the largest territory in the Flickering World, and it naturally had more responsibilities such as bringing benefits and prestige to the dynasty since it was holding the fort there.

"Really?"

"Of course." Han Xiao smiled, patting her shoulder.

You're an important fighter of mine, and the main thing that is needed is to have deterrence. If I don't defend you, should I speak for the enemy instead? Wouldn't that be ironic?

Originally, Han Xiao only wished to borrow Hila's Esper Ability to let Gorutan suffer some losses, provoking Gorutan was out of his plan. However, while things had gotten to this point, he had no fear. Since the other party had chosen to provoke him first, getting beaten to this point was his just desserts.

Hearing Han Xiao reassure her, Hila's expression relaxed a little. She paused before asking, "So, what did you say to him just now?"

"I just…"

Han Xiao simply narrated the prior events.

Hearing this, Hila could not help but smirk, and she wondered, "You were so unyielding, but he actually did not start fighting with you, huh?"

"I'm still a pinnacle Beyond Grade A after all." Han Xiao laughed. "Furthermore, it's because of you that he did not make a move."

"Me?"

"We have two Beyond Grade As here, so a battle wouldn't be in his favor. Furthermore, Gorutan is not in his peak state; making a move would bring him more disadvantages than advantages."

If it was just a normal Beyond Grade A, Gorutan might not have cared, but Hila had used [Reaper of Souls] to inflict heavy damage, which provided a strong deterrent effect. This resulted in Gorutan's HP not being at maximum capacity. If he faced off against Black Star as well, the risk for him was a bit too high.

Han Xiao hypothesized that this should be the reason for Gorutan's withdrawal. While Pugilists had heads of steel, they also knew how to judge the situation. In the face of an obviously unfavorable situation, it was better to retreat.

He also did not wish to force Gorutan, as a pinnacle Beyond Grade A Pugilist had a lot of burst power. He was there as an avatar, not his true form. Furthermore, with his reputation as a tank, Gorutan would definitely choose to attack Hila first, and with her [Death Immunity] skill still on cooldown, it would be more dangerous.

Both sides had their own reservations.

After a pause, Han Xiao said, "Gorutan will come at us again, so it's important to pay attention. There's a high chance he will target you."

"Maybe we can take the initiative and launch an attack." Hila's thinking was forever that extreme.

"Launch an attack? Depends on the situation."

Han Xiao shook his head. It was not that the idea was not possible, but he needed more assurance.

Now that the players had returned in Version 4.0, he could finally continue his rapid upgrades, and his stagnated level could finally increase once again.

Based on his current strength, it would not be so easy to deal with Gorutan. He hoped to complete one or maybe even two more advancements before resolving this matter.

Other than his plan to make Gorutan an enemy, Han Xiao had been lying low for over twenty years, letting the outside world think that he was also facing a bottleneck. But the moment he exchanges blows with another pinnacle Beyond Grade A, he would have to reveal his current strength, and that old jerk Manison would be sure to come out once more.

It is safer to first complete my advancement at level 320. This is the most important thing currently, Han Xiao thought to himself.

If he foresaw things properly, the worst-case scenario in this matter might result in a dangerous chain reaction.

He needed to be stronger to deal with it!

When the conversation ended, the Lord's Avatar fell dormant once more, and Hila returned to her position.

Since Planet Phiri had already been reduced to dust, they had to look for a new planet to build a stronghold.

…

On the other side, Gorutan's fleet was returning to their planet that served as their stronghold.

Gorutan reclined in the tall throne, holding a huge cup that fit his figure and continuously poured a special spirit down his throat.

Several of his female descendants were around him, some holding medical tools to treat his wounds, whilst others held scissors to help him trim the hair near his wounds. The rest were in charge of massaging him.

"Lord Father, is it comfortable?"

"Use more strength."

Gorutan wiped his mouth, throwing the empty cup to the side. He looked down at the Calamity Grades standing below the dais and coldly said, "Is the casualty report out?"

"It's already out. Please have a look." One of the Calamity Grades walked up, passing him a communication terminal.

Opening the virtual screen, he glanced at the figures and snorted. "She actually dared to kill five of my Calamity Grades. I'll kill that Hila sooner or later! Then there's that Black Star b*stard. To dare be so unyielding! If not for my minor injury, I would've torn his avatar apart!"

Seeing Gorutan in a rage, everyone wisely kept silent.

"Don't think that it's because I'm afraid of Black Star. He does not have the ability to force me to make concessions. I blasted Planet Phiri apart and slowed down their progress. I have accomplished what Sorokin requested." Gorutan coldly snorted.

He had chosen to stay away from Han Xiao's sharp edge because of his current condition, as well as the fact that there was no need to fight Black Star alone. His original goal was just to slow them down and test out the other party's skills.

Thus, if he wanted a better way to level the playing field, he would have to follow Sorokin's recommendation and approach the federation and church to get rid of Hila, since they already intended to do so. He would not need to move.

Gorutan then changed the topic. "Since a batch have died, raise another batch of hybrid descendants on our home planet and bring them here."

"Are you personally going to spread your seeds?"

Gorutan waved his hand. "Just use those from the storage."

In his main camp, there were females responsible for bearing descendants at all times. After all, their efficiency of mating and multiplying offspring was too low, so a large amount of Beyond Grade A DNA from Gorutan was stored in a freezer to be used for reproduction. It had extremely strong vitality and adaptability, and using artificial insemination would allow them to produce offspring on a larger scale, supplemented by hormones such as oxytocin to help accelerate childbirth.

After many years of experimenting, he had accumulated a variety of hybrid combinations that would allow them to produce excellent offspring. Through mixing with different species, he could produce offspring with various racial talents, so females were hoarded in his camp to be used as a medium for offspring.

As for the origins of these females… as a Beyond Grade A who sat high above, he naturally would not waste time falling in love with so many females. Some came willingly, others less so… None of the people who ran the Galactic Black Market were clean people anyways.

At this moment, Gorutan coughed twice.

"Lord Father, your injuries…" one of the officers muttered in a worried tone.

"Hila's Esper Ability has a strong lethality and high-explosiveness to wound even me." Gorutan frowned. "During the battle just now, I did not feel it, but my body is a little weird."

As he spoke, Gorutan closed his eyes, diving into the cellular level to observe his body's situation. Among the Super systems, the Pugilists had the greatest degree of control over their bodies.

Everyone turned silent for a while before Gorutan suddenly snapped his eyes open, abruptly standing up. The female descendants around him were all thrown back.

"Dammit, her Esper Ability can weaken the vitality of cells!"

Gorutan's expression distorted. He almost turned mad with fury.

Even when that batch of elites had died under Hila's hands, he had not been so mad!

The vitality of a cell was related to the number of cell divisions it could make, and this sort of property was extremely secretive, to the point that Beyond Grade As normally could not sense it. It was only now that he discovered that his lifespan had been cut!

Not merely just his lifespan, but fertility was also closely related to the vitality of his cells. With the reduction in vitality for his DNA, there would be a decline in the quality of his progeny!

Boom!

In his rage, the pugilist flames erupted, strong pressure forcing all his descendants to sprawl on the ground and tremble.

"Such a devilish damaging Esper ability…" The veins of Gorutan's forehead throbbed as his hatred for Hila practically overflowed.

He did not expect that this operation would actually result in his life span being reduced.

An absolute loss!

Gorutan's chest heaved up and down violently, and his breaths came out in gasps as he entertained the thought of rushing back to kill her.

"L-Lord Father…"

At this time, his descendants started to plead with him. Seeing the situation, Gorutan could only reluctantly reduce his anger, and the raging Pugilist aura slowly calmed down.

"All of you, scram!"

Everyone rushed to get out of the room as fast as possible. They were aware that they should not be around their father when he was angry.

Only Gorutan remained in the room. He sat on his throne for a while before picking up the communicator and calling Sorokin.

After three rings, the call connected, and Sorokin showed himself on the screen, smiling as he spoke.

"Your Excellency Beast Ancestor, how's the situation?"

Gorutan coldly glared at him for a while before finally saying, "The matter has been settled. I blasted Planet Phiri apart and have also tested Hila out. However, I lost quite a few of my descendants in the process, and I also almost got angered to death by Black Star."

"That's great. Your Excellency is indeed reliable. I'll compensate you for any losses. So, what is the result of your test?"

"Hila's Esper Ability is extremely dangerous, possessing frightening explosive power…"

Gorutan relayed his discoveries in battle, pausing at the last part before continuing in a deep voice.

"Her Esper Ability also has a terrifying property. As long as it hits a life form, it will be able to reduce the cell vitality and the life span of the target. I suffered a huge loss for this discovery!"

Sorokin paused, his smile vanishing immediately. His expression also turned grave.

"Are you serious?"

"I shouldn't have told you this and allowed the federation and church to activate their people. After they discover that they have shortened their life spans, they'll blame you for the information lapse." Gorutan coldly snorted.

"… I understand." Sorokin narrowed his eyes.

"I hope that you will truthfully tell the people in the federation and the church what I've said. Don't play any tricks. Or else, even if I'm a shareholder of the Limitless Financial Group, I'll still beat you up!" Gorutan's eyes were cold.

"Relax. I have integrity." Sorokin solemnly nodded before cutting the call.

Gorutan threw the communicator to the side, his expression cold and his eyes gleaming with an unknown light.

By allowing the federation and the church to know that Hila's Esper Ability had the power to reduce one's life span, two things could happen.

One, because of fear, they would give up on targeting her.

Two, because of fear, they would not allow her to continue living.

Based on what he knew of the federation and the church, the latter had a ninety-nine percent chance of occurring.

If Hila had such strength, the universal civilizations would not allow her to grow.

In the past, Hila had belonged to the Chaotic Evil Faction, and there was no clear distinction in their powers. Furthermore, most people were reluctant to provoke such a crazy woman and dying in vain.

But the situation was different. Hila was a member of the Black Star Army. She was a stinger that belonged to someone and would only point her deadly stinger toward her enemies.

As a result, the organizations and powers opposing Black Star Army would feel an immense threat.

In terms of targeting the pinnacle combatants, Hila was like a formidable chronic poison, causing a dark cloud to form over everyone's head. No one was willing to have their life span reduced!

Nobody was willing to have this dangerous character oppose them, let alone see her continue to grow.

Such Super High Risk Esper Abilities, whose very existence was a sin, should be killed as soon as possible!

Gorutan was certain that, as long as the news spread, most Beyond Grade As would not want to see this ability grow!

This would also help solidify the federation and the church's intentions to kill!

Chapter 1020: Don't Blame Your Brother for Not Having Values; Blame Your Wife for Being Too Alluring

Everyone had their own way of survival, and in the eyes of the top organizations, Sorokin was a miraculous existence.

He was obviously hired by the federation, the church, and the Galactic Black Market, yet he could slowly penetrate and become the middleman of all these influential organizations.

Under his manipulation, Gorutan's testing of Hila quickly spread to the federation and the church, immediately attracting the attention of the upper echelons, who convened their allies for an urgent meeting.

The main base of the Arcane Church was located in another Star Cluster within the free competition zone. At this time, the projections of the majority of Beyond Grade As affiliated with the church were gathered, and there were also several important bishops and officials present.

After circulating the intelligence on Hila, everyone had a noticeable change in their expression as they read it.

Tolaen jumped up, his face pale. "Hila's Esper Ability can reduce the lifespan of Beyond Grade As‽"

He was not a Pugilist, so he did not have the ability to look into the microscopic changes in his cellular activity. Before this meeting, he did not know what had happened to him!

Not only did he lose in a fight with Hila, he even lost God knew how many years from his life. This was such a huge loss for him!

Tolaen felt intense regret. How could he have been so unlucky as to meet such an opponent?

Even fighting would reduce his lifespan, so who would want to do that? Even the craziest person would think twice! If he had known, he would not have agreed to the duel. No, if he had known, he would not even have sought Dragon Emperor Ames out!

I'm going into closed door cultivation…

Everyone shot him a pitiful glance, which lasted for about three seconds, then they no longer bothered with him, instead beginning their discussion.

"I didn't expect this new Beyond Grade A to have such a strange Esper Ability. This resembles the Power of Death on the list of Super High Risk Esper Abilities." Sun Hunter was sat at the table. "I remember this being the ability of one of the Primordial Ones, but now it has resurfaced once more."

"That's right. I also remember the file. What was their name again…"

Kasuyi cut in. "Nerkese, the Controller of Death. She had an elder sister who was dubbed Mother of All Things, and she could spread her life force to any living organism."

"Right, right, it's those two! They were pretty famous among the Primordial Ones, being born from different civilizations. While they had no blood ties with each other, they happened to meet by fate within the vast and endless universe. Their Esper Abilities, which were completely in line with each other, allowed them to become sisters even without a blood tie… Ah! What an artistic legend, totally revealing the atmosphere of the exploration era, perfect," one of the Beyond Grade As exclaimed emotionally.

His name was Lawrence, and he had a subclass of an artist. He was always dressed flamboyantly, full of 'impact' to one's eyes.

"Eh? They weren't blood sisters?" One of them scratched his head.

"That's not true. After so many years, the legends have long been distorted. Those that are kept in our base are the truth," one of the senior officials commented. "Your Excellencies, can we return to the topic of Hila now?"

'Child of Light' Sagman nodded. "The Power of Death is a Super High Risk Esper Ability that can easily reap lives. If we sit and watch Hila mature, once she loses control like Thousand Shadows one day, that will be the disaster for the entire universe."

"This is secondary. The greatest problem is… she's under the Black Star Army, which is our enemy." 'Sea Spirit' Dylan gritted his teeth.

"Such an ability is dangerous. If not handled well, when Hila matures, we'll have to worry about such things when we deal with the Black Star Army," 'World Gate' Taylor added.

They were all participants of the Planet Lighthouse battle and had suffered a loss to Han Xiao. They had the strongest hostility toward the Black Star Army and always wanted to give him a slap back.

Psyker thought for a while before nodding. "That's right. To us Beyond Grade As, a decrease in lifespan is too scary."

Sun Hunter threw him a sideward glance. "I don't think you need to worry about this problem."

"Eh?" Psyker jerked back. "What do you mean?"

"Based on the strength that Hila showed when fighting against Gorutan, if you were pitted against her, you would probably be beaten to death immediately. Thus, a reduction in your lifespan should not matter to you."

"…"

Psyker thoroughly felt the evil of this world in this very moment and turned his head to follow Tolaen, going into closed door cultivation.

"Stop fooling around," Kasuyi blandly said. He turned toward the officials. "How do the upper echelons of the church view this matter?"

The few officials exchanged a glance before one of them solemnly said, "They hope for you to persuade Hila to join us, to become our ally. If it doesn't work, eliminate her."

Everyone's eyes flashed. They thoroughly understood why the Arcane Church would think this way.

In addition to the threat she posed, her very presence in another faction would also affect the recruitment of Beyond Grade As, as newly born Beyond Grade As would choose to join the faction that she was in so as not to face her.

While Hila belonged to the Black Star Army, she had yet to officially join any advanced civilizations, so the Arcane Church naturally hoped to obtain her allegiance and grasp this lethal weapon. This was something Gorutan did not think about. Only when it was impossible for them to obtain her would they choose to destroy her.

The Beyond Grade As even thought another layer deeper.

If Hila's skill only affected Beyond Grade As due to their long lifespans, would that mean that the Arcane Church planned to use her to act as a deterrent for all the Beyond Grade As present?

If this was in ordinary times, no one would have this thought, but everyone present had coincidentally attended Han Xiao's Meeting of the Gods and had been instilled with the same ideology by Manison, the idea that all Beyond Grade As were standing on the same front line. Thus, everyone could not help but think deeper.

The entire place fell silent as many of them struggled with their internal thoughts.

Kasuyi's expression remained unchanged, however. He glanced around before saying, "I feel that we can put the plan of pulling Hila over into action immediately, but as for elimination, we must think twice. While we're all in the Flickering World, and gathering is convenient, our every movement is more likely to be watched. Killing Hila will also provoke Black Star, so it's better to wait and see what the Federation of Light does. After all, they received the same intelligence as us."

"I understand." One of the officials nodded. "We have yet to be repaid for the loss of Ninjia, so we do not wish to work with the Federation for now. It's indeed better to wait and see. However, when we decide to move, I hope everyone will readily participate."

"No problem!" Other than Psyker, the rest of the participants of the Planet Lighthouse battle expressed their fervent attitudes.

Kasuyi did not speak, his eyes flickering with an unknown light.

On the other side, the Federation of Light had also convened a meeting, but the topic was vastly different from that of the Arcane Church.

"Hila's ability is indeed dangerous, no doubt, but dealing with her will incite the wrath of the Black Star Army, and that is not worth it," Hades replied.

One of the elders frowned. "But in the long run, Hila is obviously more threatening. Incurring the wrath of the Black Star Army is worth it."

"Are you sure?" Hades shot back. "Have you forgotten about the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter?"

Once these words were spoken, everyone in the Federation of Light jumped before falling into deep thought.

"The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter possesses a similar level of threat. In fact, it even has a higher priority level than Hila. This might be an opportunity for us to reach a deal with Black Star to unlock the Spacetime Amber seal for us. It will be profitable for both parties," Hades said bluntly.

At this moment, Manison dryly added, "That's right. I feel that we need to consider Black Star's attitude. The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter is more important for now."

Everyone turned to look at him, some with surprised expressions, while others seemed to know his underlying meaning.

Many of the Beyond Grade As knew that Manison had expressed his intention based on the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, but in actual fact, a great part was due to the impact of the Meeting of the Gods.

Manison was the main proposer of all the Beyond Grade As sharing the same battlefront, and he also valued Han Xiao's influence within the Flickering World. He hoped that Han Xiao could build an interaction platform based around this shared battlefront, so he was unwilling to antagonize him.

Speaking of which, if not for Han Xiao organizing the Meeting of the Gods and having spoken about the shared circumstances of the Beyond Grade A, the Beyond Grade As would probably not have had many reservations about dealing with Hila. Could this have been within his plans as well‽

After considering the matter, the Chief Elder replied after a pause, "Indeed, if we're able to undo the seal on the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, then the problem of Hila can temporarily be placed aside, but our chances of success are close to nil."

He paused and slowly added, "The Arcane Church will definitely take action, trying to poach or eliminate her, and we can warn Black Star of this, but this isn't great leverage. Behind Black Star is the dynasty, and they do not require our help in terms of combat strength. Furthermore, being an ally of the dynasty, he will definitely have his worries that if the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter is unsealed, we can use it against him. Under all these circumstances, there is no way he will agree to deal with us."

Hearing this, everyone nodded. From the perspective of Black Star, he would not possibly agree to this. The main point was that the federation's leverage was not enough to move him.

In fact, the federation had always wanted a good relationship with Han Xiao, so as to be able to unlock the seal on the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, something they currently could only see but not touch.

However, the Evolutionary Totem was a strategic asset related to the future of their civilization, and it was countless times more important than the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. Thus, the federation could only temporarily suspend the matter of the scepter at that time, targeting the Crimson Dynasty and the Black Star Army.

However, Hila's problem now allowed the federation to see another chance at obtaining a deal with Black Star.

"We need more leverage." Hades' eyes flashed. "For example… Hila herself."

Everyone felt their hearts stir.

"You mean, we should capture Hila alive and use her to deal with Black Star, exchanging her for undoing the seal of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter." The Chief Elder sighed before beginning to feel as though this was a headache inducing matter.

This plan would not require any killing, no incurring of Black Star's wrath, and it would even allow them to unseal the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. The plan also seemed easy enough, a good idea.

If this plan succeeded, the federation would earn the most, being able to utilize the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, giving the green hat to the Arcane Church.

Though, it was not their problem whether the Arcane Church profited or lost.

It's better to die without friends than to die poor!

To understand this concept, just look at Hades who suggested this idea.

Tsk, what a lowlife.

The Chief Elder coughed. "Since Hila's skills specifically deal with living life forms, the best class to take her down would be a Mechanic. Mechanic Emperor, would you…"

"I have no interest in bullying a new Beyond Grade A," Manison said.

As a Mechanic surrounded by plenty of armor, he was naturally unafraid of Hila's ability to deplete his life span, but he was not willing to bully a newcomer. This old man could not wait for more newcomers to appear, so why would he go and suppress them?

"Alright then, someone else go." The Chief Elder could only shake his head in resignation. They did not have the ability to force Manison.

One of the Beyond Grade As helplessly said, "To have so many people targeting a single person, the last person to have this treatment was probably EsGod."

"She can only blame her life for this."

The free competition zone was currently chaotic, and the movement of the local tyrants such as the Black Star Army were all closely monitored. Very quickly, news of the spat between Gorutan and the Black Star Army spread.

Planet Phiri, which was chosen by the Black Star Army, had been destroyed, and they could only choose a new stronghold, but Gorutan did not get off lightly either. He had lost quite a few subordinates, so they counted it as a tie.

Hila and Gorutan's battle was considered a normal result by all means. She would never have been the opponent of a pinnacle Beyond Grade A, but Gorutan suffering an injury was not something any newcomer could cause, so many organizations secretly raised the value of Hila's combat power in their files, thinking that she could very well be the strongest person among the recent newcomers.

As for Hila's ability, the intelligence was only circulated among the three universal civilizations and a few advanced civilizations. The rest of the world remained blissfully ignorant, unaware of the violent undercurrents.

After the fight between the Black Star Army and Gorutan, the rest of the foreign organizations that had conflicts no longer curbed themselves, all beginning to fight over the scarce resources.

This battle resulted in a rapid increase in armed conflicts, and the law and order crumbled like an avalanche. However, there were still many empty areas, and there was much room for exploration in this fourth exploration phase. Thus, the conflict was kept at a manageable state, far from the intensity in Han Xiao's previous life.

As for the guilds that had broken away from the army, they had also begun to exert their independence, joining in the competition as formal organizations!

Somewhere within the Emerald Star Cluster, a small fleet was slowly inching forward, its outer armor engraved with various emblems of organizations, with some of them being emblems of the guilds. After completing their registration through the army, they would be able to customize their own organization name and logo, and the guilds would naturally use their own emblems.

This fleet included the guilds from the well-known first tier clubs such as Long Sky, Rivervale and Thunder Storm, acting together.

In the version currently, the efficiency of making money for the players was much higher, and if they gritted their teeth to save money, buying an ordinary spaceship was not a problem. The first-tier guilds had even more funds, so even with the suicidal price of 130% of the market rate that Han Xiao gave, many of the players still managed to purchase small spaceships.

At this moment, the core members of the various guilds were gathered on the battleship of Long Sky for a meeting. Many of the Pro League players were present.

"We're not far from Planet Harker. Our estimated time of arrival is in half an hour. Let's go through our plans," the President of Sky Territory, the official guild of the Long Sky Club, Jade Green Sky said.

Twinkle Fried Rice recalled the memorandum and recited, "Planet Harker should have sufficient resources and is currently occupied by seven small organizations. There are three financial groups, two private armed forces, and two Star System level civilization gathering teams present. They are unable to drive each other out, so they can only try to snatch as much as they can. Our objective is to strike a deal with the financial group and establish a resource base on this planet, laying the foundation for construction."

"The most important thing now is how to negotiate with them," Sleepy Winter said.

"Leave that to me," Maple Moon replied. "I know what to say."

Everyone nodded, giving her a few words of encouragement.

With Han Xiao's secret hints and guidance, the players in the army were the first to understand that the focus of this version was to build up the reputation of their own organizations and interact with the NPC organizations.

After experiencing a few versions, the players were already aware that the actions of the NPCs were no different from real people. Every word and action would trigger a different reaction and response, and the freedom of this open world was off the charts. Thus, they had to use proper words on the negotiation table, and the higher one's charm value, the easier it would be to negotiate.

In the guilds, there would definitely be someone who was good at negotiating. As someone who loved games for the plot, Maple Moon was keen to interact with the NPCs.

The new style of the army had given them the status of a semi-independent unit, and coupled with such freedom, these guilds had begun to exert their initiative, proactively analyzing intelligence and looking for opportunities.

While it was safe to follow a large organization, their movements would be restricted, so players had the mentality that they would rather be leading a small group than be nobodies in a large force.

This was exactly the situation that Han Xiao wanted to see. He had released many incentives in the form of missions to encourage independent movement, trying to spread the army players to penetrate more sites. This would allow for an expansion of advantages and the tapping of new interests in different territories rather than sticking by him.

These guilds acted in concert with each other to increase their strength. Instead of following the majority, they chose to head to Planet Harker to compete against the smaller forces, precisely to maximize their own advantages.

At present, most of the players in the guilds were at Grade B, which could be regarded as the backbone of a fighting force. As a subsidiary organization under the Black Star Army, just their name had plenty of influence on the smaller organizations. Borrowing their backer's prestige, they could increase their leverage during negotiations.

After a while, the fleet began to decelerate, and Planet Harker drew closer. There was a scattered defense fleet suspended in outer space, belonging to various organizations.

Seeing the players' fleet, the defense force of Planet Harker activated a defensive position, initiating a communication application.

Frenzied Sword patted Maple Moon's shoulder and whispered, "They're all yours."

Maple Moon spat out a breath of air, blowing a raspberry as a form of warming up, eager to try it out.

"Relax, watch how I fool with them!"

Chapter 1021: The Rise of the Players

Maple Moon answered the communicator. A person resembling a mercenary appeared on the screen, alert and evidently curious.

"This is the armed forces convoy of the New Moon Financial Group. I'm Commander Feldman. Who are you?"

Hearing this, Maple Moon felt her heart leap with joy.

The guilds had investigated the current status of Planet Harker in advance, and seven organizations occupied the planet and were competing with each other, guarding the planet in different directions. They did not want more people to further divide their resources. If one encountered the armed forces or Star System civilizations, then the difficulty of negotiation would increase.

Having met a financial group off the bat, things would become a lot simpler.

Of course, with the current capabilities of the players, it was impossible for them to investigate such situations alone. All their intelligence was derived from the Black Star Army, allowing them to query for real-time intelligence in the Flickering World. This was an excellent resource provided to the players.

Maple Moon calmed herself and said, "This is an armed force consisting of Sky Territory, Thunder Storm, Rivervale…"

Feldman felt confused.

He had never heard of all these organizations before, nor did he recognize the emblems the players used.

He had no idea where this little ragtag group came from…

Feldman shook his head, speaking in a deep tone. "Planet Harker currently does not welcome any external influences. Please leave immediately before we take drastic measures."

"You're mistaken. Our objective is not to set up camp on Planet Harker. You can treat us as mercenaries." Maple Moon took out the prepared speech. "Didn't you post a recruitment notice on the Flickering World Regional Channel? We plan to work with your financial group as a hired armed force."

Feldman felt surprised.

Right now, what the Flickering World had in spades was open positions. Practically all the organizations were desperately trying to recruit armed forces, and those high levelled organizations were the most attractive. Small financial groups like them almost had no chance to recruit anyone in the free competition zone, so he did not expect someone to answer their call.

However, why did they not contact the financial group in advance, instead just turning up? They could not be an unsavory group, right?

Feldman thought about it, shaking his head.

He estimated that the combat strength of this group would not be too good as well, so he did not hold much hope. However, every little bit of strength mattered now.

After a pause, he casually said, "Alright, first tell me about your battle situation, then we'll consider if you're worth hiring."

Maple Moon was so excited. She had to clench her fists together. Acting composed, she replied, "Alright, our joint armed forces have a total of 7,000 Supers, of which 5,800 are Grade B…"

"Hold up, what‽"

For a moment, Feldman thought that he had hearing problems.

7,000 Supers was not a lot by any means, but to actually have 5,800 Grade Bs…

Even the whole of Planet Harker did not possess so many Grade Bs!

From the perspective of Han Xiao, Grade B was only good for cannon fodder, but in the eyes of many of the galactic organizations, a Grade B Super was the core force, enough to even serve as the main combat members.

Back when Han Xiao was still roaming as a mercenary, Grade Bs were already considered experts, great figures in the eyes of the masses.

Even the mercenary groups such as the Purple Gold Army and Sky Ring, before being brought under Han Xiao's wing, never had more than a few hundred Grade Bs. If not for the two Calamity Grades holding the fort, their battle strength was negligible!

Are they trying to lie to me‽ Feldman's expression was full of disbelief.

Because guilds such as Rivervale and Long Sky had large numbers of peripheral members, gathering thousands of people was an easy task. The majority of players had also advanced to Grade B when Version 4.0 opened, and those who had not yet reached that grade were newcomers or small-time players.

Maple Moon pretended to ignore him, continuing to speak. "At the same time, we're a subsidiary organization under the Black Star Army. We were once the Immortals troops under Black Star…"

"Hold up some more! You said that you guys are under the Black Star Army, and the Immortal troops at that‽"

Feldman began to tremble, his mouth agape.

Was this not a group of ragtag mercenaries? Why did they have such huge origins, belonging to Black Star‽

His first response was to think that he had been scammed!

In his eyes, Black Star could be considered a galactic giant, unattainable by mortals. The New Moon Financial Group that he worked for could not even be compared to a fart from Black Star himself, but the Immortal troop from the Black Star Army was their famed trump card, so why would they even run over to accept their employment?

Feldman immediately accessed the public channel of the Black Star Army to check on the information of these organizations. What he saw gave him a huge scare!

Sky Territory, Thunder Storm, Rivervale, and the other organizations mentioned were really semi-independent affiliated organizations of the army. Their members were all made up of Immortals, and they had been registered not too long ago!

On Maple Moon's side, the other professional players such as Frenzied Sword were observing Feldman's expression of shock as though he was a frog in a well, and they screamed out internally with pride, feeling greatly satisfied innately.

Just mentioning the name of Black Star made the other party fall into a state of shock.

It's good to have a backer!

Because of the unparalleled realism within the game, the players could deeply immerse and interest themselves. Seeing the reactions of the NPCs often gave them a sense of accomplishment.

Thus, everyone wished to borrow the prestige of the Black Star Army to improve their own influence. In a general employment relationship, the mercenaries would not have the chance to divide the resources within the planet, but with the name of Black Star, the conditions could be re-negotiated.

The choice to not monopolize the planet, instead cooperating with other organizations, was due to their lack of funds. Mining equipment required money and manpower. If one found an NPC organization to cooperate with, such costs could be avoided. While the players had high personal strength, the NPC organizations still had the advantage in numbers. Thus, it brought out the players' sincerity in wanting to cooperate.

Seeing that the other party was not responding, Maple Moon could not help but cough loudly. She urged, "How is it? Do you think we're good enough? If you do not require our services, we can leave."

Feldman snapped out of his daze as though he was woken up from a dream and anxiously shouted, "No, no, to employ you is our honor. Please follow my instructions to descend. I'll inform my superiors immediately!"

The moment he spoke, notifications appeared on the interfaces of all the players present, and when they glanced over at them, they gave a small cheer.

"It's here. The mission has activated!"

"Damn, beautiful work!"

"Haha, I just knew it. This is the way to play the game!"

What appeared on their interface was not an employment mission but a faction mission labelled [Seizing Planet Harker]. The notification indicated that they could choose a faction and aid them in obtaining dominance over the planet. This was a sort of triggered storyline mission.

Very quickly, the player's fleet followed Feldman to land on a certain base on the surface of Planet Harker. When the players disembarked from their spaceships, they saw a group of officers wearing the uniforms of the New Moon Financial Group waiting, looking excited and nervous.

As the players stepped forward, the people from New Moon Financial Group came up to welcome them. The leader walked up to Maple Moon, stretching out his hand, appearing warm and full of enthusiasm.

"Hello, I'm the Head Supervisor responsible for New Moon Financial Group at Planet Harker. My name is Smedix. On behalf of Planet Harker, welcome."

"Your name… is quite unique."

Maple Moon's mouth twitched as she held back her smile, shaking hands with him.

Smedix did not understand what she meant, but he did not take it to heart either, warmly continuing. "You came at a good time. We're in dire need of mercenaries now, but I have a small question before that… Your application, is it the Black Star Army's intention, or is it your own?"

"Both." Maple Moon's answer was ambiguous. This question was not within what she expected, but it seemed to be more beneficial toward their side.

"Then let's talk about the employment cooperation. Do you have any conditions?" Smedix asked.

Maple Moon exchanged a glance with the rest, and nodding, she spoke up. "We hope that this will not be a simple employment. In addition to remuneration, we would like to cooperate in the development of Planet Harker."

"Cooperative development?" Smedix's heart jumped as he thought of many things.

If the Black Star Army wished to occupy Planet Harker, with this group as the vanguard, there was no way the New Moon Financial Group could even compete against them.

Right now, Planet Harker could hold seven organizations mainly because everyone there was small in scale. If faced with a bigger organization, there would be no need to fight. All they needed was to tidy up their items, obediently cleaning up the planet to hand it over.

But Smedix thought that cooperation might not be a bad thing, if he was able to hold onto Black Star's thigh… er… leg hair.

Currently, the strongest entities on Planet Harker were the two Star System civilizations, but because this planet was only their resource collection point, the other organizations could still hold on. If the entire force of the Star System civilization came over, the financial groups would most likely have to move. However, with the protection of this group of Immortals, this was equivalent to borrowing the protective talisman that was the Black Star Army.

With the competition growing more intense, there might even be other organizations that would come over to Planet Harker. A strong backer would prove beneficial to them in the long run.

Thinking such, Smedix made the decision, gravely nodding. "No problem, we will formulate the specific terms here before passing it for your review. Is that ok?"

"Okay." Maple Moon nodded in return. She was only in charge of the negotiations and did not understand anything about contract law. For that area, their club would have specific talents in such areas. Their club president also had some knowledge on contract law, and in the worst-case scenario, they could search for a template on the quantum network or spend some money for Phillip to check it.

This was the advantage of being in the army. As long as they had money, they could obtain any service. Being rich was certainly the strongest ability one could have.

The New Moon Financial Group vacated an area to serve as the stronghold for the guilds. The next day, both sides arrived at a consensus and signed a formal cooperation agreement.

After signing the contract, the players immediately triggered the corresponding employment missions. Currently, the bulk of their mission lists were related to Planet Harker. Some were triggered by themselves, and others through the New Moon Financial Group. There were also some milestone-related missions released by Han Xiao to incentivize the players, such as 'Find a planet to build a resource collection point', which encouraged players to expand their reach like dandelions.

The same matter provided them with so many different types of missions, and if they could complete all of them, the players would obtain a huge reward with half the effort.

After the contract was finalized, Maple Moon and the others approached Smedix to offer their suggestions.

"Since we're partners, but you have not publicized our origins, the other organizations do not yet know of our identity and strength. This is our advantage, so I hope we can take action immediately to carry out a raid, snatching the resource base."

Smedix thought about it and nodded. "You're right. Where are you looking at?"

Maple Moon opened the virtual screen showing Planet Harker and selected a few places. All of them were the resource bases of the other organizations on Planet Harker.

"Y-you guys want to attack so many at once‽" Smedix stuttered.

"Relax, we're confident." Hao Tian smirked.

During an interstellar battle, a fleet was important, but the resource bases were on the surface, so Supers were the main focus. Since the entire number of Grade Bs on Planet Harker did not even match up to their numbers, there should not be a problem with battles on multiple fronts.

"… Then we'll follow your plan. My troops will do their best to cooperate." Smedix secretly decided to hold tightly onto this leg hair that he had been offered.

The Ursa Civilization was a Star System civilization that lived on the blackhole edge. It had also participated in the competition within the Flickering World, with one of their collection teams being part of the seven on Planet Harker. They were the most powerful and had established several resource bases on the planet.

At the edge of a canyon sat a base with various hovering equipment rising and descending into the canyon to mine resources. A large number of Ursa soldiers were within the base, patrolling around, and artillery and traps were arranged in the periphery, providing a strong fortified defense.

Somewhere in the base, two people in officer uniforms walked slowly as they inspected the base.

"I heard that a small fleet arrived on Planet Harker yesterday, and it was the New Moon Financial Group that received them," one of them, a bulky figure, said. He was the Head Supervisor of this base, a mid tier officer of Ursa, named Hundejab.

The other was the captain of the Super unit that was stationed at the base. He was a Grade B Super and was specially recruited to the Flickering World. He pursed his lips and casually remarked, "It should be reinforcements from the New Moon Financial Group. The defense captured their fleet markings, and there are no files on those organizations in the Mercenary Alliance. It's likely that they are some small shrimps."

Because the players' guilds were affiliated to the army, Han Xiao did not register them with the Mercenary Alliance. His intention of obscuring it was to turn the army into a platform of a similar nature to the Mercenary Alliance. Thus, their files could only be found on the army's website, and no one knew of the players' guilds. The Ursa team did not discover their origins, instead thinking that they were small-time mercenaries.

"Since the New Moon Financial Group has reinforcements, there will definitely be movements," Hundejab coldly said.

"You're saying that their target is us?"

"Impossible," Hundejab flatly replied. "The New Moon Financial Group does not have the guts."

"Are you that sure?"

Hundejab had a calm expression. "Of course! This is the strongest defensive base here. Not only does it have a lot of defensive measures, but there are also more than seventy Grade B Supers stationed here. If the New Moon Financial Group is smart, they will not attack here even if they had the courage to…"

Boom!

Before he finished speaking, an explosion rocked the base, and the duo staggered.

"What's happening!" Hundejab was shocked, immediately boarding a hovering vehicle to observe the situation.

He only saw a large number of anti-gravity vehicles marked with the New Moon Financial Group emblem approaching them at rapid speed. The vehicles were equipped with shields and electromagnetic kinetic weapons, allowing them to ignore the mines placed in the outer area and exchange fire with the base defenders.

The alarm within the base suddenly rang out. "Enemy attack! All personnel, man your posts!"

Hundejab was furious. "The New Moon Financial Group actually dared attack me‽"

He had just made a prediction, and the next second, the enemies had arrived! His expression was ugly, and by the side, the Super saw his commander's expression and did not provoke him further, simply saying, "I'll bring the Supers to meet the enemy."

"Good!" Hundejab gravely nodded.

The Captain of the Supers left, leaving only Hundejab on the scene. He coldly gazed at the approaching enemy forces and regained his confident image.

"Since you dare to target me, I'll give you a painful lesson!"

Very quickly, the New Moon Financial Group arrived outside the base, and the ground forces of the base also took the initiative to advance and attack with their Supers to halt the advance.

As both sides exchanged fire, they grew closer at a rapid speed. When they were about to collide, an abrupt change occurred!

The ground vehicles leading the New Moon Financial Group suddenly opened their doors, and figures jumped out one after another. There were about a hundred of them, and as they rolled on the ground with the inertia, their bodies suddenly swelled into disproportionate sizes. Their speed increased sharply, and they pierced into the ground forces of the base.

Boom!

These biochemical aberrations withstood the artillery fire with their thick skin and flesh, and their huge arms seemed to possess endless power, sweeping through all the vehicles in their path.

The 'Black Star Army Badge: Evolution' that was derived from the Ovitan Badge was also marked with a thirty-percent discount, allowing the guilds to purchase a large number of them and distribute them to the players.

A hundred of these players entered the [Evolution Limit: Aberration] state and instantly tore the ground troops of the base into pieces!

Hundejab's expression sank, and he passed down a command. "Let the Supers attack and deal with these monsters!"

On the frontline, the Captain of the Supers led thousands of men onto the battlefield, most of them Grade C and Ds. At the front of the unit were the dozens of Grade Bs as the vanguard.

On the other side, the New Moon Financial Group also launched a charge with their thousands of players.

A medium-scale Super battle was about to break out, and seeing the inferior number of players, Hundejab smiled.

"Their supers only number a quarter of ours. They're finished!"

Just as he spoke, both sides clashed. But the result was completely contrary to his expectations. His eyes almost popped out in disbelief!

The thousands of players broke out with Grade B combat strength and instantly took the upper hand, killing their enemies freely!

Seeing this scene, Hundejab's expression changed into one of despair!

"How could there be so many Grade B Supers‽"

Chapter 1022: Demons

In a small-scale surface war without the participation of any Calamity Grades, thousands of Grade Bs were enough to dominate a battle.

While the Ursa Civilization had four to five times the number of Supers in their base, in front of the suicidal players, they were just sacrifices, exploding into fireworks of dazzling light and heat as the aberrations imploded, finally merging into a whole, a pile of ashes.

The extreme evolution and self-imploding tactics were the two trump cards of the players. In their eyes, their life was just for that second of brightness and illumination, transforming themselves into matches and burning to warm others. This act was so 'noble' that it would literally make people cry.

The large number of Grade Bs in this battle provided the players with an overwhelming advantage, and with the help of the New Moon Financial Group, there was no suspense left in this battle. The resource base was quickly captured by the players, and Hundejab and the officers in the base were captured alive.

At this moment, the base was filled with explosions, and the ground and the structures had scorch marks. Some of the New Moon Financial Group and the guilds were clearing the battlefield, counting their loot. At the center of the base, Hundejab and the group of captives squatted there, holding their heads with both their hands as they were surrounded by a group of players.

"How is it? Should we get rid of all these people?" The Vice-Captain of Rivervale, Evil Sword, turned his head to look at Frenzied Sword.

"Hmm…" Frenzied Sword sighed. "Let me think about it."

The joint forces of these guilds attacked a separate resource base, and this particular raid was led by Frenzied Sword of Rivervale.

When they were fighting, they obviously did not care about the people, but now that they had defeated the enemy, it was time for the professional players to farm experience. This was one of the missions of the guild to provide resources for the professional players.

Maple Moon glanced at Hundejab and the others, blinking. "Should I first ask them for their names and see if it triggers a mission?"

Hearing this, the rest had agreed to her plan.

Maple Moon approached the group of captives, asking, "Who here is the commander?"

The group started to stir, but the majority seemed as though they were unwilling to betray their superior. However, Hundejab gritted his teeth and said, "I'm in charge of this base. The name's Hundejab. You are the forces employed by the New Moon Financial Group, right? What are your origins‽"

His shock had still not subsided. There were thousands of Grade B supers! Where did they appear from‽ They disintegrated the line of defense that he felt was so solid, so how could they be an unknown organization in the mercenary world!

Maple Moon smiled secretly but pretended to be nonchalant as she replied, "We're the Rivervale Guild, previously part of the Immortal troop from the Black Star Army. We're currently an affiliated armed force to the army.

Ka!

This news struck like a thunderbolt on a sunny day. Hundejab and the rest were stunned, their expressions filled with disbelief. He did not even expect to hear the name of 'Black Star' from these people.

The New Moon Financial Group actually got acquainted with the Black Star Army‽

Hundejab had an expression of shock, and his mental state was in a disarray. He initially still had some anger in his heart, but it all dissipated in a flash, only leaving behind feelings of panic.

His first thought was to think it unreal, but when he thought back to the anomalous situation on the battlefield, he had a sudden realization.

No wonder it seemed that some of them had died but reappeared. He did not understand it at the start, but he figured out that if they were originally the famous Immortal troops of the Black Star Army, then their origins were not falsified!

"Y-you guys…"

Facing the influence of Black Star, Hundejab could not remain stubborn, and the confidence he harbored from being part of a Star System Civilization was completely crushed.

If even he was so befuddled, then the other captives were worse, trembling all over in fear.

Maple Moon thought for a while and felt that she had to voluntarily trigger the mission. Thus, she asked, "Is there anything you want us to do for you?"

Hearing this, everyone froze in shock and despair.

We're finished. They're now asking us for our last wishes!

Feeling the atmosphere fill up in fear, Hundejab gritted his teeth and turned back to shout, "None of you should be begging them for mercy! Dying on the battlefield is our honor!"

Even while he was battling, he had psychologically prepared to sacrifice himself. At this point, his intention resurfaced.

Maple Moon scratched her head and honestly said, "Why don't you all just start begging me? Maybe I'll let you all go."

"Dream on! Even if I'm faced with death, I will not let you fool with us!"

"Uh… are you really not going to struggle? It might actually work."

"Devil! Demon! You're all delusional!"

And thus, a scenario began that left the New Moon Financial Group's members in utter shock. They witnessed the captives begging to be put to death at all costs, while the capturers were the ones persuading them to beg for mercy.

However, at this time, the New Moon Financial Group saw quite a few expressions of conflicting emotions on the captives' faces. Immediately, their bodies shivered as they guessed what the Immortals were aiming at.

The Immortals were actually trying to divide the enemy… what a scary bunch!

Because not everyone was as stubborn as Hundejab, there were a few that stood up, and under the angered glare of Hundejab, they began to plead for mercy.

Looking at her interface, Maple Moon saw the mission [XX's Plead] appear. The conditions were that they would obtain a small amount of experience if they allowed them to go free. She turned to look at Frenzied Sword. "Should we do this mission or not?"

"While the experience is low, it's still something. Just do it." Frenzied Sword nodded.

Hearing that, Maple Moon let those that pleaded move to the side, which prompted even more captives to begin begging for mercy, seeing that there was a precedent.

Some of them triggered the missions, but some of them could not. Thus, the players appeared to be choosing vegetables at a market, selecting the captives to put aside.

"The rest of them don't have any missions available; do it."

Without any hesitation, the players turned into executioners, killing those stubborn people such as Hundejab and the elites. Although most of them were weak, they had bonuses because of their identities. The experience obtained through killing them was reasonable, and this would even increase their final rating for the Planet Harker mission.

By the side, the spectating New Moon Financial Group members avoided looking at the players. "This is too cruel…"

If it were them, they would not dare provoke the Ursa Civilization and would probably have released all of them. However, the Black Star Army was actually so cruel, killing them without batting an eye.

Indeed, all those from the Black Star Army were dangerous characters!

Seeing this scene, those captives who had begged for mercy got nervous. Frenzied Sword allowed them to leave as and when they wished, and only then did they scramble out of the base.

The professional players then turned to their interfaces.

The moment this group of captives had run out of the base, the mission of pleading for mercy had been marked as completed.

"The mission requirements were so relaxed? Oh, then again, it's just a small mission." Frenzied Sword scratched his head suspiciously. Turning to look at the rest of the players, they nodded.

Barely three minutes later, the released captives were all gathered once again in the square, their faces full of disbelief.

You released us, then captured us again. What is the meaning of this‽

"Let's try again." Maple Moon coughed awkwardly. "Is there anyone who wants to plead for mercy?"

Her tone was sincere, but in the ears of the rest around her, it sounded full of ridicule and sarcasm.

Turns out, you were just fooling with us!

Can you not‽

You can kill me but not humiliate me. If we had known, we would have followed Hundejab and the rest to choose death on the spot!

The majority chose to remain silent, but a small portion broke through their limits and begged once again for the second time. However, this time, there was no sign of any missions appearing on the players' interface.

"Seems like it's a one-off mission." Evil Sword shook his head, appearing a little regretful.

"I expected that. If this was repeatable, there'd be something wrong." Maple Moon rolled her eyes.

Frenzied Sword also sighed before drawing his blood-stained sword. "Since that's the case, there's no other choice."

Thirty seconds later, the group once again got their hands on another bunch of experience.

The professional players wiped their hands clean, joining the ranks of players cleaning up the battlefield.

They left behind the group of New Moon Financial Group members, who had witnessed the entire frightening process of 'fooling the captives before killing them'. All of them had chills in their hearts, and their bodies were frozen in shock.

To give someone hope then break it so ruthlessly, sinking them into absolute despair, those Immortals were just too vicious!

Many of them involuntarily shivered, and looking at each other, they came to a similar conclusion.

They absolutely could not provoke this group of madmen. They were demons!

…

The several groups each attacked a base, all of which ended in victory. Such a record alarmed the other six organizations on Planet Harker, leading to them hurriedly inquiring about the origin of the reinforcements invited by the New Moon Financial Group.

Since the attack had succeeded, there was no need to keep it a secret. The background of the players was soon revealed, and after verifying it, the other organizations were all frightened.

Black Star Army? F*ck your mom, this is someone we cannot afford to provoke!

Not only was their background frightening, the combat strength of this group of Immortals was even more terrifying. With over five thousand Grade Bs, there was nowhere on Planet Harker they could not go to!

The greater one's name, the longer the shadow cast. Once this news got out, coupled with their battle records, three of the organizations immediately retreated. They felt that this was a hopeless scenario, and thus, they gave up on Planet Harker, recalling all their resource bases.

The remaining three were the two Star System Civilizations as well as another financial group. They were not willing to give up Planet Harker, so they only responded by reducing the bases and shrinking the area of their troops, taking a defensive stance.

However, the players did not take any action to advance and attack immediately. Instead, with the help of the New Moon Financial Group, they occupied the resource bases that they had attacked, resuming the collection of resources.

In one of the largest bases, the core players of the bigger guilds such as Long Sky, Rivervale, and Thunder Storm were standing in front of a warehouse door. Watching the batches of resources being sent in by the transport vehicles, the eyes of the players all turned into the symbol of Enas.

"This is an endless stream of gold!" Jade Green Sky exclaimed with an expression of joy. "Our guild has obtained another huge but stable income channel, and our financial situation has finally improved."

"It seems that this method of gameplay is indeed correct." Hao Tian calmly nodded, silently calculating the amount of equipment this sum could be exchanged for.

Everyone was in a good mood, and the majority of the players looked forward to earning more money.

There was no way about it. While the army sold things at a low price, the follow-up consumption was high. Weapons needed to be strengthened, ammunition resupplied, mechanical suits repaired, the Evolution badges recharged, and so on. That all cost Enas!

Their purses were all sucked dry by the sleazy Black Star Army. The players did not lack much, but they sure as f*ck lacked money!

Since the guilds had chosen to establish their base camps in the army's area, these core players naturally chose to head to the free competition zone to establish a bridgehead, complete missions, and earn more money. Right now, they were getting closer to the right track.

In the eyes of many of the players, their bright future seemed to be waving to them.

…

The guilds established a stronghold on Planet Harker, and the guilds of the other players also found their own opportunities, spreading their leaves and blooming within the Emerald Star Cluster.

After Planet Phiri was destroyed, Hila had found another planet to serve as a stronghold, and she was also participating in the trend of free competition. Right now, most people were actively opening up their maps to occupy mines, and Gorutan also did not have time to find Hila to create trouble.

The player guilds that were affiliated with the army slowly spread within the Emerald Star Cluster. Now that the actions of the Black Star Army were monitored, this movement was discovered by many other organizations.

Many of the organizations were quite curious about the situation in which the Immortals troops had turned into semi-independent affiliated organizations. They did not know what Black Star was planning, so they decided to just silently watch.

As the Chinese players gradually established their strongholds in the free competition zone, the first batch of foreign players finally arrived in the Flickering World after a long journey. The first batch were the Southeast Asian players, who were based near the Blackhole Edge.

Chapter 1023: The Burning Soul of a Whistle-blower

In the Dawn Star Cluster, one spaceship after another sailed out of the stargate, stepping into the territory of the Flickering World.

The major organizations had long been freely exploring the Flickering World, and those that had just arrived were only tourists, small obscure organizations, and reinforcements.

This fleet consisted mostly of reinforcements from the Blackhole Edge. Its composition was complicated, with armies from Star Cluster and Star System Civilizations, armed forces, financial groups, and even players present.

In the entire universe, the Shattered Star Ring appeared to be an exception in having a player-formed faction. They were all from the Black Star Army. As for the others, their makeup was extremely scattered.

Within the Blackhole Edge, the most powerful player to join in this trip was inside a neutral organization named Nineteen Towers Psionics Association. The organization could be understood as a regional organization of mages and psychics, and one would obtain contribution points within the organization through the provision of magic services. The contribution points would then be exchanged for resources and knowledge, just like a platform for professional exchanges.

In the spaceship, the professional players of the Blackhole Edge gathered together. They were composed of players from different clubs across several countries.

In the International League, the players from Southeast Asia did not have much of a presence, as their results for each season placed them at the bottom. The only impression the audience had of them was that they were not very good in tactical operations. They tended to be reckless, and their fighting style was fierce.

The teams in Southeast Asia that were more popular were the Red Bay Club with Old Yue, the Titan Club with Old Qin, as well as the Archipelago Club in Indonesia. These three were the regulars participating in the International League.

At this moment, the common topic was related to the Pro League.

"There has been no news about the Pro League yet, but the opening of the World Server is likely to cause a change in the competition format, and the mode of qualifying through sub-areas might be cancelled," Venomous Snake, the Captain of the Red Bay Battle Team said.

"If there is no longer a division-based system, it will be difficult for us to qualify." The Captain of the Archipelago Team, Gravel Castle shook his head as he replied with a tragic expression.

The reason they appeared every year was purely based on the division system. In the Blackhole Edge, the weak fought the weak, so without this system, they would not make it into the International League.

"Thus, those of us who come from the same Star Field must now unite and seize the opportunity given to us through the World Server, developing ourselves well," Venomous Snake said.

"This is difficult. The advantage of the Chinese players in the World Server is too huge. We cannot compete against them alone. We can only see if the clubs of the other countries are willing to ally with us."

"Unfortunately, we've already invested too much in our current faction, so we cannot jump ships. Even if we enter the Black Star Army now, we will not be able to win against the local Chinese players. We have to come up with a plan to give us an advantage."

At this time, Venomous Snake narrowed his eyes and muttered, "While we cannot jump ship, we still can utilize the benefits offered by the Black Star Army. The best method would be to allow some guild members to join the Black Star Army and increase their contributions within. They could then purchase a large amount of resources at discounted rates. At the same time, we can get them to monitor the movement of the players in the army, which will be beneficial for us."

"Espionage?" Everyone present shared a look. "This is indeed a good idea, but will this cause us to be targeted by the Black Star Army?"

"What does the business of us players have to do with them?" Venomous Snake was nonchalant. "What we should take notice of is the Chinese players. We need to be careful of them stealing the supplies that we purchase."

"Good, then we shall do it that way!"

Everyone confirmed the battle strategy and buried their heads to discuss the details.

…

The Lesykes Army was a large private mercenary group active around the Blackhole Edge. However, it had an official secret backer—it was the secret military force of the Ursa Civilization. This organization was named after the leader, and right now, the Captain Lesykes had just brought his reinforcements to enter the Flickering World.

In the command room, Lesykes shouted in an excited tone.

"Increase speed. Rush over to the free competition zone as soon as possible."

The Ursa Civilization had many secret mercenary groups under them, so the civilization rarely gave him any missions. Normally, he was only disguised as a normal mercenary, so he attached great importance to this opportunity to acquire some merits.

Initially, he only sent in the advance troops, and he remained in the base camp to monitor the operations of the mercenary group. However, when the Flickering World was officially opened, the players, who had disappeared from the Blackhole Edge for twenty years, came back online.

In every Star Field, the traits of the players were different, so the impressions they left on the local organizations were also different. Due to the scattered population of the players within the Blackhole Edge, their exposure was far from comparable to the players in the Black Star Army. Thus, their threat level was also lower.

However, there were also a large number of local organizations that had noticed the special existence of the players, thinking that they might be the same species as the Black Star Army's Immortal troops. But the problem was that because the players were too scattered, the local organizations were unable to figure out their actual population. Before the players showed their ability to resurrect, they would behave like any other person, making it difficult to distinguish them.

Lesykes was one of the few to notice that the players had reappeared, and he was extremely impressed with these guys who did not seem to fear death. Therefore, he made a personal decision to recruit them en masse.

As it happened, many of the players in the Blackhole Edge were also looking to enter the Flickering World. They hit it off, and he was able to recruit over ten thousand of the players to transport over to the Blackhole Edge as a support force. This would allow him to claim extra credit.

Not long ago, he had received some good news; the Ursa Civilization had fallen into trouble on the front line. One of their collection units was overturned by the Immortals of the Black Star Army, and they desperately required reinforcements. Lesykes felt that he had suddenly become the person who supplied coal during a snowstorm, and he could not help being overjoyed.

This batch of reinforcements is just in time to help the civilization fight against the Black Star Army. Not only that, in the fight with other organizations, they can also use these Immortals to take the advantage. I've made a big contribution this time! Lesykes thought to himself secretly.

…

At the same time, among his fleet, a group of players from the Blackhole Edge stood in front of the porthole, whispering among themselves while enjoying the view of the Flickering World.

"We're almost here. Hurry to the free competition zone. I'm almost dying of anxiety!"

"Look at what missions this mercenary group can do in the Flickering World."

"Stupid, why would you even still follow this mercenary group? There are so many strong organizations in the Flickering World. What's the point of remaining with this tiny organization?"

"Makes sense. When we arrive in the free competition zone, we can kick this mercenary group aside."

Now that the many top-tier organizations were beginning to gather in the Flickering World, why would the players stick with the smaller groups? Only by switching to a stronger advanced faction could they then meet their increasing needs, especially their need for Class Knowledge.

Lesykes, who was full of hope, did not realize that he was being treated as a tool by the players.

The consequences of betraying a strong organization were serious, but for such a small organization like Lesykes', the players did not give a hoot.

The top choice for the average player in the Blackhole Edge would be the three Universal Civilizations or any Beyond Grade A or advanced civilization in the Blackhole Edge, followed by the Black Star Army.

Players in other Star Fields naturally had no sense of belonging to the Black Star Army. Only the benefits and development prospects would move them. In this respect, the Black Star Army was just like a firefly in the night, extremely evident.

Throughout the many versions, the various benefits players of the army received had long been eye-catching for all the other countries. Now that they could finally cross Star Fields, the reputation and appeal of the army from several versions had accumulated to achieve the effect of allowing a large number of ordinary players to be inclined toward Han Xiao.

Among them, the ones that wanted to join the Black Star Army the most were the Mechanic players from the Blackhole Edge!

Due to the difference in planets in Version 1.0, the composition of Supers in each Star Field was also very vast. The most common Class in the Blackhole Edge was the Mage class, followed by Psychics. The overall focus there was more toward the arcane, and the mechanic department only accounted for about twelve percent of the total players in the Blackhole Edge.

In comparison, the Black Star Army was simply like a paradise for Mechanics, and with Han Xiao as the top mentor of the Mechanic Class, there was no need to worry about the lack of Class Knowledge.

In the eyes of these people, one sentence could summarize the meaning of Black Star to the mechanic players.

If the Heavens did not give birth to me, Black Star, then the Mechanics would essentially be fumbling in the dark!

As for the Mechanic Emperor… while it was rumored that he was extremely strong, the players were not too familiar with him. They instead gravitated toward Han Xiao. After all, the Chinese players had forged the route for them, so they knew that Han Xiao was a reliable person.

The group chatted around, and at the edge of this crowd, a player with the ID of Muay Thai as Warning appeared to be alone, looking out the window.

This hidden mission told me that the Lesykes mercenary group is actually an affiliated organization belonging to the Ursa Civilization. I heard from my friend that their Long Sky happened to grab some resources from the civilization and had a conflict, so our group is probably here to serve as reinforcements…

The friend he mentioned was actually a peripheral member of the Long Sky Guild. They had once gotten into a spate on the forums, but they had suddenly realized that the other party also made sense, so they apologized to each other and finally became friends.

With this in mind, a bold idea surfaced in the mind of Muay Thai as Warning, and the soul of the whistleblower started to burn brightly.

If one wishes to jump ship, then they definitely have to present a gift!

…

At the same time, somewhere in the Emerald Star Cluster, a small financial group's exploration fleet docked at a temporary transit station that was constructed by an advanced civilization for a rest. The crew went for some leisure time, only leaving the logistics personnel behind to clean and repair the equipment.

Buzz!

Within the maintenance channel inside the spaceship, two ground crew members wearing protective gear were holding onto maintenance tools, working in front of a complex piece of machinery. Sparks constantly splashed around.

It took a while before they completed their job. Evans took off his hood and wiped his sweat.

He then opened the logistics task list on his wrist, glancing at it, before opening the communication channel to report to his superior.

"Ground Handling Group No. 005 has completed the task. The issue with engine group component T1018 has been eliminated. We will now proceed to sector C0080 for cleaning."

"Received, continue your work. You still have three more tasks to complete."

"Understood."

After finishing his report, he left the communication channel before patting his companion's shoulder. "Let's go to the next area."

His companion, however, waved his hands in frustration. "We just finished our task. What's the hurry? Let's rest for a while."

Evans tried to persuade him. "We're pressed for time today, so we should try to get them done before work ends. It's best not to take a break during working hours, or else we will not be able to finish."

"Then we'll just postpone it till tomorrow. It's not just a one-day stop here." The companion sat down in dissatisfaction. "If you want, you can go on ahead. I'll rest here."

Evans frowned but shook his head and no longer tried to persuade him. He could not control anyone; he just needed to do a good job himself.

He went along the maintenance tunnel by himself, and the figure of his companion soon disappeared, leaving him alone.

The lighting in the maintenance tunnel was dim, with only one light source situated at a large distance away. After walking for a while, Evans suddenly found a red light flashing in front of him. He stopped walking.

"The lights have gone out? Did I see it wrongly?"

Evans found it a little weird. He observed the environment detector, but there was no change. He initially thought it was his eyes playing tricks and walked forward a few more steps.

Buzz!

At this moment, a burst of red lit up his vision. The light source appeared on his side, less than a meter away!

Evans quickly reacted in shock, jumping to the side and tumbling on the ground, holding the welding torch in his hands as he stood up to face the light source.

What greeted him was a bizarre scene of an unknown red light zipping around in the air, constantly moving and leaving a trail of red light behind it. There was a lot of beauty to this scene.

"What is this thing?" Evans showed a wary expression as he secretly took out his communicator, wanting to report this anomaly.

However, the next moment, his eyes blurred as the red light dashed over at an inhumane speed, piercing through his body.

Evans hurriedly looked down but found himself unscathed. Instead, he felt full of energy. His fatigue from working was swept away, and his physical strength was restored.

At this moment, the red light paused before frantically hovering around him.

Evans seemed to have felt an emotion of happiness from this bundle of light, causing him to freeze in shock.

Before he could recover, the light seemed to stop suddenly, and as if pulled by some invisible presence, it suddenly disappeared, leaving Evans standing there with a blank expression.

After a long pause, Evans slapped himself hard.

"Ouch it hurts, I'm not dreaming… It seems like I've finally gone crazy."

Chapter 1024: Jumping Ship

As the fleet passed by the Black Star Army's territory, the aspiring Lesykes was quickly dealt a harsh blow.

When he arrived at Planet Black Gate, the Immortals that he had painstakingly recruited from the Blackhole Edge suddenly broke out in a massive rebellion!

Not only did these players leave the faction, they even took over the spaceships carrying them!

Players in any area were accustomed to maximizing their benefits. Since they had already decided to leave, they would take advantage of the other party. Plus, it would be troublesome to travel without a spaceship. Many players seized control of the spaceships carrying them, leaving the designated fleet route and turning toward the Black Star Army.

Even those few players who were not planning to jump ship immediately were also forced to join in. After all, they were on the same ship, and if they fought and blew up the spaceship, there was no good end for either side.

With so many players in each spaceship, it was impossible to determine the ownership. Most people would only follow the spaceship to the transit station, where they would then scatter and act independently. This was the disadvantage of a lack of a huge faction to rally everyone.

Due to the large number of players rebelling, the total size of Lesykes' army shrank by half, and the loss of the spaceships and supplies within were significant to Lesykes, making him feel as though he was bleeding out.

"Crazy, those guys are crazy! They have no morals at all!"

Within the command room, Lesykes was jumping around in anger.

This sudden incident was completely out of his expectations. He was immersed in his dream of achieving his meritorious service and did not expect this group of players to suddenly stab him in the back.

When they were still in the Blackhole Edge, these Immortals were still pretty law abiding, so why was it that they went all crazy the moment they arrived at the Flickering World?

He found it difficult to understand, and subconsciously, he felt as though this whole thing was a conspiracy, that some organizations had secretly meddled with them. He did not even consider their personal motivations.

After all, Lesykes did not understand the players. In his view, some foul play had to be going on, otherwise there would be no reason for all these players to riot together.

The stolen spaceships quickly dispersed and disappeared off their radar. Thus, Lesykes gave up on the symbolic chase. The strength of the Immortals also gave him some reservations, and with the spaceships having a similar speed, it would be hard to catch up to them. With this area being the territory of the Black Star Army, he dared not draw too much attention.

"*ssholes!"

Lesykes was hurt and angry, and he left a black mark on the files of this group of rebellious players, reducing their credit rating on their resumes.

After completing this matter, he managed to quell his anger somewhat. Upon seeing that half of the Immortals had stayed, he felt a little thankful.

"At least half of them are here. Even if I get less credit, there's still some merit. I didn't make the trip for nothing."

Lesykes, however, no longer dared relax around the players, commanding, "Separate the rest of the Immortals and increase the defenses of each spaceship…"

After this experience, he had his guard up against the players.

However, even with his vigilance, another round of betrayals took place once again when he arrived at the free competition zone. The majority of Lesykes' armed force consisted of the players. Thus, no matter how guarded the rest of the crew were, they were useless in the face of overwhelming numbers. The players had remained up till now just to obtain a free ride to the free competition zone.

The players that he brought from the Blackhole Edge had almost completely gone, and Lesykes almost went mad with anger.

Well done, this daddy here personally ran all the way to escort you guys to the Flickering World, thinking of achieving some merit, but ended up gaining nothing. It's like fetching water using a rattan basket[1]!

The bad news poured in one after another. Lesykes quickly discovered from his intelligence that even with the black marks he left on the players' resumes, there were still top-tier factions that took in these Immortals, the most prestigious being the Black Star Army.

Lesykes found this whole thing a little hard to accept, as though he had been bullied, and his heart was full of grievances!

Dammit, why!

This life is too hard!

What he did not know was that, in a tiny batch of players left behind, there existed people like Muay Thai as Warning, serving as spies and tracking the movements of the fleet, constantly reporting back to the army.

In terms of the attractive force of the factions, the gap between him and the Black Star Army was too large. Even if he could temporarily obtain the players' bodies, he could never obtain their hearts.

…

There was naturally more than one organization that suffered from this massive wave of dissention. After entering the Flickering World, these Blackhole Edge organizations mostly experienced the phenomenon of a large number of players leaving, and the Black Star Army was the main place to go for these players.

The attractiveness of his faction had accumulated and matured over several versions, resulting in this surge in players wanting to join the army. There was no need for Han Xiao to do anything; the manual leek collection job had evolved into a fully automated process.

Within Black Star Palace, Han Xiao glanced at the EXP gauge of his attributes panel, his eyes gleaming.

"This wave of experience has shot up real quick."

His plan to expand the leek plantation had finally begun to take effect, with this first batch of 'foreign leeks' pulling themselves out from the roots to transplant themselves in his plantation.

The players from foreign countries all had their own choices, and only a portion of them would choose to join the army, but even this number was also considerable. Based on his estimation, around 17 – 24% of the total population of players from the Blackhole Edge would join his army, which amounted to millions. Most of them would be ordinary players.

"This is only the first batch. When the players from the other Star Fields come, the size of the army will swell to double or triple of what it is today." Han Xiao was secretly pleased.

There were many newcomers from the newly recruited Southeast Asian players, and they had a high demand for Class Knowledge. It was this new wave of consumption that made Han Xiao's efficiency in harvesting experience soar.

Every time a new batch of newcomers arrived, it was followed by a huge wave of experience.

"I estimate that the Southeast Asian clubs will also infiltrate the army."

Han Xiao secretly smiled. He did not intend to stop them.

He could sell more equipment and supplies, so why not? He could gain quite a bit of income from there, and re-equipping the different countries to allow them to fight against each other was akin to him being a weapons dealer, capitalizing on this business opportunity.

Furthermore, if they wished to enjoy the discount, they would need to have the corresponding rank, which meant that they had to contribute to the army. This could not be achieved in a short amount of time.

"Judging by this speed, I only need a few more waves of players to obtain enough experience to rise straight to level 320." Han Xiao was secretly excited. This was much quicker than his expectations.

As for the large number of players jumping ship from the Blackhole Edge, he had long expected this. The continuous decline in the players' credibility was one of the important factors in establishing their title as the Cancer of the Universe. They never had a good reputation, and this also included the fear and vigilance the outside world felt toward them.

One of the important signs for players to enter the stage of the universe was for the World Server to be launched. Their sense of existence had now greatly increased, which would attract the attention of many organizations, regarding them as a whole entity.

In his previous life, as the players spread chaos, leading to a decline in their overall reputation, it got to the point where some small organizations did not even dare recruit players. The consequence was that the players instead gathered toward the top organizations, switching factions to continue upgrading themselves.

These were all things that Han Xiao had witnessed, and he understood that there was no way he could force the players to remain obedient merely through means of faction welfare. As the players got stronger, they would have more thoughts, and they would become harder to control.

The players would only have attachments toward characters that they were familiar with, and for their own personal development and national war advantages, they would need to plunder for benefits and resources, starting wars.

With the growth of their strength, chaos was inevitable. Thus, Han Xiao had always been committed to developing his own organization. One of those objectives was to deal with this situation.

He also understood that, since the army was now an important target for the players to jump ship to, this situation would soon be discovered by the organizations that were monitoring him, and they would eventually form some speculations of their own.

For the time being, this had little impact on him. Firstly, his position was high enough, as was his strength. Secondly, there were also many players joining the other organizations, so the situation was not too exaggerated as of now. The various organizations would at most feel surprise. However, as more foreign players joined, the special features of the army would become more noticeable, and then the trouble would begin.

As Han Xiao shook his head to clear his thoughts, he inadvertently thought of something else.

"I didn't expect Evans to already come into contact with the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy…"

Not long ago, Phillip, who had been constantly monitoring Evans, had sent back a report, and Han Xiao was able to see the process and confirm for himself that the cluster of red light was likely related to the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. However, this appeared much earlier than the time stated by EsGod's inheritance.

He hypothesized that this was likely just one of the sub-bodies that separated from the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, returning to the universe ahead of time. It could be sent earlier as well as a coordinate marker. Whichever was the case, it was soon dragged back to the Secondary Dimension by the main body, and the Primal Esper Ability Entity had yet to descend.

This also solved one of Han Xiao's doubts. There was no wonder that the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy finally chose Evans as a host, as it turned out that he had come into contact with it well in advance.

The moment the red light passes through a person, a mismatch would cause the person to explode and die. Not only was Evans unscathed, he even got rejuvenated. Thus, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy could confirm that he had the qualification to become a host. He was prepared as backup.

"The date of the birth of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy is getting closer as well. Judging from my current rate of acquiring experience, I should be able to achieve the Promotion to level 320 before it is born."

[1] [Annotation text missing] Back

Chapter 1025: Milkmaid's Promotion—Life Replenishment

A couple of days later, in the outer square of Black Star Palace, the newly arrived batches of players from the Blackhole Edge were looking left and right in curiosity and wonder. Their mixed uniforms and equipment made them look like a group of incompetent soldiers, a stark contrast to the uniform look for the Black Star Army members.

A large number of Southeast Asian players had jumped ship to join the army, and some of them could not wait to enjoy the benefits of being part of the Black Star Army, buying supplies in bulk and accepting the Main Storyline mission of [Flickering World] from the army. The other group were more casual players, and after joining the army, they arrived together at Black Star Palace with the idea of recognizing the future Players' Main City of their faction.

Among them, most of the players were Mechanics. They came to the Black Star Palace with the mentality of performing a pilgrimage.

Because most of the Chinese players were out on missions, with the addition of this new batch of players, the originally silent palace turned lively once more.

"This is the base of the Black Star Army in the Flickering World? It's quite spectacular."

"The space is huge, and the facilities are abundant. Really good stuff."

"Will I be able to meet Black Star?"

The group of players from the Blackhole Edge chattered on, excitedly looking around Black Star Palace, their eyes sparkling.

They had roamed about the universe in the last three versions, but the factions they served could not even be compared to the Black Star Army. Just based on the size, they were not on the same level. Even the mother planets of some Star Cluster level civilizations were not as well built as Black Star Palace. For many of these players, it was their first time setting eyes on such a magnificent location.

"There are a lot of high-levelled NPCs here, a whole bunch of characters with the 'Fatally Dangerous' note."

"If we cause trouble here, we'll definitely be killed, right?"

The majority of the players suppressed their arrogance, not daring to mess around in Black Star's territory.

They were not afraid of the smaller organizations such as the Lesykes Mercenary Group and could behave fearlessly. But in the face of a behemoth like the Black Star Army, they did not dare cause trouble as these organizations had the ability to restrain them.

Among the group were also spies sent in by the Southeast Asian clubs. Because the Black Star Army did not show any bias toward the players, they had smoothly mixed in.

Disregarding the countless screaming players around them, these spies with their own special missions opened the dazzling array of faction stores and mission lists, looking through them.

Having successfully joined, as long as they worked hard to contribute and increase their ranks within the army, they could enjoy more benefits and do more purchasing for their guilds.

Their plan was a success!

At this moment, Hadavy, Feidin, and the rest of the Black Star Guards hurried over, attracting the attention of this group of players.

"Hey, look over there, the famous Black Star Guards!"

"The senior figures of the Black Star Army! I have all their decks, and now I can finally meet them in the flesh."

"Feidin! I love you!"

In the distance, Feidin heard the screams, and he came to a stop. Glancing over, he saw the motley group of Immortals and could only helplessly wave back.

Feidin had a high reputation among the players, and this reputation was not just limited to the Shattered Star Ring.

Since these Blackhole Edge players wanted to join the army, they had done their research beforehand. Furthermore, due to the promotion via Wayne Cards, Feidin was a popular idol in the Black Star Army.

"Why is it that you're so popular? Even those newcomers like you so much." Hadavy was a little salty.

"You will find the answer when you look into the mirror," one of the Black Star Guards murmured.

"…" Hadavy could not come up with a response.

Looking at Hadavy's struggling expression, Feidin could not take it and could only ruefully smile as he patted his shoulder. "Don't worry too much. You're not that ugly."

"… I can't cheer myself up with this."

The entourage of Black Star Guards did not stop to chat with the new players. They quickened their footsteps, disappearing from the players' sights.

At the same time, the eyes of those spies hiding in the crowd flashed.

Some of them not only shouldered the mission of purchasing supplies for their guild, they also had another mission, which was to infiltrate the army and monitor their movements.

While the Southeast Asian clubs did not change factions, the Flickering World contained a multitude of opportunities for them to reach out to top tier organizations. They had also secretly contacted some organizations, of which the most commonly contacted one was the Limitless Financial Group.

Sorokin had a strong interest in the player community. He tried to test out the players from the Black Star Army in the past but had suffered a loss instead. Right now, given that the players from the other Star Fields were grouping in the Flickering World, it was an opportunity for him, and he had arranged some people to contact the Blackhole Edge players.

While he did not have an interface, after a long period of research, Sorokin had also figured out some rules regarding the players. Thus, he specifically looked for those players who did not immediately switch over to join the army to issue employment tasks. The contents were to request for the players to provide information on the movements of the Black Star Army. In particular, he wanted to know Black Star's own movements, and the rewards were generous. While he did not know of the underlying principle, the fact of the matter was, as long as he offered enough money, the players would turn into the best spies.

Using gold to pave the way resulted in many of the Southeast Asian clubs accepting Sorokin's mission, which was equivalent to him having a pair of eyes inside the army.

Sorokin's focus on Han Xiao's movements was intentional. Not long ago, Gorutan had gotten into a conflict with Hila. The federation and the church each had their own thoughts about Hila. As their collaborator, Sorokin had to monitor Han Xiao's movements, providing intelligence for both parties to plan their operations.

Many of the spies glanced at each other, softly exchanging words.

"The Black Star Guards are all present, which means Black Star should also be inside."

"Without seeing him directly, can this still be considered as completing the mission?"

"Should be. The Black Star Guards' responsibility is to protect, so wherever they are, there is a high chance that Black Star will also be there."

…

On the other side, Hadavy and the rest of the Black Star Guards arrived at the core of the palace. They orderly proceeded toward an advanced training room, where a mechanical host bearing Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar took guard at the door. Aurora sat in the middle of the room, spewing out life energy that spread out in a white-gold halo around her. This halo followed her breathing as it fluctuated.

"Army Commander." The group greeted the avatar at the door before turning to look at Aurora.

Hadavy breathed in deeply, feeling his spirits rejuvenate, and exclaimed, "What an intense life energy fluctuation. Her quality seems to have sublimated once again?"

Feidin nodded. "Black Star, is this Aurora's advancement?"

Han Xiao's avatar nodded. "Her accumulated life energy has finally broken through the critical point and brought her a qualitative change in her life level."

Before Version 4.0, Aurora had been close to the threshold of the Calamity Grade. With the extra half year of accumulation, she had finally hit the required amount and broken through.

Watched by the group, Aurora closed her eyes, her eyelashes trembling slightly as the light emitted by the life energy became brighter, gradually filling the entire room.

After a long time, the light was slowly reabsorbed into Aurora, and her body displayed some obvious changes. Her platinum blonde hair swayed slightly even without any breeze present, and every strand seemed to be filled with endless vitality.

Her skin had become smoother and more supple without flaws. The milky white skin revealed a sacred aura, as though she was some exquisite artwork.

Aurora opened her eyes, slowly breathing out. Her breath, filled with the energy of life, seemed to change even the air of the room itself, giving the hard, cold steel of the room a feeling as though one had stepped into the wilderness of nature.

Her advancement was vastly different from most Calamity Grades'. There was no destructive movement; all she required was sufficient life energy, without any bottlenecks along the way.

Standing up, Aurora's eyes revealed some happiness, and she walked up to Han Xiao's avatar before excitedly chattering. "Uncle, I've reached the Calamity Grade. Are there any changes?"

Han Xiao sized Aurora up. Her originally petite and cute looks had transformed into something taller, with a better figure. Her facial features had also changed to be more refined, and the holiness seeping out from within her made others involuntarily feel warm toward her. This was a completely different style compared to the cold, glamorous blade that was Hila.

"You've become prettier," Han Xiao joked. "Other Grade As are called Calamity Grades, but for you, no matter how I see it, there's nothing Calamitous about you. Excellent, I'm proud of you."

Aurora blinked a few times, her heart blooming with joy from the praise. However, as though she recalled something, she suddenly pouted. "Humph, so many flowery words, but you still ran over to my sister and did not personally witness me step into the Calamity Grade."

Han Xiao was helpless about it. He had left Black Star Palace a few days ago, quietly going over to the Emerald Star Cluster to meet Hila.

He was clear that with a sudden influx of players, there would be many more eyes. Thus, it was inevitable that there would be spies monitoring his movements. He had left the Black Star Guards there as a simple misdirection while he went off to the Emerald Star Cluster. He had two reasons for going there; one was to compete for the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy in the near future, and the other was to reduce the risk Hila would face. While his Lord's Avatar could display some strength, it was nowhere near the abilities he displayed with his true body.

However, this caused him to miss the promotion of Aurora.

Han Xiao dryly coughed before exchanging a glance with Feidin.

With Feidin's 'emotional intelligence', even if he could not read anything from the eyes of the machine, he understood what Han Xiao was trying to say. He immediately changed the topic as he asked, "After reaching the Calamity Grade, how much have your abilities changed?"

Hearing that, Aurora rolled her eyes toward Han Xiao before turning to Feidin. She carefully looked within her body before raising her hand to emit a ball of life energy. The intensity was a lot stronger compared to when she was at Grade B.

"My life energy accumulation has increased many times from when I was a Grade B, and my healing powers have further increased. Right now, the same amount of life energy should be three or four times more potent than in the past."

Hearing this, Han Xiao felt a little regret that he was not present, or else he could have tried to find out how much Aurora's 'milk' had improved.

Hadavy could not wait, however. "Let me try it out."

Aurora shot him a side-eye but emitted a beam of life energy that sank into his body.

The next moment, Hadavy's eyes opened wide, and he experienced such great comfort that he moaned uncontrollably.

"Uhhh…"

Han Xiao shivered, almost activating the mute mode out of reflex.

D*mn you, what's with that moan‽

When I first knew you, you were a stubborn battle maniac, so why is it you've fallen to such a depraved state‽

Was your brain beaten to mush by me the past few years‽

Distressing indeed!

"What are you moaning for?" Everyone felt the same chill run up their spine.

Hadavy hastily covered his mouth and only recovered after quite a few seconds. He exclaimed in joy, "So good! I felt as though I relaxed a lot, like a weight had been taken off me somehow!"

Seeing his exaggerated expression, everyone half believed and half doubted him. However, all their doubts vanished once they experienced it for themselves. They stared at Aurora with their mouths agape, as though they were looking at some priceless heirloom.

Aurora turned shy at the stares, whispering, "After I advanced, my abilities seemed to have more functions, such as being able to stimulate the potential of the target and improve their status while accelerating recovery."

"This is indeed true." Feidin nodded. "I feel that my spirit is now more sensitive, and my energy is more lively. Not only that, but her life energy seems to have some soothing ability to placate one's emotions."

Han Xiao was quite surprised, but because his true body was not present, he could only go around and tap on his guards to get their combat information.

In addition to treatment, there were also selective gains for targets of her life energy. The additional ability gave a twenty-percent increase toward the upper limit of one's HP, Energy, and Stamina. There was an overall twelve-percent increase in resistance, a seven to eleven percent range increase for all attributes, and a ten to fifteen percent increase in ability strength. This bonus range should gradually increase as she continued to develop her abilities.

Not only was she a milkmaid, she was also a super strong support character!

At the same time, her life energy was able to appease the mental state, expelling any violent tendencies and calming the target down. It would even eliminate any hostility that the target held toward her and produce a desire to protect her. While her power was extremely lacking in attack power, she had a special protection ability.

In addition, the shelf life of her life energy could now be extended by tens of times. The blood connection between Hila and Aurora also increased, resembling that of quantum connection where they could feel each other's vital signs regardless of distance.

Aurora also had a vague feeling that if she further developed her ability gene chain, she would be able to share her life energy with Hila regardless of the distance. At present, she needed to familiarize herself with the changes in the Calamity Grade.

"Worthy of an S ranked Esper Ability. The higher the state of life, the more features it unlocks." Han Xiao was happy for her.

In the past, Aurora turned into jam too early, so no one knew what would happen if she advanced. Right now, she was giving him a lot of surprises.

At this moment, Han Xiao suddenly had a hypothesis and immediately dragged Feidin and Aurora to the biological laboratory, using them for an experiment.

He got Aurora to repeatedly wash Feidin with life energy, and he withdrew some of Feidin's cells each time, comparing the difference in the cells' basic activity.

Before long, the results of the experiment returned. Comparing the data between each baptism of life energy, Han Xiao could not help but sigh.

"I should have thought of this a long time ago. The abilities of the two sisters are diametrically opposed, so if Hila can rob the life of people, Aurora… can increase one's lifespan!"

The experimental data clearly showed that the later samples all showed some form of weak increase in basic cell activity.

In other words, the more 'milk' one got from Aurora, the longer their life span!

At Grade B, this feature had yet to awaken, and right now, she was only a Calamity Grade. Thus, the effect of life extension was weak, far less than Hila's ability to reap life.

But if she continued to grow, then would she not become an enhanced version of Tripiṭaka's flesh[1]‽

It seemed like he had just gotten his hands on another support treasure…

[1] In the mythology ‘Journey to the West’ featuring Sun Wukong, demons always tried to obtain his flesh as it would give them immortality.Back

Chapter 1026: Leek Field Expansion

"Phillip, destroy all calculation evidence and the experiment report."

"Roger, hum…"

The screen disappeared as Han Xiao waved his hand before he turned to Aurora and Feidin behind him, speaking in a solemn tone.

"This matter is only known to the two of you at the moment. Don't tell anybody else for now, or else there will be trouble. Do you understand?"

"… You're saying that there'll be people like the Germinal Organization's Leader?"

Aurora pursed her lips. The painful memories of her past flashed through her head, and a trace of fear flitted across her face. This, however, was quickly replaced by determination.

She was different from the self in the past. She had Han Xiao and her sister by her side, and she believed that she would not repeat her past mistakes.

"Yes, if word gets out, this will arouse the interest of many of the hegemons of the universe. You'll be dragged into the storm." Han Xiao nodded.

If Hila's ability to reap one's longevity made others fear her, then Aurora's ability would drive all Beyond Grade As crazy. She had the ability to control the entire universe. Most Beyond Grade As wished to extend their life span. Even those species with naturally long life spans were no exception. For example, if EsGod was still roaming around, he would not have spared no quarter to seize Aurora's power. This priority would have been even higher than the Evolutionary Totem.

Not only the Beyond Grade As, even the advanced civilizations would be tempted. With Aurora entering the Calamity Grade, she had a high efficiency in the generation of life energy. Most likely, they would not treat her like the Germinal Organization had treated her, but they would put her under house arrest, with her only job being to produce more life potions.

In this way, he would also stand at the cusp of the storm, facing the covetous gazes of many Beyond Grade As. Thus, he had to have strength that far outstripped his current self in order to suppress the greed in the hearts of others. Aurora's ability was a double-edged sword, so Han Xiao did not intend to disclose Aurora's information before he reached a higher level.

Feidin nodded and agreed. "Relax, I've always regarded Aurora as my sister, and I will not leak the news."

Han Xiao left them with some more instructions before sending the two off. He remained in the room alone, sighing to himself.

After Aurora entered the Calamity Grade, her connection to Hila had improved, becoming akin to a symbiotic relationship.

Now that Aurora had just advanced, she still needed time to familiarize with her abilities. When she awakened her new ability to treat Hila remotely, it would be very scary to face Hila.

In his previous life, because Hila lost Aurora early, without the other end of the symbiosis, she could only rampage in the cold universe alone. Right now, while Hila had not yet embarked on an endless killing spree and her growth rate was slower than in her past life, with this milkmaid Aurora that ignored distance, Hila's combat power would far exceed that of her past life.

"I'm afraid Hila will catch up to me in terms of tank-ability…" Han Xiao was helpless. Hila had unlimited uses of the Aurora Character Summon Card.

The Super High Risk Esper Abilities were all overpowered, and the two sisters could even form perfect coordination and soul resonance, which was terrifying. Only mental and spatial abilities could possibly restrain the sharing of life between the two.

Thinking about it, Han Xiao opened the communicator, sending a message to Ames, telling her about the news of Aurora entering the Calamity Grade.

…

In the outer space above Planet Aquamarine, Floating Dragon Island remained. Ames did not participate in the competition in the Flickering World, choosing to stay in the Shattered Star Ring. She wished for Floating Dragon to develop in a low-key manner, not chasing after fame and fortune. Such was the nature of a salted fish, stiff and unmoving.

While she did not participate in the lively trend, Ames was still updated about the Flickering World. Han Xiao knew that Ames enjoyed having fun, so he shared first-hand information with her every day, telling her what was happening in the Flickering World daily to satisfy her curiosity. Since then, regularly checking Han Xiao's news had become a daily necessity for Ames.

In her bedroom within the palace, Ames leaned against the headboard of her bed, condensing a small sphere using her force field to nudge at the giant white bear lying on the floor beside her, as though teasing a cat with a stick. It was obviously a fierce creature, yet in front of her, it appeared extremely obedient, rolling livelily around the floor.

When Ames moved into Planet Aquamarine, Aurora had placed all the pets she raised on the planet in Floating Dragon, asking her teacher to help care for them as her pastime.

There was another person in the room. Jenny stood to the side, reporting on the business situation of Floating Dragon. Even if Ames was not paying attention, she continued to seriously read the details out.

"… the recent polls show that thirty-nine percent of the Floating Dragon soldiers are dissatisfied with the status quo. Compared with the previous survey, the proportion has now increased by seven percent. Many of the subordinates came here after hearing the reputation of the Beyond Grade A, hoping that they would achieve some fame under your name and advance their careers, but with the lack of battle opportunities, their hearts have moved. This is especially so given that we have not participated in the Flickering World exploration. We have thus lost quite a few warriors…"

Ames seemed to let the words flow in and out of her ears, as she continued to use her force field to nudge the bear.

Jenny dryly coughed before continuing. "Ignoring the trend of the times is not wise. We should change our decision and set foot in the Flickering World…"

Ames suddenly raised her head to glance at her, slightly smiling as she said, "I thought you didn't like writing reports? This is your twenty-second time asking me to send troops into the Flickering World. Why are you so active now?"

"… Didn't you mention wanting to develop?" Jenny stroked her receding hairline. Toward this fickle shopkeeper, she was full of resignation toward her behavior.

While she detested work, she was unwilling to let go of the development Floating Dragon had been going through these few years. She could not allow herself to see Floating Dragon go to waste just because of her laziness.

"As my subordinates, they should adapt to me, not me to them." Ames seemed not to mind it, only sighing. "If only Black Star was still under me, I wouldn't need to worry about such things."

"…" Jenny's expression became pained. My heart, it hurts!

Ames ignored Jenny's expression, waving her hand as she spoke. "In any case, there's no need to persuade me further. I will not go to the Flickering World. I have no interest in that area."

Before Jenny could squeeze in another word, Ames' communicator rang. The moment she took it out, her eyes lit up.

"Black Star has sent me another message. Jenny, please wait outside."

Seeing this, Jenny could only force her words back down and walk out of the room, feeling sour in her heart.

I have not even finished talking about the official matters, but because of the daily news that Black Star sends, you do not even want to hear the important business reports anymore…

I'm obviously the first in line here…

Without caring about Jenny, Ames read the news that Han Xiao sent over in detail. Other than the news shared and the warm greetings, there was also a piece that refreshed her spirits.

"Aurora has finally reached the Calamity Grade. My students are really great." Ames was in a good mood.

At the end of the letter, Han Xiao also sent her an invitation to visit Black Star Palace and meet up with Aurora.

"To go over to the Flickering World…"

Ames hesitated.

If it was sent over by Black Star, she could not possibly reject…

What good timing.

Thinking thusly, Ames called Jenny back in.

"Prepare the spaceship. I'm going over to the Flickering World."

"You've thought it through? I'll assemble the team immediately!" Jenny exclaimed in joy.

"What team? I'm going solo." Ames waved the communicator. "Black Star invited me over to play."

Jenny's smile vanished in a flash.

Sigh, I've wasted half a day of saliva, but you immediately respond when Black Star asks you to go.

So, this is the feeling of someone who has been swayed by the other party…

At this moment, there was a song that could perfectly depict Jenny's feelings.

In this world, who is still not living a life that's akin to purgatory[1]…

…

In the Flickering World's free competition zone, more than a dozen general purpose spaceships were slowly cruising through the universe, carrying the guild members from several well-known Southeast Asian clubs such as Red Bay, Titan, and Archipelago.

"Everyone, our next move is critical and is related to whether we can quickly gain a foothold in the Flickering World."

In the meeting room, the Red Bay Captain, Venomous Snake, rapped on the table as he spoke in a serious tone.

"Snake is right," a Red Bay veteran, Forest Python, echoed. He used to be the captain of Red Bay and actively gave up his position when he was older, opting to train the newcomers instead. Venomous Snake had taken over as the new captain from the previous season.

"The current advantage of the Chinese players is huge, so we have to huddle together. Before the players from the other countries arrive, we must not provoke them first and develop in a low-key manner," Titan's Captain, Bangkok Buddha, analyzed. "However, the approach of the Chinese players is full of foresight. Maybe we can imitate their gameplay and communicate with the NPC forces in the same manner."

The Chinese clubs had an unparalleled advantage in the free competition zone, having already obtained a lot of help from the NPC organizations. This group of Southeast Asian guilds that were new to scene were naturally afraid to touch them. They first had to stand firm and develop themselves.

Due to the intervention from the army, the Chinese guilds had learned about the high-efficiency gameplay of Version 4.0 in advance, and the guilds of the various countries would naturally discover this point when conducting research. Thus, the Southeast Asian guilds wanted to copy their gameplay methods.

"But it's not as easy as it seems." Some of the people hesitated. "The Chinese players are able to succeed simply because they're affiliated with the army, but our faction has no such system, no independent qualifications, and no way for us to become a regular organization."

The guilds in the bigger clubs had not jumped ships at all and still belonged to factions from the Blackhole Edge.

The other factions did not have multiple regiments like the army, and for them, becoming a regular organization and turning independent right now was impossible.

Moreover, they were not free but rather recruited and bound by their factions. Before going to the faction base, they only had a limited time to move freely, which was incomparable to the time that the army players had.

"The Main Storyline Missions for our factions have been announced, and the free time we have in the free competition zone is limited. Let's quickly look for opportunities," Venomous Snake concluded.

Everyone discussed various countermeasures and decided to adopt the method of casting out their nets wide.

Very quickly, they hit countless nails. Because they were not an independent organization, they could only borrow the name of their faction and act as a special team. The vast majority of the organizations that they contacted directly rejected them. They were also foreign organizations, and not local tyrants such as the Black Star Army, so all of them were competing against each other. There was no need to invite wolves into their camp.

As for the remaining organizations, they were willing to listen to their requests based on the strength that they showed. While the scale of the Southeast Asian guilds was not as large as the Chinese guilds, it was still possible to form a group of more than ten thousand by uniting together.

But for Red Bay, Archipelago, and the other Southeast Asian clubs, they were not independent organizations, so they could only propose cooperation agreements. Only this way could they then develop a stronghold.

After hearing their requests, even those organizations that were interested immediately hung up on them.

Venomous Snake and the rest felt surprised. This was turning out far from expected. The Chinese players had achieved great success through this method, so why was it that they had such a difficult time communicating with the NPC organizations?

After researching, they figured out the crux of this matter. The organizations rejected them as they were unqualified as partners.

The players belonging to guilds such as Red Bay and Archipelago were mostly from Star Cluster level civilizations, which did not carry much weight in the Flickering World.

The reason behind the success of the Chinese players was because they belonged to the Black Star Army. Many organizations were willing to cooperate with them in order to embrace the thigh of the Black Star Army, which was their backer, to stabilize their strongholds and deter other organizations.

But the Star Cluster Civilizations, which were also foreign forces, did not possess such a privilege.

These people were helpless. Their faction was unwilling to lend them strength, and they also could not replicate the practice of the army players. It was no wonder they snagged only so many nails in their strategy.

The deeper they understood what the Black Star Army was capable of, the more they envied the Chinese players.

After exerting a Herculean effort, the Southeast Asian guilds finally managed to find a few small breakthrough points, completely incomparable to the scale of what the players in the Black Star Army were getting. After which, they had to respond to the call of their factions and follow them to work, temporarily unable to move freely.

Even Red Bay, Archipelago, and the other first tier guilds in Southeast Asia found it difficult to start, let alone the other Blackhole Edge players who did not join the Black Star Army. Without the capital to imitate the gameplay of the army players, they could only brute force their way through as they had done in the previous versions before Version 4.0.

As more and more players arrived, the situation quickly got complicated, and the World Server gradually took shape.

At the same time, Han Xiao had already arrived and hidden himself within the Emerald Star Cluster.

Han Xiao had carried out many plans for the army, and his leek field had successfully grown and expanded. It was time to mercilessly reap the harvest.

As more 'fresh leeks' moved their bases to the Black Star Army, his efficiency in gaining experience in the short term multiplied.

When the Black Star Army expanded to nearly eight million members, the amount of experience he needed to upgrade to level 320 was finally accumulated!

[1] [Annotation text missing] Back

Chapter 1027: God's Trait Transformation

In an unexplored area within the Emerald Star Cluster, a high-speed spaceship was proceeding at warp speed.

Only Han Xiao and a portion of the Apostle Weapons were sitting in the command room of the spaceship, watching the star map. His target marked in red flashed on the screen. The coordinates were located somewhere in the central area of the Emerald Star Cluster.

This was the place where the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy revealed in EsGod's inheritance would be born. Most of the organizations had not explored to this point. He travelled in the high-end spaceship that he had built, so he did not need to stop like the other forces and could penetrate deeper.

The time for the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy to appear was not far off. He went earlier to camp and do a stake out.

Because of Evans, only Han Xiao could be sure that the coordinates given were correct. The other forces that obtained information on the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy also had to try their luck in the several coordinates shown in the data, which could potentially reduce his competitors.

Han Xiao chose to come out with his true body for insurance. If the competitor was not strong, his avatar could do the job, and there was no need to reveal his position.

However, right now, Han Xiao was preparing to find a place to stay as his experience had finally reached the requirement to level up to level 320. His Promotion was still the priority.

During this period, he had been rushing along the journey. With the Black Star Army's foundation, he did not need to worry about it. He just had to wait for the foreign players to arrive in the Flickering World, and they would naturally join the Black Star Army.

Right now, the population of players in the army had reached about eight million, which was far from the limit. Once the remaining players in the other Star Fields came over to the World Server, the size of the army should break through the ten million mark. It would serve as a replenishment of newcomers, and he would even have a big wave of experience flowing in.

"Once all the players gather in the World Server, the players in the army should measure up to 11.5 million. This should be the biggest player faction at the moment. The number should only be second to the three Universal Civilizations in my past life."

Not all the players had arrived in the Flickering World, but they had already attracted the attention of the various major organizations, and the situation was moving toward the familiar early stage of Version 4.0 in his previous life.

Because of his own existence, the millions of players that should have been scattered around were instead situated within the Black Star Army, which would cause some deviation in the timeline. However, Han Xiao was mentally prepared for this, and the stage of making a lot of money through the players was about to pass. The major organizations would soon come to value the abilities of the players as much as he did.

"Let's not think about this for now. Anyway, my situation is quite good. The advantage is on my side, and I'm firmly seated on my benefits." Han Xiao pushed aside the thought, slowed down the spaceship, and parked in the middle of the universe.

He then exited the cabin and flew using his physical body away from the spaceship. He commanded the Apostle Weapons to guard his surroundings before opening the instrument that would isolate energy fluctuations, hiding the anomalies that would occur during his advancement.

Opening the interface, he looked at the astronomical experience numbers. Han Xiao could no longer wait.

"I've finally saved enough to advance and complete my promotion. It's been so long since I experienced this sort of rapid levelling up."

Even as he murmured to himself, he did not hesitate, immediately pumping all the experience into upgrading. His total level, which had remained stagnant for a long time, suddenly rocketed!

[Divine Throne Mechanic] leveled up to Lv.8.

+450 Energy, +5 STR, +5 DEX, +15 END, +20 INT.

You have received 15 Free Attribute Points and 1 Potential Point.

…

[Divine Throne Mechanic] leveled up to Lv.20.

+450 Energy, +5 STR, +5 DEX, +15 END, +20 INT.

You have received 15 Free Attribute Points and 1 Potential Point.

You have reached Lv.320, triggering the Promotion Mission for Lv.320!

Han Xiao had accumulated a lot of Mission Completion Cards over the decades, and the moment he saw that the mission was a troublesome one, he immediately pulled out his mission completion card.

Lv.320 Promotion Mission completed!

Promotion succeeded!

+90 END Bonus! 1 END = 570 Health = 580 Stamina.

The LV 320 special blueprints for the Tyracles Mechanical Legacy have been unlocked!

Your Energy Level has reached Lv.21. Energy has passed 78,000.

You have gained the talent [God's Trait Transformation—Machinery] (0/?)

You have gained the talent [God's Trait Transformation—Void] (0/?)

You have obtained 2 God's Trait Transformation points.

You have received a [The First Sanctum] Ability Fragment.

The effects of all your Virtual Technology skills have been increased by 50%.

Han Xiao's body jolted once, and every cell in his body seemed to have become a black hole, ravenously swallowing the cosmic dark matter around it, using it to improve itself.

The upper limit of the [Divine Throne Mechanic] was Lv.60, and he could only perform his Class Advancement at level 360. His next racial species sublimation would be at level 340.

In Han Xiao's mind, level 320 should have been a normal promotion, but the notification that appeared gave his spirit a boost.

"God's Trait Transformation?" Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

He was not completely unfamiliar with this term. In the later versions of his past life, this term constantly appeared within the Beyond Grade A circles, which was then overheard by the players. Although there was little intelligence on it, based on the hypotheses that were written on the forums, this should be an important factor to upgrade one's life level above the Beyond Grade A realm.

Furthermore, his own Machinery Deity had the term 'Deity' within, and if one had to talk about a Godhood, then it might have something to do with the Machinery Faith and the [Key of Adeptus Mechanicus]… However, he had not experienced anything to do with divinity whatsoever at this moment.

Why is it that as one's life level increases, it becomes more and more ideological? This is making me, a mechanic that only believes in materialism very awkward…

"In any case, it seems like the threshold of Lv.21 Energy Rank and 78,000 Onas of Energy are needed to trigger the God's Trait Transformation?" Han Xiao murmured to himself whilst enduring the pain that came with the advancement.

The calculation method for energy rank was quite complicated, not just a simple addition and subtraction. The larger the value, the larger the gap between every one point. For example, the energy levels of 100 to 200 and 9,900 to 10,000 were both similarly separated by a hundred points, but the difference in their actual energy values was huge. The higher one's energy was, the harder it was to increase.

When he had broken through the level 300 watershed to become a Mechanical Deity, his total energy was around 71,000.

In the next decade, he had constantly practiced new Energy Training Techniques, raising the upper limit of his energy, and he had also spent a lot of experience and potential points to improve his skills and knowledge. At the same time, he had also extracted abilities from Heber, Manison, Silver Shadow, and many others, gaining powerful talents and skills. With the [Perfect Mechanical Sense] from Nero, along with his various bonuses, his total energy finally broke through 78,000.

"The two God's Trait Transformations are split into Machinery and Void respectively… Oh, this corresponds to one's class and race. So, are these the two possible evolutionary routes, or do I need to add them both at once?"

Han Xiao glanced at the interface, where he saw a small '+' sign beside each of the God's Trait Transformation talents, and the effect was labelled with a '?'.

"It seems like I will only know the effect when I add points. Since the system gave me two God's Trait Transformation points when I was promoted, let's try one in each… The suffix of the skills should represent the final form of this talent, which should occur when the talent is maxed out. But the total number of points is labelled as a '?', so how many points should I add?"

Han Xiao tried adding a point to the [God's Trait Transformation—Machinery] talent, and the effect of it was displayed.

God's Trait Transformation—Machinery (1/?)

Stage One: +1,000 Machinery Affinity, +20% Ability power. Base effects of all Mechanic class abilities are slightly enhanced.

Han Xiao glanced at his skill list. With the slight enhancement to his class abilities, it meant that every skill had undergone a slight improvement for every level. The effect of strengthening all his Mechanic-related skills was not high, but it provided a comprehensive improvement.

"The bonus is acceptable, but I don't find it too powerful. Maybe it's because it's only at the first stage? I guess, the more points I add, the more powerful the effects unlocked." Han Xiao raised his eyebrows.

He hesitated but finally decided against adding another point to it. He added it to the [God's Trait Transformation—Void] talent instead.

God's Trait Transformation—Void (1/?)

Stage One: Exclusive Racial Talents are enhanced, and all Racial Talents of the Void Race Evolution route will be strengthened. You have been awarded 1,750 Attribute Points.

The total affinity bonus from [Mechanical Genius] increased from x1.25 to x1.28, and Machinery Creation Performance increased from forty percent to forty-four percent. The racial talents of his other Void abilities also showed some increase, with the cooldown times of most of them being reduced.

Han Xiao nodded. "This one is not bad."

With his God's Trait Transformation points spent, he did not know how to obtain more. Were they only given when he promoted, or was there another way to obtain them?

If this was only given during advancement, that would mean that the sooner one reached the 78,000 benchmark the better. After all, if one's level was low, advancing would definitely be more convenient, and one could obtain more points this way. In this manner… could that also refer to potential?

Han Xiao decided not to think further, opting to look at the other notifications.

What was this [The First Sanctum] fragment? He had not heard of this in his past life.

The introduction was also labelled with question marks. Han Xiao could not understand what this was, but from the name of [The First Sanctum], it seemed as though it had nothing to do with the Mechanic class. Furthermore, he only had a fragment, so he could not utilize it and could only stare at it.

"I keep having the feeling that this should be a key factor for something… I should find an opportunity to ask the dynasty if there's any information in this area. Most likely, I'll have to exchange contribution points for it, just like the time when I obtained the information on the Machinery Faith."

After removing everything unrelated, Han Xiao then turned toward the [Tyracles Mechanical Legacy]. There would be new blueprints unlocked at level 320 and 360.

He glanced through it quickly, and his pupils suddenly narrowed to a point. A hint of surprise leaked out.

F*ck me, I've hit the jackpot!

Chapter 1028: The King and the Emperor's Cape

Among the [Tyracles Mechanical Legacy] blueprints unlocked at level 320, there were blueprints that were shining gold in color!

Not one but two!

The Gold Grade represented equipment that was on the level of a Universal Treasure!

Han Xiao had a joyful surprise.

He originally thought that he would only get the opportunity to unlock the Universal Treasure blueprints when he reached level 360, but it unexpectedly came out in level 320. The Gold blueprints of this race might be higher than he initially imagined.

He hurriedly opened the item introduction, and the two blueprints' information appeared in his eyes.

[Blueprint: King]: This blueprint records the highest crystallization of wisdom from the Saint Tyracles Race for Superpower soldiers—The 'King'. Made exclusively for Beyond Grade A Mechanics, the blueprint's cost is high, with a set of armor comparable to the price of a large fleet, and it is extremely difficult to produce. Since its birth, the total number of finished products created by the Saint Tyracles Race numbered no more than ten. Only a Mechanic with enough strength will be able to control this mechanical suit.

[Blueprint: Emperor's Cape]: After the Saint Tyracles Race witnessed the imposingness of the Mechanical Deity, they began to zealously research, producing this extraordinary mechanical creation. This is a piece of equipment that can only be utilized by a Mechanical Deity.

Han Xiao carefully looked through the blueprints, as well as the effects of the two pieces of equipment.

The Saint Tyracles Race had advanced extremely far in the Mechanic class. The [King] mechanical suit displayed it, reaching the level that could be considered a Universal Treasure, which blended many of the advanced skills of the Saint Tyracles.

This Mechanical suit was armor designed for a Beyond Grade A Mechanic, and the reference parameters of the blueprint showed that just the basic performance of the King outstripped his current mechanical suit by at least thirty percent! His own mechanical suit was high-end Orange equipment, considered one of the best within its grade quality!

In addition to conventional combat weapons, the King also had unique features that made it extremely suitable for Mechanics.

As a dedicated equipment for Mechanics, the King provided an extra bonus toward mechanics, which provided users with an additional x1.075 coefficient to their total Machinery Affinity, only slightly less compared to the increase from the Divine Mechanical Throne. Furthermore, it increased the range of effect for the Mechanical Force bonus by thirty-five percent while reducing the energy consumption. This would strengthen normal mechanics to provide their army with a longer period of blessing.

Moreover, the King was equipped with a special energy converter that could absorb Mechanical Force and enter an enhanced state. There were multiple modes, such as improving the performance of the Mechanical suit, strengthening melee capabilities, and providing instant acceleration and defense, so as to get rid of any ambushes that the Mechanic most feared.

While this man-made combat equipment was at the level of a Universal Treasure, it did not belong to the scope of a Space Wonder, so the quality of its stats were more reflected in its performance. It would not be equipped with an unsolvable power like the Spacetime Amber. It was closer to the Universal Treasure level equipment made by the Divine Craftsman Thorne.

However… the King belonged to another type of equipment.

It was the core function of the King that made Han Xiao truly satisfied!

When the Federation of Light manufactured their Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device, they had borrowed the knowledge of the Saint Tyracles Race, and the core function of the King was related to this.

The reason why the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device was the strategic weapon of the Federation of Light was because it had the capability of unlimited transmissions. Not only was the distance long, it was also immune to interference from all spatial related devices, which was the most important thing. The King had a similar immunity as well.

'The King' possessed a unique accessory called the Throne, and both sides would resonate with each other. No matter where the King was, the user could instantly return to the location of the Throne together with the suit. This transmission ignored all external interference, and it would still take effect even when trapped within wormholes or space stabilization anchors.

The introduction for this function was simply a statement—'The King cannot be restrained.'

It was not just restricted to that. When the King returned to the Throne, the follow up effect of this function could be activated in the next three minutes. This allowed the user to blink back to the original position of the King. To be able to shuttle back and forth between two points… simply put, this was horizontal warping.

"There is the shadow of the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening ability within. So long as I'm wearing the King, I will not need to be afraid of sudden ambushes like EsGod. I can immediately choose to warp back to my Throne, leaving the danger zone." Han Xiao's eyes gleamed.

In view of his true body's physical susceptibility toward ambushes… this toy was akin to a divine artifact for him!

While it was a fixed position warp and not as effective as the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device, it still had an irreplaceable role. For the mechanic with a weak body, this was a magical escape technique. As the saying went, where there was life there was hope, and this was very apt for the mechanic.

Han Xiao looked at the manufacturing requirements, thinking to himself, The cost is high, but it is still in an acceptable range for me. Some of the core materials will be hard to get, but that was during the exploration era. Right now, we're in the Galaxy Calendar. As long as you have enough money, you can get your hands on any materials you want.

Han Xiao was not worried about the cost nor the rarity of the materials.

As the top Beyond Grade A in the Shattered Star Ring, the strongest in the Flickering World, and the 'Sugar Daddy' of hundreds of financial groups, finances were not an issue.

His main concern was the difficulty of manufacturing. It was no easy task to build Gold Grade equipment. It did not mean that he was guaranteed to produce Gold Equipment as long as he followed the blueprints.

There was a high probability that the finished product would not reach the quality of Gold Grade Equipment. There would be all sorts of reasons that led to the finished product not reaching the ideal state as stated on the blueprint.

"I'm now at level 320 and am considered a pinnacle Beyond Grade A Mechanic. The basic manufacturing abilities will definitely meet the mark, and coupled with the talents provided by the my Divine Throne Mechanic class, the success rate should not be too low."

During a prior class advancement, he had received a talent named [Spirit Instrument], which improved his success rate of manufacturing from gold blueprints. He finally had a chance to put it to use.

As for the other unlocked blueprint, the [Emperor's Cape] was special equipment that was to be used by the Mechanical Deity. In short, the King was the mechanical suit for the Mechanic, while the Emperor's Cape was used when the Mechanical Deity descended.

In appearance, it looked like an oversized war cloak. It was able to reduce the consumption of energy needed for the Divine Throne Mechanic to maintain the Mechanical Deity, indirectly extending the combat time.

Not everyone could be as perverted as Han Xiao. Most ordinary mechanics did not have as many energy conversion abilities, so the Emperor's Cape served to allow the Mechanic to use the Mechanical Deity for longer periods of time.

Other than reducing consumption, it would also provide additional protection and stabilize the interior of the Mechanical Deity. Because it was made up of countless machines, the stronger the bonds between each machine, the higher the mechanical defensiveness of the Mechanical Deity.

In his battle against Heber, that little Ty-Ty had rushed into the hand of his Mechanical Deity, trying to wreck it from the inside. Although he had failed, he had managed to temporarily destroy the right arm of the Mechanical Deity. If not for the fact that Han Xiao's energy recovery speed was frighteningly high, just the consumption needed to reform the arm would have required the Mechanic to give up a kidney.

If he had the Emperor's Cape, the internals of his Mechanical Deity would become extremely durable, such that it would still last a length of time even when invaded by a pinnacle Beyond Grade A pugilist.

In addition to its protective ability, the Emperor's Cape also brought about movement speed bonuses. Because of its huge size, the speed of the Mechanical Deity was greatly affected, so the Emperor's Cape could improve the agility and attack speed of the Mechanical Deity.

"These two are both Gold equipment that are tailor-made for Mechanics. Indeed, the famed Mechanic haven, this Saint Tyracles race."

Han Xiao was drooling at the sight of the two. After rejecting the dynasty's proposal to give up the Evolution Cube, he had thought that there would be no more chances for him to obtain Universal Treasure combat equipment in the short term. The effect of these two blueprints gave him a surprise, as they could immediately improve his combat capability, which was what he was currently lacking.

"I've got to find a way to quickly manufacture them. Right now, there are many Beyond Grade As flocking to the Flickering World, and the major organizations also roughly understand my current strength. If something happens, it will be a crisis for me…"

Han Xiao calmed himself down as he gazed at his attributes panel.

Total Level: 320

Main Class: Mechanic

Race: Black Star Race

Attributes: 8,016 STR, 7,945 DEX, 11,714 END, 20,933 INT, 6,430 MYS, 1,368 CHA, 1 LUK

Free Attribute Points: 2050

Potential Points: 28

Health: 13,984,273

Stamina: 11,806,980

Energy: 182,075 (Lv.21)

Lv.21 Energy Level bonus stat: +3,206 STR, +3,928 DEX, +4,870 END, +6,505 INT, +3,123 MYS, +1,381,520 Stamina Limit, +4,282% Machinery Affinity

Energy Rank: 82,600

Grade: SS

Grade S Bonuses: +150 END, +45% All Resistances, +40% to Highest Attribute, +25% Other Attributes, 750 Free Attribute Points, and 50 Potential Points

Remark: Standing at the peak allows you to see more of the scenery. However, this is not the end goal in the route of evolution. You must pierce through the fog to slowly touch upon the secrets to an even higher realm of life.

Chapter 1029: The Dynasty's Plans

Compared to when he was at level 300, the attribute growth was obvious, but this mainly came from the bonus given by his Lv.21 Energy Level and was due to Han Xiao's accumulation during the version update.

As his energy level continuously increased, he would also gain ever-increasing strength. This was an important part behind the power of the Supers.

The Endurance bonus for his promotion this time was '+90', which was twenty points more than his previous promotion. Because it was more difficult to upgrade in the later stage, the enhancement to one's attributes brought about by each advancement would also increase, and the increase in Energy Rank would also cause one's S-level rank bonus to upgrade even higher. There was a close connection between all the attributes, causing Han Xiao to be comprehensively strengthened.

Just an ordinary promotion already gave him such a sharp increase in stats, causing Han Xiao to be extremely satisfied.

"As for the more than 2,000 Free Attribute Points…"

Han Xiao thought about it but left them untouched for the time being. His Intelligence and Endurance were all quite high, so he decided to provide himself with some flexibility depending on the situation.

As for his potential points, they would be used to upgrade his Class knowledge, with the Ultimate Knowledge having priority.

At present, there were only three of his Ultimate Knowledges that were maxed out, namely [Virtual Creator], [Eternal Power Source], and [Relativity Theory]. The other three belonged to the other branches of the Mechanic class, and there was a three-times penalty imposed. Levelling them from Lv.1 to Lv.5 would require a total of 288 potential points.

Han Xiao had gained quite a few potential points since the update of the version. He had raised the three Ultimate Knowledges a little each, and the twenty-eight free potential points he had on the interface right now were just right to max out his [Mechanical Life Tinder] skill.

However, Han Xiao did not do so after some thought. He turned and added a level to [Ultimate Mechanical Engineering], raising it to Lv.3.

This class knowledge was related to one's manufacturing and production, and Han Xiao wanted to increase the success rate of the Emperor's Cape and the King, so he first prioritized this knowledge.

"A plan cannot always keep up with the changes. I wanted to go there and camp, but now I need to work while I wait." Han Xiao shook his head.

Now that he was alone and unable to use the workshop in his base, he could only use the army workshop in his secondary dimension, and he even had to go out of his way to obtain the raw materials.

He counted the days, and he probably could not even create it before the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was born. The time needed to manufacture a Universal Treasure-level equipment was quite hefty. That was especially so for the Emperor's Cape, which was physically huge.

"Right now, I've reached level 320, and my battle strength has experienced yet another leap, drawing closer to the Mechanic Emperor and Void Overlord. I can gauge their strength even better now…" Han Xiao sighed.

Seeing the gap in strength narrowing bit by bit, his mood was definitely good.

However, after this promotion, his upgrade costs once again skyrocketed. Because the effects of each promotion in the later stages were extraordinary, the upgrade fee naturally corresponded to this.

"I'm afraid it will take a long time to accumulate enough experience to upgrade to level 340. Also, I have to find an opportunity to ask about the God's Trait Transformation as well as The First Sanctum."

…

In Tarunamir Palace, the top leader of the hawk faction, Bekorodi, sat in a conference room with his eyes closed for a rest. After a while, a remote projection appeared. It was Gaud.

"You're here." Bekorodi opened his eyes.

"I hope you called me over to inform me about some good news." Gaud's expression was calm.

"It's indeed good news," Bekorodi said in a deep voice. "The request you submitted has been approved, and the dynasty's top management has decided to give the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy to you… provided that your Esper ability is truly as what you've said and that you can control the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy."

The dynasty had bet on Black Star, thinking that he would be an important National Pillar in the future, but the dynasty did not mind having another person as strong as him. After all, someone with Gaud's Esper Ability was too rare, so the dynasty was willing to spend the resources to cultivate this high potential Esper. Furthermore, this person still belonged to the dynasty, and he was not an ally who did not have to listen to all their orders.

"I'm very clear what my ability can and cannot do, so as long as the dynasty is willing to put their trust in me, I will not disappoint them." Gaud thinly smiled.

"As long as you can prove yourself, the dynasty will not be stingy with the resources to cultivate you, just like Black Star." The moment Bekorodi mentioned Han Xiao, his tone got a little deeper.

Black Star rejecting his one to three exchange had left Bekorodi extremely dissatisfied.

However, Gaud only replied with a smile that was not a real smile, skirting past this topic. He instead asked, "Now that the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy is about to be born, what does the dynasty intend to do?"

Bekorodi nodded. "The dynasty has already sent troops to the various locations shown by the intelligence, and we have spotted abnormal movements from many of the organizations, which confirms that they likely also got their hands on EsGod's legacy. They will be our competitors in obtaining the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy…"

"What sort of organizations are they?"

"The number is small, but their composition is complex. There are all kinds of organizations, but the church and the federation's side do not seem to have moved, so we cannot know if they are aware of this matter…"

"It sounds like there are many uncertainties. Can we ensure that the dynasty will get the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy?"

"The current situation is unclear. The Oracle of the dynasty has tried to scry for information, and it feels like the Emerald Star Cluster is the most likely place in which the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy will appear. It just so happens that the Flickering World is our territory, so the dynasty has decided to engage a few Beyond Grade A allies for help." Bekorodi narrowed his eyes as he spoke.

"Black Star?"

"He's not on the list." Bekorodi shook his head.

The Black Star Army had the greatest amount of influence in the Flickering World, so it stood to reason that Black Star should be the most reliable. However, the dynasty did not request help from him, and Bekorodi did not disclose the reason.

Gaud smiled to himself as he realized the implications.

Tsk, it seemed like the problem with the Evolution Cube caused quite a rift between Black Star and the dynasty…

His eyes flickered, and Gaud calmly said, "Since that's the case, I have a suggestion. We should tell Black Star to turn away so as to prevent side issues from arising."

"I don't have the authority to command Black Star." Bekorodi waved his hands. "In addition, the latest news states that his Black Star Guards are all within his palace, and even Ames has gone over to visit him from Shattered Star Ring. Thus, it is likely that his true body is still within his base. He probably knows his limits and will not interfere in this matter…"

Bekorodi paused for a moment before his expression sank. "However, even if Black Star decides to interfere, the dynasty can still strike a deal with him. With his current situation, the chances of him rejecting us again are miniscule. He should know what to do in order to mend his relationship with us."

"That's good. I hope that there will not be any accidents during the operation." Gaud narrowed his eyes.

The dynasty did not wish to see a special talent like him encounter any unnecessary risks before growing up, so he could not join the operation.

What Gaud needed to do was obediently stay put and wait for the dynasty to hand him the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy.

Getting the dynasty to work for me is so convenient… Gaud secretly smiled and shook his head.

Chapter 1030: Movements of the Competitors

"They want me to snatch that famous Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy on the dynasty's behalf?"

In a certain dynasty's ally stronghold in the Flickering World's free competition zone, Ravenlaude was surprised to receive this message from the upper echelons of the dynasty.

As a member of the senior celebrity group, Ravenlaude was quite highly regarded among the Beyond Grade A allies of the dynasty. His position was far above people like Kohler or Beyoni. Although he did not exactly have a good relationship with Black Star, the two of them held no grudges against each other.

Of course, Ravenlaude had no idea that the Spacetime Amber was supposed to belong to him but was taken away by Han Xiao in advance, or he would have joined the 'dynasty anti-Black Star alliance', which had Heber as its one and only member.

It was common for the dynasty to ask him for help. What Ravenlaude was surprised about was the information about the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy appearing. This was the first time he had heard of this.

"The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy…" Ravenlaude's eyes sparkled.

To be honest, he was quite tempted.

Primal Esper Abilities in the Super High Risk Esper Ability List such as this one were extremely rare. If he could make it his, it would be more than enough to raise a powerful subordinate, or he could use sealing type spells to seal the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy onto special magic puppets to use its powers, which might make the puppet as strong as a Universal Treasure.

However, these greedy thoughts only existed for a few seconds in Ravenlaude's mind before he completely extinguished them.

His organization was right in the Constellation Corridor, which was heavily affected by the dynasty. There was no need to go against the dynasty's will for just a Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy.

The dynasty told him about this information to let him help, but if he was tempted by it, it would definitely upset the dynasty. To him, there was more to lose than gain.

"But a Universal Treasure…"

Ravenlaude still found it tough to let go. It was not really because he did not even have the courage to let go of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, but after seeing Han Xiao's Spacetime Amber, he had felt a sense of emptiness in his heart, like he had missed something very important. Universal Treasures had become almost an impulse for him.

It was like a kid seeing the other kids with fun toys and also wanting one.

One word, jealous!

"Since the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy is as valuable as a Universal Treasure, it's the right time to negotiate terms with the dynasty."

Ravenlaude then gave his request to the dynasty—if they wanted his help, the dynasty had to grant him a Universal Treasure from their inventory.

Not long after his request, the dynasty's reply came, expressing their approval of Ravenlaude's request but with additional terms.

If the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy appeared in other areas, Ravenlaude would only receive some resources as a reward for his trouble.

But if the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy appeared in the Emerald Star Cluster and Ravenlaude obtained it, he would be allowed to pick one Universal Treasure from the dynasty's inventory.

A list was also attached with the reply with the Universal Treasures the dynasty allowed Ravenlaude to claim. Most of them were combat equipment; it was the same list given to Han Xiao in exchange for the Evolution Cube.

Ravenlaude browsed through carefully and nodded with satisfaction.

Han Xiao had no interest in these things, but they were very valuable to Ravenlaude. After all, Han Xiao already had the Evolution Cube and the Spacetime Amber, so ordinary Universal Treasures could not meet his standards.

With the reward promised, Ravenlaude became motivated about this mission. After carefully looking at the list of competitors that the dynasty had provided, he smiled with confidence.

How hard would it be to snatch something from a bunch of weaklings?

…

In an unexplored area of the Emerald Star Cluster, a fleet was moving in hyperdrive. Its exterior armor had no symbols.

Inside the main ship, a tall man wearing a purple rope stood before the command console, giving off a cold aura and silently looking at the star map. The red dots on it marked the coordinates where the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy might appear.

Beside him, a fishman-like creature who was restrained by magical ropes said with a shivering and nervous tone, "Your Excellency Secret Master, I swear this piece of intelligence is real. It's really EsGod's heritage, not fake news I made up!"

"It had better be, or you know the consequences," a cold and indifferent voice replied. The man turned around and glanced at him. All of the skin he was showing was covered in magnificent and complicated magical runes flickering with dim light, like he was a tattoo addicted.

Just like 'Beast Ancestor' Gorutan, this man was also a protector of the Galactic Black Market. He was the famous Secret Master renowned in the magic society. He was an authority in Rune Studies, Alchemy Studies, and Secret Studies, especially in Secret Studies. The reason he had this nickname was because there was a rumor going around that he had mastered a type of spell that could control someone's 'luck', also that he was a master in fortune telling and foresight.

All the tattoos on his body were Forbidden Spell grade rune enchantments that provided powerful enhancements to his body. The organization that Secret Master was in specialized in extremely advanced rune technology, which could be seen from looking at his subordinates. All of them were wearing exquisite rune armor, and the skin they were showing was also covered in complex magical patterns.

Secret Master turned to the star map, and the cold look in his eyes rippled ever so slightly.

"The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy…"

Not long ago, he had suddenly foreseen that a huge event would happen in the Emerald Star Cluster that might be beneficial to him, so he had used his power in the black market and investigated it. With his outstanding luck, he discovered a small organization that had fought for EsGod's heritage previously. They happened to have the coordinates of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. After they were captured and interrogated, Secret Master developed an interest for the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy.

He was someone who did not mind using all kinds of external agents to increase his strength, and all these runes over his body were proof of that. At the same time, he had plenty of high-quality magic items; his desire to collect rare items was almost at an OCD level. Therefore, he naturally wanted this extremely rare Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy as well.

Due to the distance, he had sent officers to the other coordinates while he headed personally to the Emerald Star Cluster as it had the highest possibility.

"I wonder what organizations will be part of this…"

This question appeared in his mind but was very soon forgotten. He had a lot of confidence.

No matter what organization comes, I'll just have to beat them up. How many of them will be able to stand up to a Beyond Grade A like me?

…

The stronghold of the Modo Civilization was situated in another area of the Emerald Star Cluster.

An elite team formed by Calamity Grade Supers gathered at a secret dock, and the commander of the Modo Civilization's Expedition Fleet Roddick and the inspector Lagos stood before them, examining the team.

"I'll leave the mission of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy to you guys." Roddick nodded at everyone solemnly.

Some advanced civilizations had also received information from EsGod's heritage, among which the Modo Civilization was one of those who knew about the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. The Modo Civilization had no reason to let go of something this valuable.

The other locations were given to others to take care of, while the Expedition Fleet led by Roddick was responsible for the coordinates in the Emerald Star Cluster.

Ever since the Expedition Fleet was last attacked by the 'mysterious force', pressured by the upper echelons, Roddick had become much more vigilant. He was very careful in resupplying the resources.

However, it did not turn out to be very useful. The reinforcements redeployed from the Shattered Star Ring were often attacked by 'unknown forces' on the way, which cost them a lot of time.

Luckily, after they arrived in the free competition zone, the Super Star Cluster allies had helped them slightly, which made the situation better for the Modo Civilization. Therefore, Roddick's team were not attacked again in the Emerald Star Cluster.

Hence, he had the time to gather an elite team, ready to complete the mission given by the upper echelons—capture the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy.

Super Star Cluster civilizations had vast territories and rich resources, as well as plenty of high level combatants. They had thousands of Calamity Grades, far more than those Star System civilizations that only had a few dozens.

The Modo Civilization had high hopes for the Expedition Fleet, so they had deployed around a hundred Calamity Grades. This elite team that would be heading to capture the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy included forty percent of the Expedition Fleet's Calamity Grade officers, which was about forty to fifty of them. This was a powerful armed force.

For this operation, the Modo Civilization did not notify the other allies of the Super Star Cluster alliance. After all, there was only one Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy; it could not be shared.

Maybe the other civilizations had this intelligence too, but the Modo Civilization clearly was not going to tell others about it.

Watching the fleet enter stealth mode and leave, Lagos came to Roddick and asked in a worried tone, "Isn't it too risky to send this many people? If something happens, we'll lose a large number of elites. Calamity Grades are difficult to raise…"

"I've told them to be careful. If any Beyond Grade As participate, they'll act cautiously. If not, they can crush any and all competing organizations," Roddick said with a deep voice.

"But now that we've sent them out, the defenses of our stronghold will be weak. Aren't you worried that Blac… the mysterious force will attack us again?" Lagos asked.

Roddick snorted and said in a firm tone, "Humph, the strongholds of the Super Star Cluster alliance look over each other's shoulders. We even hired some Beyond Grade As, who are all more reliable than Garoze. So what if Black Star's forces are strong? He won't dare come and touch us."

They did not have to advance anymore. Back then, they had no help, so there was nothing they could do when they were attacked. Now, however, all their teammates had gathered, and the lines of defenses were stronger than ever. If Black Star caused trouble, he would have to face the entire Super Star Cluster alliance. He did not think Black Star would dare do that.

…

After the Flickering World opened, Psyker did not give up on the opportunity and also followed the Arcane Church in to develop his forces and built a stronghold in the free competition zone.

As the three Universal Civilizations were coexisting there, Psyker did not get targeted, so his days were quite peaceful. Looking at the exploration fleet doing better work every day, he was rather content.

"I shall see how things go first. If I can stabilize my territory in the Flickering World, I can migrate a portion of my people here and have them live here as a branch of the race."

At the top of the base, Psyker looked up at the sky and thought about his migration plan.

At this time, an officer hastily walked over.

"Leader, the base's radar has discovered two fleets closing in. They seem to be in combat. One side only has three battleships left, and they cannot hang on much longer. According to the direction they're heading, their battle will very soon reach our stronghold. What should we do?"

Psyker used his seven eyes to look at the radar images and ordered, "Chase them away. Tell them to not fight around my territory."

As the order was given, the subordinates quickly executed it. However, after some time, this officer ran back hastily again.

"Leader, they have already been chased away, but that group of people we saved aren't willing to leave. One of them is a Calamity Grade Super. He thinks that you saved them, so he wants to join us with his team."

"Join us?" Psyker was a little stunned. He felt a complicated emotion in his heart.

He suddenly remembered that ever since he was targeted by Black Star, it had been a very long time since anyone came to join his forces. He had almost forgotten what it was like to be a Beyond Grade A.

This long-lost feeling… was so comforting.

"Invite him here. I want to see him." Psyker was glad, and his attitude became much friendlier. Psyker decided to see him personally to show him that he took him seriously.

After some time, this Calamity Grade was brought before Psyker. He had many wounds on his body, and it was clear he had just come from a tough battle.

"Your Excellency Star Pupil." This person's face was filled with appreciation. He ignored the pain in his body and bowed with admiration. "You saved my life. I'm willing to join your forces and work for you."

"Hmm, it's a small matter." Psyker looked calmed on the surface, but he actually liked this a lot. The respectful attitude from this person made him remember what it was like to be a Beyond Grade A again.

"To repay you, I would like to give you a gift. It's a piece of valuable intelligence."

"What intelligence?" Psyker asked.

"A clue about that legendary Super High Risk Esper Ability, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy!"

Psyker paused for a second, and interest flashed through his seven eyes at the same time.

…

In Black Star Palace…

"What, he invited me over, but he went out‽"

Ames narrowed her eyes. The temperature in the room seemed to decrease by a hundred degrees in an instant. A powerful force field roared like tides. The floor and the walls made of high strength alloys vibrated nonstop while making squeaking noises, and cracks appeared very quickly.

Aurora's legs were going soft. She lowered her head with a sense of guilt.

My teacher is… so scary when she's angry.

She could feel Ames' anger just from this powerful force field.

She had accepted the invitation with excitement, travelled all that way, only to discover that Han Xiao was not even there. Anyone would be angry because of that…

No, it was even worse. Han Xiao was not home, yet he had called her over. It was almost like a deliberate prank.

Even someone as carefree as Ames felt that she had been toyed with.

"Teacher, why not stay here for some time? Uncle will come back," Aurora said cautiously.

Ames glanced at her and rebutted subconsciously, "You think I'm that free?"

Then, both of them fell silent.

Aurora wanted to say something but did not.

Don't you know exactly whether you're very free or not?

The two of them looked into each other's eyes, and the atmosphere gradually turned awkward.

After looking at each other for a few moments, Ames suddenly retracted the roaring force field. Without changing her expression, she purposely used a tone that sounded like she did not care and said, "I'll stay for some time then. I'm mainly here for you anyway. Whether Black Star is here or not, I don't care. In fact, it bothers me to see his face. It's best that he's not here.

Aurora remained silent. Sure, I believe you.

Chapter 1031: Tough Path of Evolution and Appearance

Han Xiao looked at Aurora's bloated cheeks on the communicator and said with a smile, "I see, Ames has already arrived. Tell her to stay at my place for some time… Oh? You've already dealt with her? Great job, I'll give you a red flower when I'm back."

After settling Ames down, Aurora had notified Han Xiao at the first instance to explain the situation, which was mostly her blaming him. He purposely stood her teacher up and left her to deal with it. What a horrible man.

"You'd best speak with her, or Her Excellency Dragon Emperor will definitely get angrier."

"I have my plans. Settle her down properly and use your cuteness to make her less angry. I'll explain everything to her when I get back."

Han Xiao chatted for a while and ended the call. He then shook his head and smiled.

He had deliberately invited Ames to Black Star Palace to make others believe that his main body was in his base. Also, it would increase the defenses of his base while he was away, but it was mainly to protect Aurora and the others.

After all, the Secret Studies was a path to many abilities. Many were paying attention to Hila, and there would definitely be people who had used foresight abilities on her. Someone might discover Aurora's strengthened life link with Hila. Being more cautious about others attacking his base could never be wrong.

After handling this matter, Han Xiao opened up the data that the dynasty had sent him a few days ago and continued reading.

After his Promotion, he had asked the dynasty about [God's Trait Transformation] and [The First Sanctum]. He had received some confidential information regarding that.

According to the data, after entering the peak of the Beyond Grade A realm, one had to dig deeper into the Super system and the nature of one's own genes. When one evolved to this stage, a new extra evolution path would appear, which was named [God's Trait Transformation].

Every transformation was a special evolution that granted new powers, as if one had surpassed a certain limit of evolution and had gained new 'superpowers'. Most peak Beyond Grade As felt that this was an important factor of entering that unknown higher power. However, the God's Trait Transformation seemed to have no end. No one had ever been known for completing all of the God's Trait Transformations. It was still a mystery.

The dynasty was not surprised about Han Xiao asking about God's Trait Transformation. It was not strange for Black Star to come in touch with this territory given his current position. Plus, Han Xiao had just hosted the Meeting of the Gods not long ago, so he had most likely heard this name from the other peak Beyond Grade As and approached them to research it.

This data cost some Faction Contribution Points, and it not only included the introduction but also the dynasty's research on it, as well as the experience and understanding of the peak Beyond Grade As of the past. Thanks to this, Han Xiao had a deeper understanding of God's Trait Transformation.

However, he did not find any other way to obtain God's Trait Transformation Points in this data. It seemed that he could only obtain them through Promotion.

Nonetheless, the data was still useful. After arranging the information, Han Xiao found a pattern—every Promotion seemed to have brought a different number of God's Trait Transformation Points. It seemed to be reliant on multiple factors.

Although the others did not have an interface and could not quantify their attributes, Han Xiao still used the data to do calculations and speculate. According to that, the following could be the factors that affected the God's Trait Transformation Points gained through every Promotion: Highest attribute > 20,000, second highest attribute >15,000, >85,000 Energy Rank, maximum level Knowledge, and having a soul connection with a Universal Treasure.

Once one of the above requirements was met, the God's Trait Transformation Points gained through every Promotion would increase by one. He had received two points at once because he satisfied two of these requirements.

If I want more points, I'll have to prioritize these requirements before Promotion.

He had obtained two God's Trait Transformation Points through the first Promotion, which was neither the best nor the worst, just mediocre.

This meant that at the peak of the Beyond Grade A realm, keeping one's level low would be the mainstream play style, and going through Promotions after more requirements were met would be the most beneficial.

If I'm guessing correctly, the Promotion mission in the future might require my God's Trait Transformation to be at a certain level, Han Xiao speculated and instantly understood the difficulty of it.

If normal peak Beyond Grade As did not prioritize these requirements, they would not obtain enough God's Trait Transformation Points through Promotions and would not reach the required transformation level for the next Promotion. Their path to greater power would be completely blocked off, and they would never be able to continue evolving!

Their strength would never increase!

No wonder. This is way too difficult. No mistakes are allowed. Maybe this is one of the main reasons all the peak Beyond Grade As can't step into the higher realm.

As long as one step went wrong, they would fall into an inescapable abyss. Terrifying…

However, after he thought about it, he gave up on planning not to level up for the sake of God's Trait Transformation Points.

With the existence of Mission Completion Cards, he could ignore all kinds of difficult Promotion Requirements.

Not enough points obtained through one Promotion?

Just go through Promotions more often!

Leveling up quickly was his biggest advantage. Although God's Trait Transformation was great, it was far from being as beneficial as the increase in strength he would obtain from Promotions.

Han Xiao's thoughts were clear.

It doesn't matter whether my God's Trait Transformation levels are high or not, as long as I'm stronger than everyone!

With the God's Trait Transformation information successfully obtained, the information about The First Sanctum shocked Han Xiao.

Even the dynasty did not know what it was!

I only knew that I got the Ability Fragment of [The First Sanctum] after Promotion because of the interface, but no other peak Beyond Grade As has that, so no one has discovered it, huh?

Han Xiao was stunned. As even the three Universal Civilizations did not have any related information, this might be a major new discovery.

What does Sanctum mean? It sounds like a place… If there's a first, is there a second or a third sanctum?

If only [Bold Explorer] could be used on this. Han Xiao sighed. This ability could only be used on unknown items and locations, not on the Ability Fragments in his interface.

Han Xiao put the communicator away and looked out the porthole. It was not the dark cosmic space but a bright sea of light.

This was a certain location in the center area of the Emerald Star Cluster, which had a large mass of bright, cloud-shaped nebulas mixed with both gas and dust. The gas released light due to the radiation of the Fixed Stars, while the nebulas reflected and refracted the light from relatively close Fixed Stars. The color of this entire area had a theme of mainly green and red. It looked beautiful and dreamlike.

In the universe, most areas were pitch black, so this beautiful scenery was considered rare.

The location where the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy will appear is in this mass of nebulas. I can start preparing now.

Han Xiao found a place and hid with the stealth mode of his spaceship activated, planning to only act at the right moment.

…

As the date of its appearance closed in, more and more fleets arrived at this nebula. They were all there for the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy.

Most of these organizations were ordinary organizations. Some planned to obtain it at all costs; some just wanted to try their luck. They guarded themselves against each other like they were deep behind enemy lines. However, when they saw the fleets of two Universal Civilizations arrive, their hearts sank.

Ravenlaude came with the dynasty's fleet, and although Psyker had only brought his own fleet, he had the church as his backer. The organizations present believed that he had been instructed to head there by the church.

With the interference of two Universal Civilizations, the chance of obtaining the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy became negligible, but no one wanted to back away in the final moment.

After all, they had traveled so far. Even if they might not get it, they had to try at the very least.

The Modo Civilization and some fleets from advanced civilizations, however, did not give up yet. Only two Beyond Grade As seemed to have interfered. If the two of them restrained each other, they felt like they would still have a chance.

"You guys improvise on the spot when to act later."

Inside the communication channel, Roddick reminded the elite force formed by many Calamity Grades.

On the other side, in the eyes of Ravenlaude and Psyker, all the other competitors were weaklings. They only saw each other as their biggest competitors.

Inside the main ship of the dynasty's fleet, Ravenlaude looked at Psyker's fleet from afar and narrowed his eyes.

"Psyker did not bring the church's fleet along, which means he did not report this to the church and wants to take it himself. Hehe, he's braver than me."

He had thought that this would be a piece of cake, but with another Beyond Grade A interfering, it became quite a bit more difficult.

However, Ravenlaude was not really nervous. His expression was rather relaxed.

Ravenlaude was confident in dealing with this seven-eyed freak. It would not be difficult for him to deal with Psyker.

For the sake of the Universal Treasure promised by the dynasty, Ravenlaude had to get the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy.

According to the current situation, he felt that he already had victory in his hands.

Comparatively, Psyker, who was in the opposing fleet, felt this would be rather difficult.

"Ravenlaude is here, too…"

Psyker's expression was not looking good.

The Calamity Grade who had provided the intelligence about the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy as a sign of loyalty said, "Your Excellency Star Pupil, the situation doesn't look very good for us…"

Psyker pulled out a smile and said, "Don't worry. It doesn't matter if we can't obtain it. I will still remember your contribution in providing me with this information."

He did not care about his own strength. His race's power was more important in comparison. He had always been looking for ways to create more talents in his race. He did not come to fight for the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy for himself to use but to find a suitable owner in his people and create a new strong individual for his race.

"I believe in you."

This Calamity Grade's face was filled with trust, but he was secretly plotting.

He did not really join under Psyker's command because of appreciation, nor was it because he had planned to. It was more like a coincidence.

With the information about the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy in his hands, he was not blinded by desire. He knew very well that he would never have a chance to get the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy with his own power, so he might as well use this information to find a backer and use their power to take part in this fight.

However, he did not completely give up either. If the person he joined obtained the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy and the opportunity presented itself, he would steal it. If there was no chance, he would just slowly work his way up, using the contribution he obtained by providing this information as a head start. This way, he would be able to fully utilize the value of this piece of intelligence, much better than being a gambler and putting all his chips on trying to get the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy.

Originally, his target candidate was not Psyker, but he met him coincidentally. After thinking about it, he realized that Psyker's forces were not weak, and Psyker was a Beyond Grade A, despite not being in the top tier, which actually increased the chance of him successfully stealing it if things went well. Therefore, he had changed his target and used Psyker as his backer.

Ravenlaude and Psyker both had their own goals, but they had yet to notice that in the remaining organizations, there was still another Beyond Grade A in a fleet without any organization symbols. It was Secret Master.

Both the dynasty and the church's people came…

Secret Master's eyes flickered.

He was stronger than both of them.

Since he was hidden, he decided to keep it that way. When the two of them had fought and wounded each other badly, he would then appear to grab the prize.

This plan is feasible, and the chances are high!

Secret Master stacked more stealth spells on himself and restrained the energy ripples around him, hiding himself to even a greater extent. He smiled coldly.

The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy must be mine!

…

Ravenlaude and Psyker's fleet were opposite each other. The rest of the organizations were not chased away, so without saying anything to each other, they all started to deploy inactive space stabilizing traps.

The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was a Primal Esper Ability Entity with independent thought. It had the ability to cross between secondary dimensions. The traps would prevent it from escaping once it discovered this ambush.

After this was completed, the various organizations waited in this area peacefully for the time being.

The date was near to begin with. After a few days, the day marked by the intelligence arrived.

The various organizations all focused their attention and stared at the area of the coordinates closely.

Other than a few individuals, most people there were not sure if the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy would even appear. They were waiting with anticipation and nervousness.

Buzz!

Before all those spectators, a ball of bright red energy suddenly overflowed from the void. Its size expanded extremely quickly and formed a red, fog-shaped cloud with a unique energy wave.

Seeing this, everyone there became thrilled!

"This is the right location. The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy has finally appeared!"

Chapter 1032: The Oriole

In the dreamlike nebula, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy returned from the secondary dimension and appeared in front of everyone's eyes.

This was an enormous cluster of bright red energy in the form of fog, like a boiling cloud. Gray lights flickered within like lightning. The energy at its center was the densest, and the further away from the center, the less dense the energy was. At its edge, red energy swayed and danced like silk. When looking closer, this energy seemed to be formed by countless tiny particles.

A large number of tiny red light clusters danced around the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. These were the sub-bodies the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy produced, something like its offspring or underlings. What Evans had once met was one of these.

The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was a Primal Esper Ability Entity. It had its independent consciousness. Most of its consciousness and energy had been hibernating, only leaving a small portion of its instincts to maintain daily activities. It gave up thinking to let itself wander the universe randomly.

This large cluster of bright red reflected in the pupils of the crew of every organization through the porthole, lighting up the surprise and excitement in their eyes.

"It appeared! Move, quickly!"

This time, all the organizations present activated the spacetime stabilization traps they had set earlier.

Buzz!

All the devices around were activated, as well as all kinds of magical runes and items.

The erupting spacetime energy expanded from different points like ripples, quickly flattening the 'folds' in this area. The spacetime became extremely stable. Be it hyperdrive or wormhole, they could no longer be used!

The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was very sensitive to the changes of the space. It instantly sensed the drastic change in the environment around it. Its hibernating consciousness awakened with shock. The enormous energy cloud suddenly retracted. It shrank, and its density increased at an extremely high rate, attempting to turn into a black hole to break the stable spacetime of this area and tear open a crack in space.

The space in the area was like a piece of paper, and the traps were like forces that stretched outward to make the paper straight and tight. The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy making itself extremely dense was an attempt to poke this piece of paper, concentrating its energy in one point to create a fold in space. These two forces were fighting each other. Under normal circumstances, this 'piece of paper' would have been penetrated immediately, but it would not be as easy in this highly stable space.

Seeing this, a voice appeared in the public area channel.

"Quickly contain the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. The spacetime coefficient is falling from the peak. If it keeps resisting, it will escape our trap sooner or later!"

The next moment, the closest small fleet immediately charged toward the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, which had already turned into an extremely bright cluster of light. The exterior armor of these spaceships slid open, showing a special mechanical device that released an astonishing absorption force toward the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy started to vibrate slightly. Waves of energy were pulled away from the cluster of light and sucked into the devices, like streams of light.

These organizations that had gone to fight for the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy had made thorough preparations. This was a device used to contain and restrain energy life forms. Even though the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy could condense itself, its energy would still be sucked out. It would be like a tug of war.

However, this time, without any warning, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy shot out a flurry of dense light beams, which bombarded this fleet.

The next second, their shields were penetrated, and their ships exploded into fireworks immediately. This fleet was annihilated by one round of attacks!

With the explosion of its energy, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy's psychic attribute was activated. Waves of impactful Psychic Currents appeared and expanded outward. The people who surrounded the Psychic Current all felt headaches, like they were affected by infrasound, as if they were heavily drunk.

Inside the dynasty's fleet, Ravenlaude saw this, and his lips curled up.

"Hehe, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy isn't something you can get without risks."

Primal Esper Ability Entities were extremely ancient. They were clusters of energy without owners. Therefore, they used their own methods to use their powers, such as shooting their energy out in beams continuously.

At this time, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy turned around and fled at an extremely high speed like a meteor. The fleets around immediately chased after, trying to block its path.

"Let me!"

Ravenlaude's eyes sparkled. He left his ship and chased after it with magic at high speed, simultaneously casting spells.

Runes and spells surrounded his body, shining with magical lights. Dense magic energy dragged down the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy and increased its speed drastically. At the same time, arcane impact waves were sent flying into the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, turning into magical runes controlled by Ravenlaude to mix foreign energy into the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, reducing its control over its own body.

The effect was clear. The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy could no longer maintain its condensed form, and the cluster of light exploded quickly, expanding back into an energy cloud cluster. Its hitbox multiplied countless times over.

Beyond Grade A Mages often travelled in secondary dimensions. Ravenlaude's experience in dealing with energy entities was way too rich, so it was no difficult task. The energy beam the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy shot out with all its might was easily blocked by him with magical shields.

As the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was gradually falling into Ravenlaude's hands, a powerful wave of psychic energy suddenly approached him from behind.

Ravenlaude narrowed his eyes, diverted his attention to use defensive spells, and blocked the psychic attack. Not far away, the silhouette quickly surpassed him and charged right toward the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. In its hands was a highly advanced enhanced version of the portable energy entity container.

"Humph, Psyker."

Without any more words, Ravenlaude launched attacks toward Psyker as well. The two of them fought while chasing after the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, dragging each other down.

The organizations around saw this and wanted to use it as an opportunity. However, any spaceship that even came close to the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was shattered by the 'fallout' of the battle between Beyond Grade As.

Ravenlaude had the upper hand and suppressed Psyker's attacks. However, despite the battle being rather intense, neither of them went all out. They did not forget about saving some energy to contain the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy.

With two Beyond Grade As present, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy would not be able to cause any trouble. Sealing runes were punched onto its body one after another. Its resistance grew weaker and weaker, gradually showing signs that it was about to be completely contained.

At the same time, the Modo Civilization's team was also wandering around the edge of the battlefield. The dozens of Calamity Grades in the ship stared closely at the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy and softly discussed possible tactics.

"Guys, the two of them are holding each other down. Should we act now?"

"The odds of success are too low. We will only be able to guard their attacks for a very short moment even with all of us working together. There won't be enough time for us to retreat. We will certainly have to sacrifice many lives. It's not worth it, is it?"

They exchanged looks and shook their heads in their minds.

Their boss had told them to improvise, but there was no opportunity at all. Although these Calamity Grades were usually quite proud, they had absolutely no confidence in facing Beyond Grade As. Even though they were truly loyal to the Modo Civilization, no one wanted to waste their life for nothing.

Roddick stayed silent in the communication channel for a while before saying, "If there's not a chance, forget it. Don't interfere."

Hearing this, the dozens of Calamity Grade relaxed their uptight bodies with relief.

Roddick was a little bit disappointed but was not too persistent about it. His original goal by sending so many Calamity Grades was to have the absolute upper hand in terms of power if there were no Beyond Grade As.

However, with the interference of Beyond Grade As, the mission had basically failed. Since there was no chance, the best choice was to retreat. There was no need to let the Calamity Grade elites of the civilization die in vain.

"This is just a side mission, no need to force it. The upper echelons will understand in cases like this. If I sacrifice many elites because of this, the upper echelons will even blame me for it."

Having this thought, Roddick loudly said, "Guys, retreat!"

"Roger!" Everyone responded with joy.

However, the next moment, a drastic change occurred!

The Modo Civilization's fleet suddenly turned around and charged right toward the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. Not only that, they suddenly fired all their weapons at Ravenlaude and Psyker!

Everyone present was completely stunned.

Even the battle between Ravenlaude and Psyker stopped as they had to block this sudden attack. Both of them looked a little confused.

T-they dared fire at us?

Who are these brave soldiers‽

Inside the command center at the base, Roddick's expression changed drastically. He yelled with rage, "What the hell are you doing? Are you out of your mind‽"

"We have lost control of our spaceships!" The many Calamity Grades were stupefied.

Roddick suddenly thought of something, and his face turned pale.

This familiar feeling…

It's Virtual Intrusion‽

*sshole!

With wrath and shock, Roddick was just about to yell at everyone to flee.

However, before he could, the remote communication link was cut off. The screen turned black, reflecting his furiously twisted expression.

"Black Star!"

Bang!

Roddick roared and smashed the communicator into pieces. The room was filled with his rage and helplessness.

The interference of a third party attracted enough attention. Both Ravenlaude and Psyker stopped fighting each other for a moment. Magic tides and psychic storms slammed directly into the Modo Civilization's fleet, swiftly eliminating the small fleet.

The dozens of Calamity Grades were panicking. They immediately fled their spaceships and scattered. However, Ravenlaude and Psyker did not enjoy letting people who suddenly attacked them go, so they chased after them.

The Calamity Grade elites, whom the Modo Civilization had spent tons of efforts to raise, lasted barely a moment before they fell one after another.

These people had no chance in fighting back; they could only run with their lives.

After more than eighty percent of Calamity Grades were eliminated. Only then did Ravenlaude and Psyker stop and return to fighting each other.

This intimidated the other organizations present. They all moved further away with their fleets and did not dare fight against the two of them for the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy.

The dynasty's fleet was not just watching. It was battling the Star Pupil Holy Race's fleet. In terms of both spaceship technology and size, the dynasty was superior. The Star Pupil Holy Race's fleet was slowly getting beaten.

"Still want to fight me?" Ravenlaude raised his brows and sent a voice message through a spell. "We can fight for days and nights, but your fleet will be wiped out. I've heard your people are very important to you. So, is the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy worth you sacrificing that many lives?"

Psyker sent out a tsunami-like wave of psychic energy to shatter the flying arcane bomb, clenched his teeth, and said, "Do you think you can make me give up with just a few words? Your dynasty's fleet will suffer quite a lot of losses too!"

"That's right, but those are the dynasty's soldiers. I don't care about their casualties," Ravenlaude said. "You won't be able to win against me, so don't make unnecessary sacrifices. As soon as I contain the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy and let my people disarm the space stabilization trap, I can leave this battlefield via a teleportation gate in an instant. Will you be able to chase me as a Psychic?"

Psyker looked to be conflicted. Then, he stopped fighting and turned around to help his fleet force the dynasty's fleet away.

Seeing this, Ravenlaude knew that Psyker had given up on competing and smiled with satisfaction. Without anyone standing in the way, he focused on casting sealing spells, sending countless arcane lights into the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy.

Very soon, a magical shield shrouded the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy and quickly shrank. The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was then sealed into the crystal magic ball in Ravenlaude's hands.

"It's done!"

Ravenlaude's eyes sparkled. He could almost see the Universal Treasure that the dynasty had promised waving at him.

Before he had time to feel the joy, the moment the sealing was complete, a mind spell that had been prepared for a very long time suddenly crashed into him and slammed into his mental barrier. With his mind shaken, Ravenlaude entered the state of being stunned for a short moment.

At the same time, a figure flew out from an ordinary fleet and approached at a very high speed, casting spells on the way. Magic arrays formed around Ravenlaude one after another, but countless blue magic tentacles appeared from these arrays and tightly tied Ravenlaude's body.

This was not just simply tying him up. The official name of this spell was [Descent of Atomte—Devil's Tentacles]. It was a top tier spell that had a short silence effect on Mages, as well as the ability to restrain their soul. Once tied up, the target would enter an even longer period of immobility, unable to control their body.

"There's another Beyond Grade A‽" Psyker, who was not far away, sensed the energy wave that had suddenly erupted and turned around in shock.

Ravenlaude finally regained consciousness. Absolutely shocked, he hastily tried to escape the restraints.

However, this silhouette had already come right beside him, taken away the magic ball sealing the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, and pressed his palm onto Ravenlaude's chest.

Powerful and rich magic energy gushed out and turned into a violet beam of light, immediately blowing Ravenlaude far away.

This attack did not cause much damage. Ravenlaude flew a short distance back and quickly regained his balance. He looked up with shock. Seeing this person covered in tattoos, his expression stiffened for a second.

"It's you, Secret Master!"

Given how small the Beyond Grade A circle was, famous Beyond Grade As all knew each other. Secret Master's position in the circle was a little higher than his.

Secret Master's expression was cold. He did not care about Ravenlaude, who was conflicted with rage and fear. He sized up the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy in his hands, nodded, and said with the same indifferent face, "Thanks for helping me to contain the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. I let you safekeep it for me for a few seconds. Now, it's returned to its original owner."

Ravenlaude was so furious he laughed. "I thought Black Star is the most shameless among Beyond Grade As. I didn't expect you to be not much worse. What return to its original owner? Since when were you the owner of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy?"

"I'm here, so it's mine," Secret Master said coldly.

Angered, Ravenlaude said, "Cut the cr*p. You think you can just leave?"

With the opportunity to gain a Universal Treasure right before his eyes, even if Secret Master was stronger, Ravenlaude would not give up easily.

Secret Master glanced at him and said with a poker face, "I can leave whenever I want."

The moment his sentence ended, a huge crack suddenly appeared on the space stabilization traps in the area, and some of the devices even exploded. While they were setting up the traps, Secret Master had secretly planted invisible, remote-controlled explosion runes so that he could use a teleportation spell after he succeeded.

The spacetime coefficient and the effect of the traps plummeted, no longer able to stop Beyond Grade A space magic. Ravenlaude's expression changed drastically as he immediately understood what Secret Master's plan was. He quickly started to channel spells to restrict Secret Master's teleportation.

However, Secret Master was even quicker. He had prepared the fundamentals of the teleportation gate well in advance, so it activated instantly. A blue vortex appeared right beside him.

Seeing Ravenlaude fast approaching, Secret Master was completely calm.

"Till next time, Ra… hmm‽"

Suddenly, he felt his hand become heavier. The sealing container of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy in his hands disappeared, replaced by a mechanical arm that was connected to a human-shaped machine with flickering blue-gold eyes, which had appeared beside him out of nowhere.

"You…" Shock finally appeared on Secret Master's face.

This machine tilted its head and suddenly vibrated. A strange Void Energy expanded instantly and shrouded a large area, including even Ravenlaude.

The next second, Secret Master and Ravenlaude realized that the space in this area had become thick and dense. Their movements were forcefully slowed.

Void Prison!

With a flash of insight, Ravenlaude immediately recalled the owner of this ability. "Black Star‽"

Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar turned to look at him and smiled. "Yo, you recognized me?"

"You've come at the right time!" Ravenlaude was overjoyed. He thought that Han Xiao was secret backup sent by the dynasty.

Han Xiao saw through what he was thinking immediately and shook his head. "I'm not here for the dynasty."

Ravenlaude's smile stiffened.

He immediately understood. Unlike him, Black Star was not fighting for the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy for the dynasty but had uncovered this information himself and wanted to obtain it.

This way, although Black Star was also a dynasty ally, he was his competitor in this matter.

Having realized that, Ravenlaude's heart sank a little.

At the same time, Secret Master narrowed his eyes. Having all his effort go to waste made him embarrassed and enraged. He coldly said, "Black Star, you took my Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy?"

Han Xiao turned to look at him and smiled.

"To borrow your words… thank you for safekeeping it for me for a few seconds."

He had been there for a long time. His Lord's Avatar and mechanical army had hidden nearby, watching the whole thing while messing with the Modo Civilization.

Only when Secret Master broke the space stabilization trap and was about to leave did the Lord's Avatar finally find the right opportunity to strike. It immediately used [Void Swap] to exchange itself with the sealed container holding the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. Thus, the container was in the hands of his mechanical army.

However, this way, the energy ripple would cause the mechanical army to be exposed as well. To avoid the two of them from chasing after the mechanical army, he had used his Lord's Avatar to activate Void Prison immediately to restrain Secret Master and Ravenlaude, while the mechanical army could leave with the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy.

Once they returned to the safe area, it would be a complete success.

As the mantis stalked the cicada, it was unaware of the oriole behind it. Secret Master thought that he was the oriole, but he did not know that Han Xiao had hidden even deeper than him.

"The only problem is…"

Han Xiao turned to look at Psyker, who was far away. This guy was not in the range of the Void Prison, so he could chase if he wanted to.

Noticing Han Xiao's stare, Psyker's expression looked as if he had just fallen into a pile of feces.

This time, the voice of a Star Pupil Holy Race officer sounded in the communication network.

"Leader, we have detected a mechanical army that has suddenly appeared. It is escorting the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy and fleeing at high speed. Shall we chase after it?"

"No, retreat!"

Having seen Han Xiao, Psyker backed away without hesitation.

He did not want to have a direct conflict with Black Star at this time.

Most importantly, even if Black Star's mechanical army had no Lord's Avatar in it, he felt that he still might not be able to win.

Han Xiao could not help but scratch his head and laugh in his mind.

He's this smart‽

He then looked at Secret Master, who had a troubled look and was full of hostility, and stretched his neck.

"I shall take the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy with a smile. If you're not happy about that… how about I give your bones a good stretch?"

Chapter 1033: Secret Master, I Have Never Seen Someone This Unlucky

Faced with Han Xiao's tease, Secret Master's face sank, and he was too lazy to respond. His eyes looked past Han Xiao at the streams of light heading away from the edge of the battlefield.

Very soon, the exposed mechanical army separated some of its units to escort the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy and disappeared from sight.

His mood slipped from the top of the mountain to the bottom.

He wanted to chase after it, but Black Star's Lord's Avatar stood in his way and gave off a vibe that made him subconsciously uptight. He knew that as soon as he did anything, he would inevitably face a storm of attacks.

Secret Master's eyes refocused on Han Xiao, who was before him, carefully sizing him up. He then said with a somewhat interested but mostly unsatisfied tone, "Black Star, this should be the second time we've met, right?"

"Including the Meeting of the Gods, it is indeed the second time." Han Xiao nodded.

"Humph, then we're… quite… fated!" Secret Master said word by word.

He was irritated and angry about the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy getting stolen, but everyone was there to fight for it, so it all depended on their strength. It belonged to anyone who could obtain it; he could accuse Han Xiao of nothing.

He really wanted the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. Although it had been taken away by Black Star, there was no need to make too much of a fuss. They were both famous people in the universe. If he could not get the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, so be it. If he made it a bigger deal than it was, it would not look good for anyone, nor was it necessary.

However, there was no way he would just retreat like that; he had to fight back in some way. Secret Master did not want to watch Han Xiao easily get away; it would look like he was afraid of Han Xiao. He had shame, unlike that seven eyes beside him who was already used to it.

He secretly tried a teleportation spell and realized that it was restricted by the Void Prison.

When this area is no longer locked, there's still a chance to catch up to the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy through teleportation and snatch it back, Secret Master thought as he adjusted his mood, putting his focus on the current situation and suppressing his anger. His expression returned to being cold, and he started chatting.

"By the way, I've always been curious about you. Although we did not have much contact in the past, I've always had a strong impression of you."

"Strong in what way?" Han Xiao did not mind wasting time. It was what he wanted too.

"Your deeds are spread all across the universe. In my eyes, you're a careerist with a grand plan, as well as an opportunist. Luck is a very big reason you were able to build what you've built today. It helped you choose the right opportunities and brought you the chance to develop this quickly. You're a lucky man."

Hearing his words, Han Xiao could not help but glance at Secret Master a few more times.

This is the first time anyone has ever said I'm lucky. You've probably got the wrong person…

Nonetheless, he could understand why Secret Master had this kind of impression of him. To the outside world, his rise was extremely quick and fierce, as well as smooth. There were so many opportunities that seemed to have just fallen onto his laps, which all looked like it was because of his luck.

However, these opportunities were created by him instead of this 'luck', all because he was familiar with the direction the world would take and had information about the future that no one else had.

But no one would ever know that.

"I guess you can say that I'm lucky," Han Xiao agreed as a joke.

"Hehe, but from today onward, your luck ends." Magic runes appeared in the depths of Secret Master's pupils. "You should've heard my nickname. I can control someone's luck."

Seeing his confidence, Han Xiao felt strange but continued to cooperate with his performance.

"Are you trying to reduce my luck permanently?"

Secret Master snorted. "You took what's mine; you'll have to pay for it."

Actually, he was not very willing to mess with Han Xiao. After all, after the Meeting of the Gods, Han Xiao's position was rather special within the Beyond Grade A circle. As a neutral Beyond Grade A, it was best not to mess with him if there was no need.

However, he could not put up with this, even just for the sake of saving his own face. Therefore, he decided to use his best trick to slightly punish Han Xiao.

So, it still came to speaking with fists… Han Xiao had expected this. He did not think that Secret Master would let this go easily.

The next moment, blinding magical blue light shone from Secret Master's body.

"They all say you're good at fighting. Let me see how strong you are personally."

The magic energy in his body gushed out like a roaring tide, erupting in an instant.

Boom!

Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar was washed away by the exploding magical energy and was pushed back some distance.

Secret Master took the opportunity to back away, trying to increase the distance between Han Xiao and himself. However, after the enhancement of God's Trait Transformation, the effect of Void Prison was stronger and slowed down the people in it even more. This ability could not differentiate friend or foe, but Han Xiao, who had Void Race talents, could move freely within.

He realized very soon that he was not able to get away from Han Xiao no matter how much he backed off, so he decided to just not move at all. He started to cast spells continuously like a spell cannon.

In order to snatch the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, the Lord's Avatar had used Void Swap to swap places with the sealing container, which led to it being isolated and only being able to fight with Secret Master alone. The mechanical army was on the way.

Bang!

Beams of blue magical energy dragged along lightning trails and rocketed toward Han Xiao continuously, shattering into sparks on the Lord's Avatar's shield.

Without the mechanical army, Han Xiao clearly had a firepower problem. Therefore, he decided to charge forward against the sea of spells and close the distance while Secret Master could not back away.

After this Promotion, his Strength and Dexterity attributes could be considered high even among Beyond Grade As. When facing a Mage with his Lord's Avatar, close-range combat instead became the better option for him.

While one side stood in place, the other approached extremely quickly. The distance between them shortened in no time.

In Han Xiao's eyes, Secret Master's huge face was getting closer.

"Eat my rocket headbutt!"

Activating critical strike abilities, Han Xiao smashed his head directly forward.

Clank!

His metal forehead landed right on Secret Master's head through his magic shield.

Secret Master felt a buzzing in his head immediately, like someone was ringing a bell in his head. He hastily regained focus. The rune enchantments on his body suddenly all lit up, and hundreds of hands appeared beside him, creating afterimages of punches everywhere.

As a Mage, it was only logical to have some close-range combat abilities.

Having been suppressed in close-range combat, Secret Master was secretly shocked. Such powerful blows.

He had sparred with quite a number of Pugilists before, and he realized that Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar's close combat strength was even stronger than some Beyond Grade A Pugilists. The storm-like attacks were very difficult for him to hold on. He was stunned by Han Xiao's strength.

Black Star feels stronger than rumors say…

This thought only flashed for an instant before disappearing. Secret Master focused on the matter at hand and diverted his attention to do two things at once. He dealt with Han Xiao's fierce close-range attacks while controlling his magic energy to build up to his best Secret Studies spell that was aimed at one's luck.

Luck was originally formless and almost superficial, but at this moment, in Secret Master's vision, blurry fog suddenly appeared around every life form. Some fog clouds were thick, and some were thin.

This was Secret Master's unique spell. It combined the study of the soul, mind, foresight, fortune telling, and many more magic fields. He was successfully able to quantify the target's luck. The thickness of the fog represented the luck of a being.

The luckier one was, the thicker the fog would be. Those protagonist-type charters who had Luck Glows usually had the thickest fog.

"Let me see how strong your luck is!"

Secret Master had made up his mind to reduce Han Xiao's luck.

When he looked closely, he was completely stupefied.

Usually, Beyond Grade As were very lucky people. For them to reach this territory at the top of the universe, there was at least a minimum to how unlucky they could be. Black Star's luck should have been exceptionally strong; he should have been covered in thick fog.

However, the real situation was the complete opposite. The fog around Black Star was so thin that it was almost non-existent!

Secret Master had observed countless people before, but this was the first time he had ever seen someone this unlucky! He could hardly believe his own eyes!

It doesn't make sense! How can a Beyond Grade A's luck be this weak‽

How can someone this unlucky become a Beyond Grade A‽

Secret Master was completely stunned.

Initially, he wanted to damage Black Star's luck, but now that he looked at it…

Can this guy's luck even be decreased‽

Secret Master's many unique spells revolved around indirectly dealing large amounts of spiritual damage through decreasing the target's luck, but facing Han Xiao… he realized that his trump card seemed useless.

For an instant, he lost concentration and immediately showed flaws mid-combat. Han Xiao did not care about his internal thoughts at all and seized the opportunity.

Bang bang bang!

Lightning-fast punches landed on Secret Master's body quickly, sending in waves of impact.

Being badly beaten up, many defensive runes on Secret Master's body shattered. Feeling the pain, Secret Master did not dare let himself get distracted again. He took a defensive stance and held on under Han Xiao's attacks.

While the two of them fought intensely, Ravenlaude, who was also included in the range of the Void Prison, felt conflicted.

Normally, Ravenlaude would help the dynasty's ally, but now, Black Star was also a competitor who was fighting for the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy.

"I can only complete the mission and gain a Universal Treasure if I take the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy back from Han Xiao's hands."

After some thought, Ravenlaude made his decision and started to cast spells to cancel out the effects of the Void Prison.

"Hmm?" Sensing the disturbance, Han Xiao turned around and gave Ravenlaude a death stare.

"Don't look at me. I'm just executing the dynasty's mission."

Ravenlaude noticed Han Xiao's stare and nervously replied. Then, he silently tried to break away from the Void Prison together with Secret Master.

The next second, the Void Prison was broken. The space around returned to normal. While the two of them fought, Ravenlaude opened a teleportation gate immediately and disappeared, heading toward the mechanical army, which was escorting the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy away.

Seeing this, Secret Master wanted to do the same. However, the Lord's Avatar prevented him from doing so.

The rest of Han Xiao's machinery had now arrived. They activated space stabilizing devices and magic disruption devices that covered this area, stopping the use of teleportation spells once again, causing Secret Master to be unable to chase after the Prime Chaos Mysterious Energy.

"Sh*t!" Secret Master's face sank even further. This situation basically meant that he was already eliminated from this competition.

Furthermore, Secret Master could see that Black Star actually had a way to stop Ravenlaude too. Only, he purposely let Ravenlaude go but kept him there.

He's targeting me specifically‽

That's too much!

Seeing Secret Master's expression, Han Xiao chuckled. "You noticed I've let Ravenlaude on purpose? I'm not targeting you but him."

He had purposely let Ravenlaude go and given him a chance to chase after his mechanical army because he wanted to make Ravenlaude a target to showcase his fists.

Due to the unhappiness last time, Han Xiao wanted to showcase more of his strength to the dynasty, but he did not want the outside world to know he had grown once again, in case the Mechanic Emperor sought him out again. Therefore, he wanted to shift the battlefield and not have witnesses.

A dynasty ally was the best target for that.

Compared to beating up enemies, beating up teammates seems better when creating a reputation? After all, after getting beaten up, his teammate still had to hide the information of the battle.

Although the Lord's Avatar stayed to hold Secret Master back, all the Apostle Weapons were in the escort team.

With all that and the mechanical army, it would be strong enough even without him present.

Diverting forces and fighting in multiple battles at the same time was the Beyond Grade A Mechanic fighting method.

Chapter 1034: Duel

Psyker was scared away by Black Star, Secret Master was held back by the Lord's Avatar, and Ravenlaude teleported to chase after the mechanical army. The situation of the battle changed multiple times in a short period. The fleets of the other organizations present became mere onlookers.

At this point, these organizations knew full well that the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy would have nothing more to do with them.

They were somewhat disappointed but not surprised. A few days back, when they realized that the dynasty and church had interfered in this, they knew that their chances were negligible.

However, being able to confirm that the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy had appeared in the Emerald Star Cluster, as well as having the opportunity to watch a battle between many Beyond Grade As, most of them felt it was worth the trip.

Although the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was taken away by Black Star, they did not disperse immediately but took out their snacks to watch the wrestling between Black Star and Secret Master.

Only a few organizations who had yet to give up wanted to chase after the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, but they were stopped by the mechanical army. Looking at the dense psionic barrels, these people could only remain there with resignation.

While the Lord's Avatar led the mechanical army to fight Secret Master, the dynasty's fleet responded as well and immediately reported Black Star's interference in this battle. This got to the man in charge of this operation, an upper echelon of the dynasty's hawk faction, Bekorodi.

"Black Star is there too? And he got it‽"

Far away in the remote command center inside the dynasty's territory, Bekorodi's eyes opened so wide that they almost popped out. He was shocked and enraged.

"His Excellency Ravenlaude is already chasing after it. He will probably have a direct conflict with Black Star. What should we do?" the fleet's commander asked cautiously.

Hearing this, Bekorodi frowned heavily. He was filled with hesitation.

He felt that this matter was very difficult to deal with. Black Star was an important ally to the dynasty. Usually, the two sides should avoid conflict as much as possible.

However, before this, the dynasty did not know that Black Star would interfere with this, which made Bekorodi rather worried.

With the dynasty's control of the Flickering World, somehow, they did not notice that Black Star had sent a team out to that place. This showed that the Black Star Army had secretly built quite a number of things in the Flickering World by making use of the dynasty's support.

Bekorodi felt that in situations like this, Black Star should be the one to take a step back first. However, Black Star clearly saw that the dynasty was involved, yet he still took part in the battle. To Bekorodi, this was Black Star not giving the dynasty's face, which made a hawk faction upper echelon like him rather unhappy.

Undoubtedly, he felt that the situation was all Black Star's fault, so he was in a dilemma.

Should he continue the operation while taking the risk of offending Black Star or back off and give up the plan?

"Sir, should we contact the Ruler?"

While pondering, his subordinate's voice pulled Bekorodi out of his train of thought. He paused then said with a deep voice, "Don't notify the Ruler yet. Contact Black Star first. I'll talk to him."

He knew that Urranrell liked Black Star, so he did not want to notify her. He could only control the mission if he dealt with it himself.

The command center called up Black Star's number. It rang three times before it was picked up. Han Xiao's face appeared on the screen with a meaningful smile.

"Not bad, not bad, you contacted me earlier than I expected."

Bekorodi's eyes twitched. He suppressed his anger, forced out a smile, and said, "Black Star, remember me? I'm Bekorodi."

"Hello, we meet again. Have you eaten?"

"Just had dinner."

"You look quite well. Have you been sleeping well recently? You're not young anymore, so don't work so hard. Rest more."

"I'm used to working hard, just can't seem to be too free. After so many years, I've gotten used to working every day long ago, but I have indeed been getting rather good sleep recently. I…"

Halfway through speaking, Bekorodi suddenly stopped.

He only just noticed that without knowing, he had followed Han Xiao's lead and actually subconsciously started chattering, almost forgetting what he wanted to say in this call.

Plus, we're not even close! Black Star, are you trying to play for time?

Bekorodi coughed heavily, trying to cover up the awkwardness. He then quickly gained back control and questioned, "You know why I've called you, don't you? It's a surprise you've had your eyes on the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy too. This information came from EsGod's heritage. You should have notified the dynasty or at least reported your actions. If you'd done that, the accidents today would have been totally avoided. Why didn't you?"

Han Xiao's expression looked strange, as if he was saying, What kind of question is that?

"Doesn't not notifying you guys mean that I want it for myself? Plus, I don't seem to recall that I'm obligated to give all the intelligence I have to the dynasty or report my personal activities. We're allies, not employer and employee."

Bekorodi made a serious expression and said, "Anyway, there's no need for discussion on this matter. Listen to me. The dynasty doesn't want the outside world to see us fight with our allies. This needs a solution."

"It's simple then—give up. Give the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy to me, and it's done." Han Xiao smiled.

"Impossible," Bekorodi said subconsciously, but he then realized that his tone was not very appropriate, so he calmed down. "The dynasty needs the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy too. We won't let it go so easily."

"What do you need the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy for?" Han Xiao was curious.

Bekorodi shut up immediately.

It was not like he could tell Black Star the truth and say that it was to replicate the Evolution Cube's abilities.

They wanted the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy to make Gaud grow quicker and step into the Beyond Grade A territory sooner. The goal of that was to analyze the Evolution Cube. Gaud would only be able to analyze the Evolution Energy with his Esper Ability if he was Beyond Grade A.

After quite some time, Bekorodi finally forced the words "It's confidential…" out of his mouth.

"Never mind then." Han Xiao shook his head. "Anyway, I won't just back off like this. It's true that we're allies, but I can't possibly give everything to you once you just tell me to do so. Even those Ultimate Knowledges required me to make contributions to gain access to them. You can't just ask me to give selflessly, can you?"

Bekorodi nodded. "Okay, then let's make a deal. We're willing to exchange for the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. What do you want? Intelligence? Knowledge? Resources? A Universal Treasure? I'm guessing you want the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy probably because you want to turn it into a Universal Treasure, so you might as well exchange it with us. You can choose from the list we gave you last time. I can approve this deal personally."

The dynasty had to give Ravenlaude a Universal Treasure to hire him to start with, so since the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was now in Black Star's hands, Bekorodi just made the same deal with Black Star.

The deal with Ravenlaude, of course, would no longer be valid. He would at most receive some resources as compensation…

Ravenlaude, who was still chasing the mechanical army, did not yet know that his employer had already given up hope on him and that the Universal Treasure he had been thinking of was basically out of his reach.

Han Xiao raised his brows. "And what if you go back on your word?"

"If you agree, I'll make Ravenlaude retreat first, and you can keep the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy for the time being. Then, you will make a public announcement to eliminate the rumors caused by this conflict. Following that, you can exchange it for a Universal Treasure with us. Therefore, you don't have to worry that we won't keep up our side of the deal."

Bekorodi did not plan to play any tricks at all. He at least had this much pride as a superior in the dynasty.

However, Han Xiao did not plan to agree immediately…

If my teammate runs away, who do I beat up?

"We'll talk about this next time. I have yet to decide if I want to give you guys or not. I need to think about it. Therefore, for now, let's just compete fairly… Since you don't want the outside world to know, we'll fight in a place where there's no one else." Han Xiao's tone was calm, and he did not completely reject the deal.

Bekorodi's face stiffened. He was very annoyed.

He did not want to waste any more time and gave a simple "okay". He then ended the call. He told his subordinate to notify Ravenlaude that he had to obtain the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy.

In his mind, Han Xiao's original body was still in Black Star Palace, and only a Lord's Avatar and a group of mechanical troops were there. Secret Master was restraining the Lord's Avatar, so Ravenlaude should still have a chance.

…

Inside the bright nebula, Ravenlaude chased after the fleeing mechanical army, getting further away from the battlefield that the Lord's Avatar was in and out of everyone's sight.

Without the restrictions of the space stabilization devices, Ravenlaude's teleportation spells were quicker. No matter how fast the mechanical troops were running, he could catch up in an instant. He had only slowly followed behind all this time because he wanted to get further away from the Lord's Avatar so that it would not be able to interfere with his battle.

After all, whether the Lord's Avatar was present or not would make a bit of difference. He did not want to face the Lord's Avatar's attacks with his body like Secret Master. After all…

I'm a proper Mage! I'm like paper!

Remote artillery style is our forte. Melee combat? How can you call yourself a Mage‽

That Secret Master, who drew all over his body, had quite strong melee combat power, but Ravenlaude was an old fashioned Mage who had mastered pure arcane arts. To make him fight in melee range would be the same as Mechanics rushing into Pugilists' arms… Hmm, except for Black Star.

This is far enough.

Ravenlaude focused his mind and used another teleportation spell. He appeared right before the mechanical troops. With a wave of his hand, a top-tier magic staff appeared and hovered above his head. The gem at the top of the staff shone with a bright magical light.

The next moment, thick magical books appeared one after another around Ravenlaude, circling him slowly like a ring of stars and giving off powerful magical energy.

As the magical books opened and the pages turned extremely quickly, a thick and enormous purple magic light appeared and expanded instantly, turning into a spherical, dark-purple energy barrier that shrouded all the mechanical troops before him. The sphere was extremely large.

Looking from inside, the inside wall of this sphere was dark purple covered in circulating streams of bright blue and flaming white magical streams of light, like arcane comets. It looked like a purple curtain decorated with blue and white patterns.

"Wall of Tragal—Dark Purple Arena. This is a new forbidden spell created by my spell research team."

After casting this spell, Ravenlaude smiled with confidence as if the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was already in his hands.

The Mechanical Force lightning on the mechanical troops suddenly became much weaker. They fired at the wall, but the psionic cannon attacks disappeared when landing on the inside of this sphere like they were absorbed. Some mechanical soldiers flew to the edges, but the moment they touched the inside wall, a bright arcane explosion repelled the mechanical soldiers away.

Ravenlaude was certain that the mechanical troops could not escape. In a situation like this, the villain soul lying deep inside his body started to boil. He started to perform the signature move of a villain—explain!

"This is a forbidden-level sealing spell. It can absorb the energy attacks inside it and transfer it to its outside. At the same time, it prevents any material from passing through its wall. Your mechanical troops won't be able to escape. Furthermore, this spell can also reduce the efficiency of energy transmission. Haven't you noticed? The Mechanical Force you applied on them has become weaker."

He was having a good time talking, but the mechanical troops ignored him and continued to physically attack the inside wall, getting repelled away time after time.

Seeing this, Ravenlaude shook his head and smiled. He slowly said, "Stop wasting your time, Black Star. I know you can hear my voice. Let's discuss this."

After a few seconds, the mechanical troops gave up trying, turned to look at him, and opened the area communication channel. Han Xiao's voice appeared.

"Discuss what?"

"Black Star, I respect your strength, but your Lord's Avatar isn't here. If you fight me, you'll only waste these troops. So, why not just give me the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy? I'll remember this favor I owe you and give you enough compensation. You know, we're allies; we don't have to solve the problem with violence."

Ravenlaude smiled faintly and felt that he was giving Black Star a lot of face.

However, only inexperienced youngsters would give up their own profit because of a few kind words. Although Han Xiao was considered basically a baby in terms of age among the Beyond Grade As, his experience in life was far from being this immature. He was completely unaffected and immediately ordered the mechanical troops to fire.

Tu tu tu tu!

The mechanical troops surrounded Ravenlaude and fired at him immediately. However, Ravenlaude was prepared. Multiple layers of arcane shields protected him while he moved at a high speed to dodge attacks. Offensive spells were thrown out from his hands continuously, bombarding the mechanical troops.

The size of this sphere was extremely large, giving Ravenlaude enough space to kite. In addition, his mobility provided by teleportation could keep the battle at medium range, so it would be a battle of cannon fires and spells.

"The goal isn't to destroy the mechanical army. It's best to leave after getting the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy."

While shooting spells at the mechanical army, Ravenlaude noted the location of the mechanical soldier that was escorting the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy.

Suddenly, the formation of the mechanical army showed a flaw. There was a gap in the protection of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy for an instant, and he noticed it immediately.

"Chance!"

Ravenlaude cast a spell that he had already prepared long ago. An invisible shockwave shot out and divided the mechanical army. He cast another teleportation spell, which was also prepared beforehand, immediately appearing beside the mechanical soldier escorting the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. A purple hand formed of arcane energy grabbed toward the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy contained right before his eyes.

At this moment, a dark blue tint of light suddenly appeared at the edge of his sights. The sharp feeling it gave off made his hair stand on end.

In an instant, Ravenlaude hastily retracted his abdomen to dodge the light. A white spear covered in a gold pattern and surrounded by dark blue energy easily tore open all his shields, slipping right past his vital spot under his abdomen. He was suddenly covered in cold sweat.

That was close, almost lost my offspring.

Psionic Prime, who had been lying in wait among the army for a long time, twisted his spear, shooting out an energy wave and directly slapping Ravenlaude away!

The Psionic Prime Spear was his 'Life Weapon', which appeared when he became an Apostle Weapon. It had a silver-orange Grade, and it would become stronger together with the Apostle Weapon.

At this point, the Psionic Prime Spear had many new characteristics. When used by Psionic Prime himself, these characteristics would be enhanced. It was a terrifying close- to mid-range weapon in his hands that could easily penetrate most shields. Ravenlaude's magic shield was like paper in front of the Psionic Prime Spear.

Psionic Prime shook his spear and chased right after Ravenlaude, not letting go of the opportunity that he had gained by suddenly attacking. As he caught up in no time, he immediately used a smooth Mechanical Pugilist combo on him, not giving Ravenlaude any time to catch his breath.

Not long after, Ravenlaude once again felt a strong sense of danger behind him. A few more hidden Apostle Weapons charged toward him at close range. They were all good at close combat, such as Mad Sky Hunter, Purple Sky Spirit, and Heaven-Suppressing Banner. They forced Ravenlaude to not have the time to use teleport to increase the distance between them.

Other than Apostle Weapons that had usual sizes such as Giant King Kong, all the other Apostle Weapons were there and had been hiding among the mechanical troops. Now, they finally all struck. Psionic Prime led some of them to fight at close range while Silver Flash led the other ones to attack from a distance. They cooperated perfectly.

With the success of the surprise attack, Ravenlaude was stuck being passive.

With Han Xiao's Mechanical Force enhancement, every single one of these Apostle Weapons had Beyond Grade A strength. Now that Han Xiao had gone through another Promotion, his machinery-related abilities were strengthened again, so the strength of his Apostle Weapons had increased as well. Even just one could fight with a normal Beyond Grade A for a long time… and it went without saying whom this referred to.

'Dueling' more than a dozen of Apostle Weapons with this kind of strength at the same time… Ravenlaude could hardly hold on.

There were no tricks to get out of this. It was a complete difference in raw strength. The situation quickly turned one sided.

I can't even beat a medium-sized mechanical army without a Lord's Avatar? Has his strength already grown to this level‽

Ravenlaude clenched his teeth and endured the fierce attacks from these more than ten Apostle Weapons. The magic energy in his body flew out like a broken dam. His heart was filled with disbelief and helplessness that sank deep into his bones.

Feeling the state he was in now, Ravenlaude could fully confirm one thing—Black Star had become stronger again!

At this time, he suddenly recalled his experience against the Mechanic Emperor many years ago…

This was how it felt!

So strong that even a Beyond Grade A like him was afraid!

Chapter 1035: Beat Up My Teammate

This was not the first time Han Xiao had fought with a Mage. Every Beyond Grade A Mage had their own style and a different way of fighting.

Ravenlaude was one of the Ancient Ones. Although, due to his limited potential, he had already reached the top of his strength and would not be able to become a peak Beyond Grade A, in his long life, he had learned countless spells. The Arcane Institute under his command was an organization used to study and invent new spells for him. In this fight, he had showcased his extremely broad knowledge in the study of magic.

As an Ancient One as well, 'Dragon King' Milizaus' style had very clear differences. Milizaus focused on the powerful dragon magic spells, fighting with raw strength in a straight forward style, while Ravenlaude had endless spells to swiftly deal with all kinds of situations.

Every Beyond Grade A had their specialty. Facing such a disadvantageous situation, although Ravenlaude was suppressed by the Apostle Weapons, he gradually used his ever-changing spell combos to give himself some breathing space, which was followed up by a combo he had prepared for a very long time.

With a flash of the gem on his staff, silk-like rings made of runes appeared around him. Purple arcane energy started spinning and quickly expanded into a tornado. The violent energy blew the nearby Apostle Weapons away, creating a short opportunity to cast more spells. Ravenlaude was in the storm eye. With the change of his hand sign, the arcane storm swiftly condensed into thousands of magic arrows hovering around him. The highly concentrated arcane energy almost looked solid as if they had turned into transparent purple crystals.

"Secret Ability—Arcane Nova Arrow Rain!"

The purple crystal-like arrows shot out in all directions into the mechanical army, causing clusters of bright purple arcane energy explosions.

Boom boom boom boom!

Impact wave rippled and expanded, blowing away tons of mechanical soldiers. At the same time, the vibration of magic particles caused many mechanical soldiers to become immobilized. This ability had both damage and control effects in a large range.

Ravenlaude did not stop there. He waved his hand, a magic book suddenly appeared and flipped open. All of its shining pages danced and turned into a circular turning light belt, creating a white secondary dimension entrance that expanded rapidly behind him. The entrance was expanding to several thousand meters wide.

Ohm!

An enormous quadrangle tower tip that looked like it was made of crystal extended out from the tunnel, slowly showing its full appearance. It was clearly a magnificent magic building.

High Grade Arcane Spell—Mage Pagoda Summoning!

"He's summoning his Mage Pagoda. Stop him!" Psionic Prime's eyes flickered. He stopped himself from being blown away and charged forward once again.

The Mage Pagoda was the core equipment of high-level Mages. A Mage with and without the Mage Pagoda would be on two completely different levels. A Mage would only reach full strength when fighting alongside the Mage Pagoda.

For example, Austin's Palace of Hidden Spells was a gold Grade Mage Pagoda, which not only gave him extremely powerful enhancements but also exceptional mobility.

The cost of Mage Pagodas that could be stored in a secondary dimension and summoned anytime was extremely expensive. Usually, when a Mage summoned their Mage Pagoda, it meant that they had decided to stand their ground and fight on that spot. This was because most Mage Pagodas did not have as strong teleportation powers as the Palace of Hidden Spells.

A Mage Pagoda was a trump card. Since it had been summoned, it meant that Ravenlaude was no longer holding back. He was going all out.

"Black Star, you're indeed stronger than me… but it won't be that easy to defeat me!"

Ravenlaude bit his lip. His pride as a Beyond Grade A was harmed, and his will to fight was flaming.

The mechanical army immediately activated the space stabilization device. However, inside the Dark Purple Arena, the thick magic energy weakened its effects. Ravenlaude was also doing all he could to keep the summoning portal stable.

The Mage Pagoda extended out bit by bit. Silver Flash and the mechanical army shifted the target of the long-range attacks to the Mage Pagoda. Large defensive runes appeared on the Mage Pagoda to protect it, like a translucent purple light energy shield. It stopped the bombardment and vibrated nonstop as explosions and sparks erupted on its surface.

Ravenlaude used his magic energy at maximum capacity. Dark purple light glowed from his body. In the process of summoning the Mage Pagoda, his mobility would be reduced tremendously. The thick layers of arcane shields protected his casting from being interrupted.

Suddenly, the space behind him rippled. Mad Sky Hunter, who had a short distance teleportation ability, teleported right inside the shields. With his sharp blades and teeth, he pounced right at Ravenlaude.

In the blink of an eye, Ravenlaude hastily turned his body, and Mad Sky Hunter slid past.

The arcane energy slapped Mad Sky Hunter away. He then looked down. His ribs and the side of his leg were slashed right open with deep wounds. He could see his flesh moving inside, trying to close the wounds.

Before he could do anything else, Psionic Prime appeared. His spear stabbed forward as fast as a meteor, leaving only afterimages behind.

The Psionic Prime Spear's ability to penetrate shields was a major counter to him. The summoning was near its end. In order to block this attack, he had to cast spells and stop the summoning. Ravenlaude clenched his teeth and decided to just not dodge it. He had to summon the Mage Pagoda even at the price of being injured.

Whoosh!

As usual, the shield was penetrated with ease, and the spear stabbed right into Ravenlaude's chest.

The taste of blood gushed up his throat. Ravenlaude ignored it and completed the last part of the summoning spell.

"Descend!"

Boom!

The entire Mage Pagoda was finally summoned. It released an extremely powerful magic energy impact wave that stirred up a tornado, blowing all the mechanical soldiers away onto the inside wall of the Dark Purple Arena, including the Apostle Weapons, damaging them twice.

This was a tall crystal tower. Its base was an enormous disc. Overall, it looked like an enlarged chess piece. Colorful magic streams flowed within the crystal, and countless runes and magic arrays formed a slowly spinning sphere shaped barrier that shrouded the Mage Pagoda.

Ravenlaude coughed a few times, casually created a light green healing magical sphere, and stuffed it into the penetrating wound made by Psionic Prime to stop the bleeding. Then, he flew into the Mage Pagoda, connecting his own magic energy with the energy core of the Mage Pagoda. Only then were they fully linked.

The next second, rows of black holes appeared at the bottom of the Mage Pagoda. Tons of magic puppets and colossi swarmed out. Right after, teleportation tunnels appeared all around, and countless monsters were summoned, charging toward the mechanical army.

Psionic Prime swung and spun the spear in his hands, shooting out waves of light, easily slashing the colossi and monsters in his way in half, creating empty areas in the pile of enemies.

At this time, Ravenlaude's voice sounded in the entire arena like thunder.

"Since you desire battle, enjoy it to the end. Come, Black Star!"

"A Beyond Grade A Mage at full performance… I can't disappoint the lord's trust!"

Electric sparkles flashed in Psionic Prime's eyes. Unafraid, he led the mechanical army and charged forward.

The army of two slides collided!

Long after the dynasty's fleet arrived at the scene, what they saw was a wreckage.

Shattered gems, flesh, and machinery floated in this area. There were also countless radiation reactions in the cosmic space created by high energy explosions. A heavily damaged Mage Pagoda floated, covered in burnt holes and cracks. The magic light around it dimmed completely. It had clearly experienced an extremely tough battle.

The dynasty fleet did not see signs of the mechanical army, so they sent people into the Mage Pagoda and found Ravenlaude, who was leaning against the wall. His clothes were tattered, and he was in a mess. His body was covered in wounds, and there were piles of dried golden blood marks on the floor. A magic staff that was broken into two lay beside his feet; the cut was as smooth as a mirror.

"You guys… ahem… finally came."

Ravenlaude's voice was weak. He stood up with the help of the wall. A few dynasty soldiers quickly approached to help.

"What happened? How have you ended up like this‽" Bekorodi, who was remotely commanding the troops, was shocked.

The opponent was just Black Star's mechanical army. Even if Ravenlaude failed, as a Beyond Grade A, how did he end up this badly beaten‽

Bekorodi thought of a possibility and asked, "Was Black Star's original body here?"

Ravenlaude shook his head, gasped for air, and said, "No, he wasn't."

"Oh… so you should have annihilated the mechanical army and obtained the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, right?" Bekorodi asked. No wonder there were no signs of the mechanical army. He felt that this was the most likely outcome.

Ravenlaude shook his head again with a complicated expression. "No, I was defeated."

Bekorodi's expression stiffened. "So, you're saying, you, a Beyond Grade A, came personally and even used your Mage Pagoda, but you were defeated by one of Black Star's mechanical armies that didn't even have a Lord's Avatar?"

Bro, what is this?

Aren't you too weak‽

Seeing Bekorodi's expression, Ravenlaude knew full well that he despised him. He felt embarrassed and said with a deep voice, "You know nothing about Black Star's strength!"

Then, he repeated the process of the battle in detail and made an accurate analysis on Han Xiao's current level of strength.

"I once fought Mechanic Emperor, and the impression he gave me is still vivid. Black Star has definitely touched the level of God's Trait Transformation, which is why his Apostle Weapons and mechanical army have the power to defeat me!"

Unknowingly, while listening to the report, Bekorodi's expression had become extremely serious.

After a long silence, he finally slowly spoke.

"Black Star's strength hasn't grown for about twenty years. I used to think he needed more time to get through that barrier. I didn't expect him to have grown again this soon."

During the version update, Han Xiao did not level up much, so it looked like he had run into a wall, which made the outside world relieved. They thought that he had finally reached his limit for the time being.

Bekorodi had thought the same. But now, seeing how beaten Ravenlaude was, he knew that Black Star had found the path forward again. Twenty years was not a short time, but compared to the growth of Beyond Grade As, this was way too quick!

With a deep exhale, Bekorodi said in a solemn tone, "Report what happened to Her Excellency and only put this intelligence in confidential documents. Do not leak it."

At this moment, he made the right choice. Hiding the fact that Black Star had become stronger was not because he wanted to but because he knew that the Ruler Urranrell would definitely give that order.

Although Bekorodi did not like Black Star, he knew that hiding the strength of the dynasty's allies was beneficial for the dynasty. Even though his precious Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy had been snatched away, he still had to suck it up and clean up after Black Star.

"Retreat." With resignation, Bekorodi ended the operation.

"Our deal…" Ravenlaude spoke and hinted at the mess with his eyes. His meaning was clear. I gave my all. At least compensate me for it.

"The dynasty will compensate you for the repair fees of your Mage Pagoda and your colossi. As for the Universal Treasure… sorry, you did not complete the mission, so I can't give it to you. Those are the rules," Bekorodi said with a poker face.

He did not want to speak of this matter anymore and ended the communication.

Ravenlaude clenched his teeth with anger.

Not only was his Mage Pagoda broken, but his colossuses were also all destroyed, and he was beaten up. Plus, the Universal Treasure that he had been looking forward to was gone as well. It was a complete loss!

Ravenlaude rubbed his face.

I took this heavy beating for nothing!

Black Star, you *sshole. We're allies, but you really didn't hold back!

Remember this, I'll get you back for this one day!

The Tyrant was bullied by Black Star before. I'll go find him!

He was only angry because he was beaten up by Han Xiao. As for losing the Universal Treasure, he did not blame Han Xiao for it. Without Black Star, Secret Master would most likely have gotten it. He was still sensible in this respect…

But I'm still so angry!

Back at the initial battlefield, the Lord's Avatar and the mechanical army were still fighting intensely with Secret Master.

At this time, the Lord's Avatar suddenly paused. The army stopped firing and backed away.

"Hmm?" Secret Master frowned. He held the magic axe in his hands and did not throw it out. "Why did you stop?"

Han Xiao waved his hand. "I've got it. There's no need to fight anymore. But if you still are not satisfied, I can continue accompanying you."

Secret Master went silent.

He had already been stalled for way too long. He had lost track of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy long ago, so there would be no way to chase after it. He initially wanted to teach Han Xiao a lesson with his secret luck spell, but this guy turned out to be the unluckiest person he had ever seen. His luck could not have been any worse. According to any fortune telling, he should have died young. Therefore, technically, he should have died long ago, but he became someone this powerful and strong.

To be honest, Secret Master actually felt a little respect for Han Xiao. To be able to come this far with such a tragic fate, he had to give him his respect.

Since anything related to luck was useless to Black Star, Secret Master could only put up with it. After all, even if he tore the Lord's Avatar apart, it would not cause too much damage to Black Star… not to mention the fact that he could not even tear it apart.

"You've won today." Secret Master gave Han Xiao a meaningful look. He then sent a voice message with mind energy to Han Xiao alone. "Since you're unlucky to a pitiful level, I'll give you a heads up. Gorutan might be plotting something against you."

Han Xiao was stunned for a moment. "You're warning me? Are you this kind-hearted?"

"Humph." Secret Master did not reply. He turned around and returned to his spaceship, departing with his fleet.

Watching Secret Master leave, Han Xiao thought those words.

Han Xiao remembered that both Secret Master and Gorutan were protectors of the Galactic Black Market, so they should be in the same faction. He had destroyed Secret Master's plan to get the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, yet he had warned him and sold Gorutan out.

"Looks like there are internal conflicts between the protectors of the Galactic Black Market too. Could it be that the fewer the protectors, the more profit each one gets?" Han Xiao pondered.

As the battle between the two of them ended, the rubbernecking organizations also scattered.

To most organizations, although they did not gain anything, they had taken part in a major event, so it was worth it. With first-hand information, they would have plenty of chances to brag about it in the future.

The Modo Civilization, however, became the biggest loser of this incident.

They did not even touch the tip of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, and more than eighty percent of their Calamity Grade elites had died for it.

"What a tragedy…"

Han Xiao expressed his sympathy.

As the fight for the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy came to an end and all the irrelevant people left, he could finally take a look at this treasure.

Chapter 1037: Gaud's Headache

"Not bad, even gave me a mission."

Han Xiao glanced at it with interest.

Primal Esper Ability Entities were strong, but they were not much to him now.

Using a certain comic that he had read in his previous life as reference, Primal Esper Ability Entities were like tailed beasts, praised by the writer as something almost unbeatable at the start, but to those characters in the later stages of the comic…

What? Can this thing even kill anyone?

Similarly, the owner was like the Jinchuriki. If the Primal Esper Ability Entity met a powerful owner, it would have strong powers.

Looking at the mission reward, Han Xiao started planning.

In terms of this mission's difficulty, it would require many Calamity Grades to form a team, so it's considered a team mission for the later versions. Two Character Summon Cards, so probably the Character Summon Cards of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy and Holy Light Particle.

To players, they basically cannot become the owners of Primal Esper Ability Entities, so Character Summon Cards are useful to them. To someone like me who can tame them, however, Character Summon Cards are just the cherry on top… But this Milestone Mission seems quite interesting…

Han Xiao had seen other special milestones in his previous life, which were usually all hidden missions. However, this was the first time he had seen this [Primal Esper Ability Collector] milestone. No one had ever triggered it in his previous life.

"Sounds exotic, but its effects are unknown. Maybe it's more suitable for Espers."

Han Xiao caressed his chin, thought about it for just a few seconds, and then put it aside.

No matter what this milestone was about, he was going to get the Holy Light Particle one way or another. He mainly wanted another Primal Esper Ability Entity, so the mission was just the icing on the cake. He would see about this special milestone when the time came; speculating would not lead to anything.

"I'll agree to this then. Let's make the Holy Light Particle come and accompany you."

"So, when do we depart?"

The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy could not wait. It looked like it wanted to take revenge on its arch enemy, but according to what had happened in Han Xiao's previous life, Han Xiao kept feeling like it was looking forward to seeing its old friend.

Hehe, Esper Abilities.

Han Xiao thought about it, shook his head, and said, "Not now, I have something to do. When the time comes, I'll go find it."

He still had some things to do. His priority was to build the King and Emperor's Cape, the two pieces of gold equipment. Also, he had to invent and build a special host for the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, the artificial mechanical owner.

This way, he would have a special mechanical guard that possessed a Super High Risk Esper Ability. Its Grade would be difficult to judge, as it would depend on the performance of the host. If he could turn it into a mechanical life, with the effect of the Esper Ability, it would have exceptional specifications.

Of course, there were precedents of this in the Mechanic class. The Beyond Grade As whom the Mechanic Emperor had captured were used as materials to make special mechanical puppets. Apostle Weapons were high-level soldiers provided by the class itself, but Mechanics could invent and create their own high-level soldiers.

On the other hand, the intelligence that Secret Master had given him made Han Xiao more certain that Hila was in a risky position. Therefore, his original body had to stay hidden in the Emerald Star Cluster and would only move when the opportunity came.

At the same time, players all over the universe were swarming toward the Flickering World. The World Server was forming very quickly. According to Han Xiao's knowledge about the players, although he was having a great time harvesting leeks, due to how much the army players stood out, they might become the target of the players from the other factions. He had to stay there and see the direction of things. Due to the existence of the Black Star Army, the players in the Flickering World would, of course, take different actions compared to his previous life. Hence, he had to improvise and adapt.

Compared to the importance of these things, capturing the Holy Light Particle would have to be postpones. Not to mention the fact that he had to travel to a secondary dimension to carry out this mission, as well as find out which secondary dimension the Holy Light Particle was in.

"Alright, I'll wait."

The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy did not mind; it was not in a hurry. It understood that Black Star was its master, not an owner or tool like those before.

The only thing it was sad about was that it might be sealed in a lifeless mechanical body and not be able to communicate with anyone, which would be a lot less fun than playing with its owner.

"Sigh, I only found a perfect compatible owner not long ago. Sadly, I won't be able to enter him."

Han Xiao cut off the psionic link, put the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy into his pocket, and stood up. He stowed the Divine Mechanical Throne away, summoned his ride, and headed back with Psionic Prime and the others.

…

As dust settled around the ownership of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, all the participants who retreated did not keep it a secret. They quickly posted the recording of the event, which became the top news in just a few hours.

"The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy Appeared, Fell into Black Star's Hands!"

The changes in the Flickering World affected the entire universe. The news about the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy appearing in the free competition zone and falling into Black Star's hands quickly spread across the various Star Fields.

The galactic residents did not know much about Primal Esper Ability Entities, but the Super High Risk Esper Ability List was famous. Furthermore, the news mentioned the two popular terms 'Flickering World' and 'Black Star'. There was even the recording of the battle venue. Hence, this news becoming a hot topic at countless dinner tables was not uncommon.

A few hours after this news, the production company of Wayne Cards made an announcement, expressing that they would be making the new Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy card and potentially adding it to the Black Star Army's faction card set. Furthermore, they would be considering introducing the 'Primal Esper Ability Entity' set card. The way they rode the hype train was astonishing.

The players who liked to surf the internet saw this news too. While shocked, they learned the new concept of 'Primal Esper Ability Entities'.

However, the popularity of this news mainly revolved around the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. Black Star had done way too many astonishing things. Compared to the major events in the past, this was not that big a deal. The countless galactic residents and players were used to it.

We knew how incredible Black Star is long ago. This is just a basic occurrence, so sit down.

…

At a certain military base of the dynasty, in a very crowded and noisy bar that was filled with loud laughter and cheers, the atmosphere was joyous. All the guests there were soldiers and officers wearing the dynasty's uniform.

This military base mainly functioned as a training ground. Many dynasty soldiers accepted training there. As it was a half-closed base, it had internal entertainment venues, mainly bars. In the current era, the civilizations would not be too strict with the Super soldiers. They had quite good privileges and benefits. Even when training in an isolated base, they could still enjoy life to a certain extent.

Many Super key training camps were training there too, which consisted of those who were on the list of people the dynasty wanted to focus on training. Gaud was one of them.

A group of key training students were sitting at the bar. They were all Calamity Grades. They drank joyfully and chattered with each other.

Gaud was among them. He held his glass with a calm smile on his face, occasionally saying a few words, looking like he was quite sociable. It was a friendly atmosphere.

He got the most attention among all the training students. The Esper Ability he possessed had an extremely bright future. Hence, he had always been famous in the training camp.

Someone shook his head and said with a smile, "Among us, the one who has the highest chance of breaking through the Beyond Grade A limit is you, Gaud. It's so hard to compete. Maybe we will all become your subordinates in the future. We'll need you to take care of us then."

"By the way, if you become a Beyond Grade A, what position do you plan to take on? You probably won't make it as the Ruler's guard, and the dynasty most likely won't send you out, so you'll probably be the commander of a certain army," someone else said.

"It's whatever for me." Gaud smiled. His identity would be a direct Beyond Grade A of the dynasty, so his development direction would be different from the allies. He could be a part of the dynasty's core authority like Clotti.

Someone laughed and jokingly said, "According to past conventions, we'll likely join your team… Sigh, we might as well cheer for our future boss. You're not going anywhere today before you get drunk."

Gaud smiled and accepted the passion of his comrades.

While the atmosphere was exciting, Gaud suddenly caught a glimpse of the news that was playing on the virtual screen on the bar's war. His face quickly stiffened, and his smile disappeared.

His abnormal response surprised his comrades. They looked over following his sight and saw that the screen was playing the news about the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy being snatched away by Black Star.

"Yo, Black Star did something again."

"Incredible, no wonder he's the next pillar the dynasty has chosen."

"A few years ago, when I accepted the changes of the Evolution Cube, I met him up close and almost could not stop myself from wanting to ask him for an autograph."

"Luckily, he's the dynasty's ally instead of the federation or the church. It's a blessing for the dynasty."

The others could not help but start chatting about this topic. Everyone there admired the strong. Many of them were fans of the various Beyond Grade A dynasty allies, and a number of them were Black Star's fans.

At this time, Gaud put down his glass, stood up with a poker face, and coldly said, "I have something to attend to. I'm heading off."

Without waiting for the others to respond, he passed through the crowd and left the bar, leaving his many comrades confused and exchanging looks.

What's going on? What happened?

Gaud left the bar, quickly returned to his room, took out his communicator, and contacted Bekorodi.

After it rang for quite a while, the other side finally picked up. Gaud instantly questioned, "You told me to wait for the good news—is this the good news you spoke of?"

Bekorodi stayed silent for a few seconds before finally slowly replying. "Black Star's interference was unexpected. The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy is indeed in his hands now."

"So, what do you plan to do?" Gaud was expressionless.

"I'll try to save this, see if we can exchange something for the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy."

Gaud stayed silent and did not ask what was going to happen if that did not work.

The dynasty was willing to give the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy to him for him to make full use of his Esper Ability and help him become a Beyond Grade A sooner. Then, he would be able to analyze the principles of the Evolution Energy. Without the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, the dynasty would still wait for him to slowly grow.

However, to Gaud, this meant that he had lost a powerful source of strength. Without the various special abilities of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, the specialized plan he had made for himself would be severely messed up, and he would not reach his strongest form.

This meant that his future maximum strength was directly reduced!

"Black Star won't be able to use the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy himself. As long as we take out enough chips, he'll be willing to exchange it. It's not impossible. I…"

Bekorodi was still analyzing the situation when Gaud spoke and interrupted him.

"Let's keep to that then. Notify me when there's any progress."

Then, Gaud hung up the call and frowned slightly.

He was in an extremely bad mood and did not bother wasting his time with Bekorodi. He knew that the chance of regaining the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was thin.

The dynasty would not overpay for a Primal Esper Ability Entity that was not completely necessary, and Black Star was a piece of sh*t who would never make a losing deal. From what he knew about these two sides, the odds of making the deal were infinitely close to zero.

Gaud shook his head and crossed out the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy in his mind.

With the power he had now, he had absolutely no way to interfere with the fight for the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. The only way was to borrow the dynasty's forces, and the dynasty had failed. Hence, he had no other options, and there was nothing he could do about it.

He had yet to fulfil his potential, while Black Star's forces became stronger and stronger. Since the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was gone, he could only let it be. It was far from time to mess with Black Star.

"I thought that with the dynasty taking part, this would be in the bag, but you ruined it. Now, I have to adjust my growth plan… Tsk, Black Star, oh Black Star, you really give me a lot of trouble."

Gaud was in a very bad mood.

…

Outside the remote communication room of the Modo Civilization's Emerald Star Cluster stronghold, two soldiers who were stationed there were whispering.

"How long has it been since the commander and the inspector went in?"

"Probably almost an hour."

"Looks like the Three Kings have summoned them. I wonder when they will come out…"

"Hey, the gate's opening. Stand properly."

The gate of the room slid open, the two guards quickly stood straight, stopped talking, and looked straight forward, acting diligent. However, their eyes uncontrollably shifted to glance at Commander Roddick and Inspector Lagos.

Roddick's face looked like he was on the verge of exploding, while Lagos looked borderline depressed.

As the sacrifice of tens of Calamity Grade elites was completely meaningless, they had earned a thunderous scolding from the Three Kings of Modo, as well as their direct bosses. Their image among the upper echelons fell to rock-bottom.

Although he was just executing the mission given by the people above and the death of tens of Calamity Grades was not his fault, he could do nothing but take the blame. He was so furious that he had almost exploded.

Lagos had no way of comforting him. He asked hesitantly, "Our high-level combatants have suffered heavy losses. Like the Three Kings said earlier, that cannot occur. What do you plan to do?"

"It's all because of Black Star!" Roddick clenched his fists tightly and said with rage, "If we continue to be this passive, Black Star will ruthlessly bite off our forces. Without solving this problem once and for all, similar things will keep happening."

If we could stop Black Star, we would have… Lagos smiled bitterly with resignation and asked, "So, what idea do you have?"

"If we could kill Black Star…" Roddick was murmuring. He then turned around and immediately saw Lagos's unamused expression, so he swallowed what he was going to say next. He thought about it and said, "By ourselves, there's no way we can fight Black Star, so we can only borrow external forces. If we cause the Black Star Army a lot of trouble and make them have no time to deal with us, maybe we can mitigate the current situation."

"For example?"

Roddick opened his mouth and felt helpless.

If something like this was so easy to think of, how could they have ended up in this situation? If they did not make some gigantic contributions, their promotion would probably never come.

Chapter 1038: Recruitment

In a certain area inside the Emerald Star Cluster, the exploration fleet of a small financial group was flying. Organizations like this were not strong enough to occupy resource rich planets; they could only gain profit through normal exploration or getting hired. This was very common in the current Flickering World.

This fleet mainly consisted of exploration ships and transportation ships. As a fleet used for expeditions, other than the necessary crews on every ship, there were also extra people who lived in a travel ship that was specially used to transport people. This ship mainly had life facilities inside. The number of people it could hold far exceeded functional spaceships such as exploration ships. Most staff who did not have crew duties stayed there usually.

This long-term travel ship was like a portable space station. It was bigger than even the industrial transportation ships in the team. It took care of manpower logistics, food supplies, and entertainment facilities. With how intense the competition was in the Flickering World, without daily benefits, it would be very tough to hire anyone. As a commercial financial group, their crew could not be considered truly loyal, so the treatment they got was one of the important factors that attracted more employees.

The hall of the space station was a multifunctional entertainment social venue. There were entertainment facilities and all kinds of stores, where the crew could spend money. The hall was on the bottommost floor, and above it were bridges made of transparent materials. The people in the hall could see the people above them walking by when looking up. Overall, it looked like a crowded and prosperous business square.

In one area of the hall was the staff canteen, which was boisterous and noisy. Staff from all positions could be seen there.

At the edge of the canteen, Evans sat at a table by himself, slowly eating his meal. His eyes were hardly open, staring down at the table and daydreaming.

He was still wearing the yellow protective suit but with the helmet open now. He looked ordinary and common like every typical ground crew member. In fact, ninety-nine percent of the people who took this job were ordinary people. They were the staff at the lowest level of the financial group.

At the tables around him, other ground crew workers filled the seats, chattering while eating, sometimes bursting into laughter. Occasionally, some people's eyes darted past Evans, but they did not stop and ignored him completely.

Evans was used to this. Ground crew members were mostly normal people. Their work efficiency was not high, and many of them liked to slack off. Comparatively, he was hardworking and never lazed around, often completing his tasks beyond the minimum requirements. Therefore, he was always publicly praised by the team's manager and even received some bonuses.

Due to his attitude, some of his colleagues started to urge others to isolate him, maybe because they were jealous, or maybe because they did not like an ex-convict who had just left prison. Gradually, more and more people stopped interacting with him.

Being boycotted, Evans did not mind it at all. He had never liked socializing with colleagues to begin with. After spending many years in prison, he had learned not to care about what others thought.

"Hmm? Evans, you're sitting alone?" A voice that he recognized appeared beside him. Evans looked up, and a familiar person stood beside him holding the meal plate. It was the manager of the ground crew team he was in.

There were many teams in the ground crew department. This team manager was just a base-level officer who did not have much power. He was Evans' direct boss who liked him.

"Since there's no one sitting beside you, do you mind if I join your table?" the team leader said with a smile.

"Not at all." Evans signed for the team manager to please sit down.

The team manager sat opposite him and chatted with Evans while eating. The ground crew members could no longer ignore Evans' table, so they turned to greet their boss.

"Manager, you don't have to help me for this," Evans softly said with resignation. "I really don't care about being disliked by others."

"That won't do. What happens if you delay your work because of a bad mood? The quota of our team might have to rely on you to be completed." The team manager shrugged.

Evans smiled bitterly. This manager was a normal person, and a kind one at that. Because of his high work efficiency, the manager took extra care of him and was very friendly.

After gulping down the meal, Evans bade farewell to the manager, who was still eating, before standing up with the empty plate in his hands. He then went to the recycling window of the canteen and threw the plate in.

At this time, a few people in mechanical suits walked into the canteen. They were all bottom level mercenaries, and their faces did not look normal. There was a slight redness from excitement. They were walking in Evans' direction and attracted his attention.

"Supers… looks like they've consumed some kind of stimulation drug and are high."

Evans gave a few more looks to these people, and as he was just about to pass them by and leave the canteen, he suddenly heard the voice of a mercenary increase amid their conversation. One of them seemed very emotional.

"You don't believe I've invented a new way to use my Esper Ability‽ I'll show you then!"

Right after he said that, this excited mercenary clenched his hand. The air around him gathered and formed an invisible wind sphere. It then smashed right into the ground below him. The sphere of wind exploded and turned into tiny blades of wind that scattered and spread everywhere.

The financial group had a rule that the powers of Supers were not allowed to be used in public areas. If discovered, punishments ranged from paying a fine to being fired. However, these Grade D mercenaries who had just used mind stimulation drugs were in a state of overexcitement and had completely lost their senses. They totally forgot about this rule.

The people around panicked. The floor was filled with traces of slash marks, and the staff around backed away hastily.

As the power of this sphere of wind was limited, the others were not really injured. Evans, however, was the closest to it. He was blown away by the wind pressure, and his protective suit was cut open in many places.

A tint of bright red appeared in everyone's eyes.

"Someone's wounded!"

Many people immediately moved to rubberneck. The staff of the ground crew squeezed in too, but when they saw that Evans was the one who was wounded, their footsteps stopped as they hesitated over whether they should help him up or not. While they were hesitating, the team manager already quickly walked up and helped Evans up before looking at his wound.

"Where are you wounded? Let me see."

"Just a small wound, I'm okay. Tsss…"

Evans tightened his face, but the twitch at the edge of his eyes showed that the wounds were quite painful. The wind blades had slashed open more than ten wounds on his body, all of which were bleeding. Very soon, the protective suit was dyed red.

A few patrol guards heard the fuss and ran over.

"What's going on ‽"

The team manager pointed at these mercenaries with anger and said, "They violated the rules and used an Esper Ability in a public area, causing a crew to be wounded.

The guard frowned and looked at the scene, noticed that Evans was injured, and then looked at the few mercenaries. He asked with a deep voice, "Is that true?"

After this accident, these few people were more awake. The mercenary who had thrown the sphere of wind coughed and said, "I did it unintentionally. It's just an accident. I'll go to ask for the punishment later."

"Hmm, luckily, only one person was hurt. You'll be fined at most, not a big deal." The guard comforted the mercenary a bit. He then turned to Evans, glanced at the ground crew uniform on his body, and said casually, "You're Evans, right? It's just flesh wounds. Get them treated at the medical room, and you'll be fine. You won't die."

"That's it?" The team manager was unsatisfied. "Not even an apology?"

The mercenary who had caused the incident glanced at Evans and said in a very perfunctory tone filled with arrogance, "This is my fault, sorry."

No sincerity could be felt at all.

"What kind of attitude is that?" The team manager was resentful.

This time, the guard interrupted him. "That's enough. He has already apologized, and his salary will be deducted later too. Don't keep dwelling on it."

Although the guard looked like he was doing what should be done, his attitude clearly showed the different treatment he gave to the two sides. He was a Super too. Seeing that this mercenary had only accidentally wounded a normal ground worker, he did not think it was a big deal. To him, although this mercenary had made a mistake, as long as he was willing to take the punishment, it would be best to give him some comfort. This was more important than a normal person.

This mercenary looked like this was completely normal. Seeing that Evans would not die, he did not bother looking at him anymore and turned around to casually chat with his friends.

This was witnessed by the people around. Many normal people had complicated expressions on their faces.

Most Supers did not care about how affected ordinary people, and the ordinary people knew that very well. Even though the other party apologized and accepted the punishment, he still did not care at all. Seeing this, most present felt a flame burning in their chest.

Supers having privileges was a rule silently accepted in the entire universe, and there was nothing they could do about that.

This time, Evans pulled the team manager a little and stood up by pressing on his knees. Blood dripped onto the floor, splashing around everywhere. He endured the pain and said, "It's okay. It's just not my day. Bring me to the medical room."

The team manager gave the other side a glare and gave up on arguing. He then assisted Evans and walked out of the crowd.

"It's all settled. Nothing more to see here." The guard waved the crowd away.

However, at this instant, a sudden change occurred!

Bang!

The spaceship suddenly trembled as if it had stopped in an instant. Even the internal shock absorption system could not eliminate the enormous inertial force. Everyone present staggered and fell onto the ground in panic.

"What's going on?"

"Looks like the spaceship was forced to stop!"

"Did we meet galactic pirates‽"

While everyone was getting up anxiously and was about to rush out of the canteen to take refuge, the speaker inside the spaceship suddenly sounded and echoed through the entire fleet. Everyone could hear it.

"This is the Black Star Army. Your spaceship has been forced to come to a stop by us. There's no need to panic. Our goal is only to find one person. His name is Evans. He works in your ground crew…"

As soon as the sentence ended, all eyes focused on Evans.

Swoosh!

In an instant, the area around Evans became empty. Everyone hid with shock.

The Black Star Army is looking for this guy by name‽

How did he get into trouble with the Black Star Army? And why are they putting in so much effort to find him? Does he have a secret identity‽

This time, Evans' most ordinary appearance suddenly became mysterious in the eyes of everyone around him.

"Black Star Army?" Evans was stunned too.

Isn't that an advanced organization I'm far from being able to encounter? Why are they looking for me? They probably have the wrong guy.

He turned to look at the team manager, but the team manager had let go of his hand long ago and hid to the side with fear on his face.

Evans was just about to say something when he suddenly realized that these guards and mercenaries had walked toward him and surrounded him.

"What are you doing?"

"Preventing you from escaping. Since the Black Star Army wants to see you, you shall wait here," a guard said coldly.

Evans clenched his teeth. He breathed rapidly a few times, and only after a while did his fists open again. He then said with resignation, "Don't worry, I won't run. I want to find out what this is about too."

The people waited there for a while. Suddenly, footsteps appeared outside, and a group of people walked in. The upper echelons who were usually arrogant and mighty were now all walking beside this group of Black Star Army warriors with their heads low. The warrior leader leading the group gave off a powerful energy wave. He was a Grade B, and he was considered a very powerful person to these bottom level workers.

The scene was so silent that no one dared breath heavily.

The group of them walked to Evans. The fleet's commander pointed over and said, "He's the person you're looking for."

"Hmm." This Black Star Army's Grade B warrior sized Evans up with a poker face. "You're Evans?"

Evans took a deep breath. "That is indeed my name, but I have no past interaction with the Black Star Army. I think you might have found the wrong person."

Hearing this, this Grade B team leader took out a resume and showed it to Evans. "Is this your resume?"

Looking at it closely, Evans nodded with shock. His face was filled with doubt and confusion.

The Black Star Army really is looking for me?

The Grade B team leader nodded. "That's correct then. You're the one we're looking for. Follow me."

"Wait a moment, I would like to know, why did you guys come for me?" Evans asked.

Everyone perked up their ears to listen to the reply.

They also wanted to know the answer to this question.

The Grade B team leader suddenly smiled, reached out his hand, and said passionately, "You're a talent His Excellency Black Star asked to recruit by name. Brother, welcome to the Black Star Army."

The entire venue became silent for an instant.

Boom!

Then, like a bomb, roaring voices exploded!

"What!"

The team manager shivered with his eyes wide open. The earlier guard and the mercenary were completely frozen with shock.

Everyone present was stupefied. Some even thought that they were hearing things. Countless looks of disbelief focused on Evans.

Did we hear that right?

That famous Beyond Grade A Black Star is recruiting a normal person by name‽

Could he be so talented that even a Beyond Grade A is tempted to recruit him‽

He's definitely been hiding his talents, which is why we did not notice it all this time.

You really can't judge a book by its cover!

Admiration appeared in everyone's eyes.

That was especially so for the colleagues who isolated Evans. They were filled with regret and hastily looked down covered in sweat, worried about being noticed by Evans.

"Recruit… me?"

Evans was stupefied.

At this instant, he fell into a deep state of self-doubt.

What's so incredible about me that even a Beyond Grade A is interested in me?

Could it be that it's really like what I fantasized about when I was young?

That my body has sealed the power of the evil Universe Overlord, the Master of Destruction, Black Devil‽

At the same time, inside a mysterious base in a distant Ancient Star Desert, a few silhouettes were discussing the news about the appearance of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy inside the private conference room.

"Another Primal Esper Ability Entity has appeared."

"It's the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. We have to find a way to get it."

"It has fallen into Black Star's hands. Black Star is a Beyond Grade A who rose in the past few decades. His growth speed is astonishing. He won't be easy to deal with."

"Black Star can live for a very long time, but we don't have so much time to wait. The Primal Esper Ability Entities are the keys to open the Third Sanctum. They must be obtained… Let's make use of the products we've invented in recent years. The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy is an important material for fusion. We must get it."

"Sadly, EsGod's body is in the Crimson Dynasty's hands. Otherwise, his Esper Ability would be the best tool."

"Speaking of which, things on Thousand Shadows' side are almost maturing. We can expect to harvest it after some time."

"Before the promised date arrives, we have to finish preparing the awakening ceremony."

"The honor of the Primordial Ones shall never wither."

Chapter 1039: EsGod's Destined Arch Enemy!

Thousand Shadows' territory was situated in the Abyss of Stars' Shadow Realm. The black gaseous planet was still hovering beside the Shadow Realm like a black satellite, covered in thick streams of black energy that occasionally formed wave-like tides.

A spaceship stopped beside the dark satellite, and the hatch opened. Calamity Grade Shadows pushed the various prisoners they had captured from different Star Fields down with a poker face. The prisoners were mostly Calamity Grades. There were also low-grade Supers with special abilities.

These prisoners were covered in restraining devices and were extremely weak. They had no power to fight back at all. The scene looked like cooking dumplings. Every time someone fell onto the surface of this dark satellite, there would be one wave of black energy engulfing it. The next second, that person would disappear.

This was how Thousand Shadows' servants replenished shadows for him. There were close to a thousand prisoners in this batch, and they were all consumed by the planet-sized Thousand Shadows.

At this time, the space beside the spaceship suddenly rippled. A blurry silhouette suddenly appeared. It was wearing a hooded black robe and did not show its face or body. The edges of the silhouette looked like flames, as if it was emitting gas. Overall, it looked like a black cloud. This was not a remote projection of the quantum network but some kind of mind projection. Only Thousand Shadows and his Shadow Servants could see it.

The next second, the planet surface of Thousand Shadows suddenly started moving violently, forming huge black tsunamis. Very soon, a face appeared on the planet's surface, just eyes, nose, and mouth formed by energy vortexes. It was opening its mouth wide as if it was roaring.

Two invisible psychic waves were released from both sides and formed a psychic communication link.

"How's the progress? How long is the transformation going to take?" The blurry silhouette spoke first.

"I don't know. Thousand Shadows is very persistent."

"How conscious is he?"

"Not very. I obtained control of his body long ago and inherited all of his memories. As soon as I completely consume his last bit of conscience, it will dramatically increase the speed of the transformation."

"Make it as quick as possible. You're a core factor of our plan. We've tried many methods in these years. In the end, we discovered that, in order to open the Third Sanctum, it can only be done with Esper Abilities. Therefore, you're the foundation of our fusion ceremony, the vessel to contain the other Primal Esper Ability Entities."

"Don't worry. Back then, Thousand Shadows wanted to live for eternity and vitalized me using your technology. Humph, this greedy guy brought this upon himself. He exceeded the limits of his physical body, but he suffered damage from it. You guys have given me life and independence. When I transform into a true Primal Esper Ability Entity, I will be able to help you."

"Hmm, when the plan is complete, we promise you freedom."

After that, the blurry silhouette disappeared without a trace.

The surface of the dark planet slowly returned to normal after the face disappeared.

…

The news about the appearance of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy only remained as the hot topic for a few days. In the current Flickering World, conflicts were abound, so the popularity of the news shifted very rapidly. Very soon, there was other news that attracted the attention of the galactic residents and the various organizations.

As the final winner of the competition, Black Star's mechanical army also received a certain amount of attention. However, it quickly disappeared without a trace, and its whereabouts were not known to the outside world.

At this moment, Han Xiao's invisible spaceship was hidden nearby Hila's territory in the Emerald Star Cluster. He was currently calling Ames.

"… So, that's the situation. I invited you over as a guest to protect Hila, make it look like I'm in my base to make the hidden enemies let their guards down, and have you help protect the base and look after Aurora… Therefore, I really did not stand you up on purpose." Han Xiao's tone was filled with resignation.

On the screen, Ames was playing with a small green force field sphere with her eyelids hanging low. Despite her calm tone, it gave off a strange vibe of danger.

"If you'd told me directly, I would've helped you too. Do you not trust me?"

"How could that be? Didn't you want to see Aurora after she advanced? Well, now you've seen her. Plus, when I invited you, I didn't say anything about me wanting to see you." Han Xiao scratched his head and joked, "I didn't say it directly mainly because I wanted to be polite. I know that as long as I ask, you definitely will agree. After all, I'm already so strong now. I'm worried you might think I'm ordering you."

"Hehe, you didn't order me sure, but I feel like you're using me. Doesn't that seem worse?" Ames narrowed her eyes. A green tint flashed across her eyes.

"Hey, that's not true at all. With the relationship we have, using the term 'use" is exaggerating it." Han Xiao waved.

"Is that so? You've used me many times in the past." Ames smiled every so faintly.

"That's in the past. Things are different now. Our two organizations are intertwined. We're a family. As family, well, it's normal to occasionally joke around…"

"Tsk, who's your family? Shameless." Ames frowned slightly.

Seeing this, Han Xiao smiled and teased her. "Hehe, did you really want to see me so badly? Do you want me to go back and accompany you?"

"… Who wants to see you?"

Ames paused, deactivated the force field, and casually said, "Stay there to protect my student then. Do you need me to go over to help?"

"No need."

"Because I'm too weak?" Ames raised her brows slightly.

"Ahem, of course not. It's mainly because another thing needs your help. You have to stay in Black Star Palace and act as if I'm there too."

"Since it's for my student, I shall cooperate with your show… but don't be in a rush to thank me. We have yet to settle the matter of you tricking me."

"Alright, when I return, how about I accompany you on a sightseeing trip in a secondary dimension?" Han Xiao raised his brows. "Just the two of us."

I'll have to capture the Holy Light Particle in a secondary dimension too, killing two birds with one stone… I'm so brilliant!

"Okay, it's decided then." Ames had no objections.

Although she had been tricked into going all the way there, after stroking Aurora for the past few days, she was not really angry anymore.

If someone else had toyed with her and used her like this, Ames would have been furious for sure. But since it was Black Star who pranked her, she did not mind it too much—only those close to her could do something like this.

Furthermore, this reminded her of the past when Black Star kept using her despite being so weak. It made her feel nostalgic.

After chattering for a while longer, Han Xiao hung up the call and looked over at the workbench on the side.

He was currently inside the machinery workshop of the spaceship. His Mechanical Force was controlling all kinds of devices to build the King mechanical suit. To his side, there was already a pile of failed products.

He called them all failed products, but they were still all orange equipment, which could be considered rare equipment. Unfortunately, they did not reach the Universal Treasure level. Not only were their performances tremendously weaker, but they also had none of the incredible effects they were supposed to have. Plus, the cost was horrifyingly expensive. To him, these were undoubtedly failures.

After putting his communicator away, Han Xiao could finally focus on building this attempt at the King right in front of him. The [Spirit Instrument] talent on his interface constantly glowed. This talent would only be activated when building Universal Treasures.

However, when Han Xiao was more than halfway done, Phillip suddenly appeared and reported that some of the mechanical soldiers had already returned with Evans.

"Bring him over then." Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

After a while, the gate of the machinery workshop opened. A few mechanical soldiers escorted a man in. It was Evans.

As soon as Evans walked in, he saw a handsome and domineering black-clothed man looking at him with a faint smile, and he immediately became nervous.

"Your Excellency, are you Black Star?"

"That's me."

Han Xiao smiled and nodded as he sized Evans up. His first impression of him was ordinary, way too ordinary.

Evans felt that Han Xiao's eyes seemed to be able to look right through him, like there was nothing he could hide in front of Han Xiao. He became even more anxious.

Although he was usually calm and levelheaded, even he could no longer maintain his cool when facing someone who stood at the top of the universe like Black Star.

Evans took a deep breath, found the courage, and asked, "Your Excellency Black Star, I'm just an ordinary person without Super genes. What part of me has caused you to be interested?"

Han Xiao smiled playfully. "Your physique is quite special, and I'm very interested in that."

"Special physique?"

Evans was stunned. He looked down at himself and felt that he was basically the direct opposite of the word 'special'.

"Anyway, don't worry, as a Beyond Grade A, I won't put in so much effort just to find trouble with an ordinary person like you. Your life is not in danger here. You just have to cooperate with my experiments at most. After that, you can take up an office job in the army, which pays way more handsomely than the financial group you worked for before. What do you think?"

"… You've already brought me here, can I still reject?" Evans smiled bitterly.

He had just come out of prison. He had come to the Flickering World both to gain knowledge and to make a living. He did not mind working for the Black Star Army at all. Plus, the pay would be much higher.

Seeing he had no objections, Han Xiao picked up a syringe and walked to Evans. He told him to stand still and sucked a vial of blood out of him.

Han Xiao was not lying. He did intend to run some experiments.

Evans had been the shared host of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy and Holy Light Particle in Han Xiao's previous life, so his physique was undoubtedly special. Han Xiao wanted to build the mechanical host for Primal Esper Ability Entities, so extracting and studying Evans' cells would help to explain the reasoning behind his exceptional compatibility with Primal Esper Abilities, which would speed up the progress of the research.

On the other hand, Han Xiao also dealt damage to Evans by punching the needle into his body, so the combat information was triggered as well.

The Great Mechanic Han's eyes sparkled as he opened the interface to see Evans' attributes.

The attribute interface of an ordinary person was very simple; only two special talents attracted Han Xiao's attention. One was [Medium Luck Glow], meaning he was a protagonist-type character, and it was only medium because while Evans obtained power, he also had a new arch enemy, EsGod.

The other special talent was called [Highest Grade Esper Ability Affinity Physique], and its effects were all related to the Esper class. It drastically increased his compatibility with Primal Esper Ability Entities. At the same time, when being attacked by Espers, it provided a certain chance to recover some of his health and energy. Plus, the difficulty of cultivating and exploring his own Esper Ability decreased drastically, while the power of his Esper Ability would be increased drastically. It even passively increased the potential of Esper Abilities by one grade.

No wonder he could possess two Primal Esper Abilities, this talent is basically the 'Perfect Mechanical Sense' of the Esper class. Its effects are way too incredible.

Han Xiao was astounded.

Usually, those with such talents should all be able to awaken as Espers, but sadly, Evans was an ordinary person. What a waste of this tal…

Wait a minute!

That's not right. If he has this talent, how can he not have Super genes? Something must be wrong!

Han Xiao suddenly turned around with very bright eyes.

With Evans having an unwilling expression on his face, Han Xiao told him to take off all his clothes. He then obediently underwent a detailed full body check. Evans was broken in the past. Of course, he had no way to check his Super gene in some high-level facilities. Therefore, Han Xiao thought something might have been overlooked.

And with this check, he really found something!

Han Xiao looked at the report and frowned.

"W-what is it?" Evans wore his clothes back and was a little nervous.

"It's not that you don't have Super genes. I don't know who did the check for you, but they did not check thoroughly enough."

Evans was stunned.

He had always thought that he was an ordinary person with no talent. Never did he expect to have someone tell him today that he actually had talent. Even though he had gotten used to the identity of an ordinary person, he was still full of shock.

"But don't get excited too early." Han Xiao waved and spoke slowly. "There's something wrong with your Super genes. It seems to be suppressed by some kind of drug. After so many years, your Super genes have shrunk so much that it's almost impossible to be detected, so the chance of your Super genes awakening is close to zero. This was an act of man. Did you have any enemies growing up?"

Evans barely suppressed the boiling emotions in his heart and started seriously searching through his memories. He then said with uncertainty, "I accepted Super gene detection when I was ten. If someone did something like this, it must have been before I was ten. But how could I have made enemies when I was that young? Because of my family? But I only have a normal family. How could this be…"

His expression kept changing. He could live with not having any talent, but only today did he know that he initially had talent, but it was destroyed by someone when he was young!

His talent was not the only thing that was destroyed but his life in the last few decades too!

Evans had initially already accepted his fate, but now, the flames of wrath burned violently in his heart.

Clap clap.

Suddenly, Han Xiao clapped and interrupted his thoughts.

"Alright, don't think about it if you can't figure it out. You can research it in the future. Let's talk about a more important matter. I might have a way to help you awaken."

Evans' entire body shivered. He suppressed his excitement and asked, "What do I have to give in return?"

"Simple. I initially thought you're just an ordinary person, but if you can awaken your Esper Ability, just fight for me." Han Xiao paused, smiled, and slowly said, "I've researched you. When you were an ordinary person like you have always been, to protect your friends, you found a way to kill a low-grade Super. Not every ordinary person has guts like you. You have fighting talent. You once refused to accept your fate, and the many years spent in the prison extinguished your passion, but now, you might have a chance to be reborn. I only hope you don't waste it."

"Okay," Evans replied firmly. His eyes were filled with perseverance. The vibe he gave off became completely different from when he had already accepted his fate, like a sharp sword buried in dust that has been finally dug up and cleaned off the rust.

Seeing this, Han Xiao took out a bottle of life force potion made by Aurora.

Evans' symptom was that his Super genes had shrunk and lost all activity. As long as enough life energy was injected, they would recover. The life force potion was the perfect medicine for this.

Han Xiao injected just one tenth of the golden medicine into Evans' body so that he would not end up having overflowing life force.

Buzz!

The next moment, Evans started glowing and releasing strong vitality energy from all over his body.

This glow lasted many minutes before dimming down. Evans closed his eyes and stood at the same place, but he felt completely different. He could not be any healthier. All the damage incurred from his many years in prison and the rest of his life had all disappeared.

"How do you feel?"

"Like I've been reborn."

Evans opened his eyes. The gold light in his eyes finally dissipated. He looked at Han Xiao with appreciation in his eyes.

Han Xiao nodded with satisfaction and asked, "Have you sensed your Esper Ability?"

Evans frowned. He carefully sensed the changes that he had undergone but was a little hesitant.

"It does feel different, like I have a new sensory organ. That should be my Esper Ability, right?"

"Show it to me." Han Xiao was curious.

Evans nodded. He then used all his strength to try to use it, but he realized that nothing happened at all, so he doubted himself. "I can't seem to be able to control it. Did my Esper Ability really awaken?"

Anyone who had just awakened would become a Grade E Super, but despite being very weak, situations where Espers were not able to control their Esper Ability should not happen. Han Xiao frowned. He felt that this was not a simple matter, so he poked Evans another time with a needle to look at his combat information.

However, with just one glance, Han Xiao's entire body stiffened, and he stood in place. He rubbed his eyes and almost thought he was hallucinating.

He looked at it for a total of more than ten seconds before he recovered from the shock. He looked at Evans with an extremely strange expression and murmured, "No wonder… no wonder…"

"Have you found out what my Esper Ability is?" Evans asked nervously.

Han Xiao took a deep breath, patted Evans' shoulder with a complicated expression, pursed his lips, and said with deep meaning in his words, "You have to be a good person…"

Then, he did not care about Evans' confused expression, turned his back to him, and roared in his heart.

You son of a bi*ch!

This kid's ability… is also absorbing Esper Abilities!

Exactly the same as EsGod!

No wonder… now this guy's uniqueness in my previous life all makes sense!

No wonder you're EsGod's arch enemy! Is this the choice of Steins;Gate‽

He had snatched the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy that led to Evans losing the opportunity to change his fate, so Han Xiao initially felt somewhat guilty and wanted to give him some compensation.

Now…

The Primal Esper Abilities are not good enough for you!

You are the biggest profit I've made on this trip!

Chapter 1040: EsGod Raising Plan and Universal Treasure Creator

[Esper Ability—Copy]

This was EsGod's core ability, but it had appeared in Evans.

Han Xiao's first response was to suspect what relationship Evans had with EsGod, then he instantly made up a two-million-word romantic novel in his mind. However, after thinking about the storyline in his previous life, he denied this possibility.

The chance of this being a coincidence was higher. In the universe, Espers who awakened the same abilities were not uncommon. Abilities like controlling fire, water, force fields and so on were basically everywhere. Therefore, another person being able to absorb Esper Abilities was not impossible.

However, a coincidence like this still made Han Xiao feel extremely weird. EsGod had been locked in Spacetime Amber by him just not many years ago, and now, a new 'EsGod' had appeared in the outside world… Could this be reincarnation? Did there always have to be an evil lord?

What a surprise, I've met an 'EsGod' at his newbie stage.

Han Xiao was pleasantly surprised.

Having [Esper Ability—Copy], Evans would certainly have to take the path of absorbing the Esper Abilities of others. His talents were suppressed by someone, but now he would have no choice but to take away others' talents. This was all very dramatic and ironic to Han Xiao.

Obviously, without a firm belief, the way this Esper Ability was destined to grow would very easily make its owner fall to the dark side.

Evans, however, had experienced decades as an ordinary person, tasting the bitterness of being at the lowest level of the society, so he might not be as aggressive as EsGod.. Nonetheless, he might have some deeply buried hatred that could explode after being suppressed for too long, and no one could know if that would happen.

He's a double-edged sword, Han Xiao thought. If he can be of use to me, he'll have extraordinary potential. I have to guide him to be on my side as much as I can. He feels grateful to me, so he should be very loyal. If he someday shows any sign of decadence, I'll have no choice but to kill him, so there won't be a second EsGod.

Though powerful, what people were afraid of was not [Esper Ability—Copy] but EsGod himself.

In the hands of EsGod, all the abilities he absorbed had Beyond Grade A strength. Without his strength as the foundation. No matter how many Esper Abilities he absorbed, it would still make no difference.

Absorbing Esper Abilities was a way to obtain more combat methods, they were considered as abilities and would not increase one's own levels and attributes. Therefore, in order for Evans to increase his Grade, there were no shortcuts. He had to slowly train just like the other Espers. Even though he was talented enough to have [Highest Grade Esper Ability Affinity Physique], he would still not be able to skip the process.

At the moment, Evans had only just awakened and was extremely weak, only around Grade E. Although the subject of comparison was that notorious EsGod, how long had EsGod lived? How much combat experience did he have? God knew how long it would take for Evans to reach the level of the Beyond Grade A.

Due to how extremely rare this Esper Ability was, Han Xiao wanted to plan his growing path for him so that it would not be wasted.

EsGod had already proved the limitations of [Esper Ability—Copy]. If he absorbed too many Esper Abilities, his genetic chain would be at risk of shattering.

This meant that the maximum number of Esper Abilities Evans could absorb would increase as his Grade increased. Once that limit was exceeded, he would die. Therefore, the situation of him having thousands of Esper Abilities when he was at a low Grade would never happen.

However, due to Evans' physique, at the same level, the maximum number of Esper Abilities he would be able to absorb should be more than EsGod.

Also, [Esper Ability—Copy] did not guarantee a perfect success rate when absorbing Esper Abilities. EsGod had always absorbed Esper Abilities from Espers whose Grade was lower than his, so there were never any problems.

However, when absorbing the Esper Ability of someone at the same Grade or even at a higher Grade, the success rate would be extremely low.

Therefore, in order for Evans to absorb Esper Abilities from someone whose Grade was higher than his, there were extremely strict requirements. For instance, the target needed to be near death, or the target could be captured. Basically, it would only have a chance to succeed when the target could not resist.

"EsGod has been collecting Esper Abilities for so many years. He's a high-quality material. The Esper Abilities he uses to battle are all quite powerful. Sadly, Evans won't be able to do anything through the Spacetime Amber. If the seal is opened, EsGod will escape straight away. It's only been a few decades; no way his conscience will have shattered this easily. For safety reasons, we have to keep him locked up for at least five hundred years."

The amber blocked any and all energy. The outside world could not inspect the condition of EsGod, and he would not bear the risk of letting EsGod escape to open the seal.

Han Xiao put this thought behind and pondered about Evans' growth path. He soon came up with some ideas.

"It's not suitable for Evans to take EsGod's path. He should plan what to absorb, quality over quantity, so he will benefit from it his whole life."

EsGod was powerful indeed, but he had absorbed way too many Esper Abilities, which made his genetic chain reach the cusp of shattering. EsGod had no use for the vast majority of these abilities. Instead, they suppressed his strength.

Although the army at the super healer Aurora, Han Xiao did not want her to have too much contact with Evans. At most, he would let him use the life force potions.

One reason EsGod absorbed that many abilities was his ambition. He wanted to fuse the Super High Risk Esper Abilities to transform himself and break through the limit of peak Beyond Grade As, becoming an entirely new being.

Another reason was that part of EsGod's ambition came from his experience. Han Xiao had read about his past before. When EsGod was weak, he had always been alone. He relied on himself for everything, and he could only trust himself. Therefore, he wanted to become almighty so that he would never need any friends.

However, Evans had no need to do that, so he had the luxury to only absorb useful and strong Esper Abilities. This might be a much more suitable path.

Seeing that Black Star faced away from him and did not speak for a while, Evans became more confused as time went on. Finally, he asked, "Your Excellency Black Star, I…"

Han Xiao regained his focus. He turned around and patted Evans' shoulder. "Your ability can absorb the Esper Abilities of others. This is an ability with a lot of potential…"

As Han Xiao explained the ability, Evans then understood his own power but frowned. "I don't really like this kind of Esper Ability…"

Evans looked conflicted. His talent had been suppressed for decades, so he did not like the Esper Ability that took away others' talents.

Han Xiao uncontrollably rolled his eyes in his mind.

You think you're buying groceries in the market? So picky.

The Great Mechanic Han then coughed and said with a friendly tone, "Don't worry, since you're now my man, I'll guide your path. I won't allow you to absorb abilities from others whenever you want, so you don't have to be troubled. No one will force you to walk the path of a criminal.

"But, at the same time, I hope you can resist the temptation. Don't have the thought of wanting to make someone else's Esper Ability your own when you see how good it is. Don't walk the wrong path because of a moment's temptation.

"EsGod is the perfect lesson. He fell to evil, caused crimes everywhere, and created countless enemies. In the end, he was still locked up by the group of us and lost his freedom. Therefore, learn from his mistakes. Keep a low profile like me, understood?"

Hearing Black Star's lecture, Evans nodded.

He had heard of the notorious EsGod. Despite having the same ability, he was not the same type of person. He warned himself in his heart to never forget where his heart was and never fall to the side of evil like EsGod.

Han Xiao said a few more words before telling some mechanical soldiers to lead Evans away.

He was the only one left in the room. He touched his chin and murmured, "This guy's ability is worth raising. As long as he doesn't take the wrong path, he'll undoubtedly become someone strong in the future. As for how to help him obtain Esper abilities… Hmm, to me, this should be the easiest part."

Han Xiao chuckled.

In his previous life, EsGod had tried absorbing the players' Esper abilities, so Han Xiao understood that…

It was possible!

Although the players could revive, their bodies were made of existing materials. Other than having strange limitations and turning into light after dying, they would still bleed and get injured from normal battles. Only, the way this was displayed to them would be all kinds of debuffs.

In Version 1.0, there were even organizations that tried to dissect the players. Although, due to their health, not long into the dissection, the players turned into light. Nonetheless, the blood samples collected were no different from normal beings.

If an Esper class player was absorbed by EsGod, he would lose his Esper Ability too, entering the state of [Ability Frozen]. All abilities related to his Esper ability would become gray and unusable. This state was fixed and permanent; no ability could get rid of it, just like how the NPCs' Esper abilities were taken away…

However!

When this player died and respawned, his status would be refreshed, and he would regain his Esper Ability!

This was related to the mechanisms of [Esper Ability—Copy]. The process of this ability could be simply explained as: Snatch → Analyze → Genetic Chain Construction → Fixation → Storage.

After snatching an Esper Ability, [Esper Ability—Copy] would break it down and analyze it, then store this ability in the owner's body in a genetic chain. What constructed these genetic chains was a special matter produced by [Esper Ability—Copy], which was considered the material produced by the owner of this ability himself. Hence, it would not disappear as the players disappeared, just as EsGod would not lose his abilities when the original owner of the ability died.

Therefore, in Han Xiao's previous life, a phenomenon where the players sold their bodies to EsGod in exchange for money appeared. This was something that had never happened before, and it led to the three Universal Civilizations having no choice but to come up with a special policy stating that if Immortals actively gave their Esper abilities to EsGod, they would be seen as wanted criminals. Of course, the players had all kinds of tricks to get past this policy, so this policy rarely had any effect.

Of course, EsGod was no philanthropist. Due to the limitations of his genetic chain, he would only absorb the abilities he was interested in. Otherwise, he would not absorb the players' Esper abilities even if they came right to his doorstep to sacrifice themselves.

Also, this action of the players caused a hilarious misunderstanding. At the start, EsGod thought that this was the three Universal Civilizations' plot to purposely send people over to die to make his genetic chain shatter. After killing many players, only then did he finally notice that these people were sincerely there to commit suic… to give him Esper abilities.

At that time, even the ever so calm EsGod had been completely astonished, which led to him saying one of his signature sentences among the players. "If I'd met you people earlier, I might have been able to become a good person."

Thinking about that, Han Xiao uncontrollably grinned.

"So, I don't even have to do much to help him get Esper abilities. All I have to do is give out a mission to the Esper class players, offering a high enough reward, and people will come forward themselves…"

This way, the millions of Esper players would be the largest material inventory!

Furthermore, no one would die; it was legal!

Although he had given Evans the clear path of choosing quality over quantity, with so many materials, he could slowly gather peak the Esper Abilities that complemented each other and form all kinds of strategies, achieving the most perfect combos!

Having this thought, Han Xiao was completely thrilled. At this time, a new plan was born in his head.

"Phillip!"

"Yes, hum…"

"Sketch up a new plan, the content is to record the various Esper Abilities of all the Esper Immortals under the army's command. Then, according to the effects of these Esper Abilities, simulate all kinds of tactical combos that can be put together. Set the minimum to two Esper abilities, and set the maximum to ten Esper Abilities for the time being. Mark this plan with the highest level of confidentiality. Also, don't mention Evans' existence."

"Okay, hum… This will only occupy a little bit of my memory. What's the name of the plan?"

"Don't have to name it. Just give it a serial number."

Han Xiao really wanted to name it something like 'EsGod Raising Plan', but he thought about it and gave up that idea.

Although his database would basically never be hacked again, Han Xiao still chose to be low profile about this.

He had already made up his mind that before Evans matured, he needed to hide him as a secret weapon.

"Speaking of which, I have the Evolution Cube and the Spacetime Amber, and the army has Hila and Aurora. It's indeed a little too conspicuous. If I even tell anyone I'm planning to create a second EsGod… tsk, the enemies will probably all want to rob me."

Thinking of that, even Han Xiao shivered controllably.

He then rested for a while to digest all these emotions before getting back to the work he was doing earlier, continuing to build the King mechanical suit that was more than halfway done.

He did not know whether it was because of the incredible luck Evans had left in the room or not, but when Han Xiao completed the last process and at the instant the King mechanical suit was complete, a notification suddenly popped up on the interface.

You have built a Gold Grade equipment (Universal Treasure).

You have benefitted from [Spirit Instrument].

You have received 1 God's Trait Transformation Point. (Another cannot be obtained again through the same blueprint.)

One of your random attributes has been decreased by 200…

Randomizing, randomizing complete.

-200 LUK.

You have received 200 Free Attribute Points.

You have received Level One Bonus from [Spirit Instrument]: +2.5% basic success rate of building gold equipment, +1.2% basic success rate of inventing gold blueprints.

You have received a new talent, [Universal Treasure Creator]!

Chapter 1042: Reappeared Shady Trick

Camping corpses was a task that required skill.

To protect the players' fragile hearts, there were many ways to revive they could choose from—revive on the spot, at the nearest city, nearest carrier, or special designated coordinates. They could even not revive and just go offline. Also, they could revive a maximum of ten times every six days. Therefore, camping someone's corpse was pretty difficult.

In his previous life, the fact that Han Xiao was okay despite being completely ruthless was mostly thanks to this kind of reviving method.

However, even with so many difficulties, the players never got tired of camping the other players' corpses. The more common methods were kidnapping, forcing carriers to stop, and so on. In combat mode, there were restrictions to logging off for the players, and they would be punished for forcefully exiting the game. Hence the kidnapping method. They would bring the target to the nearest revive point and surround the target. Forcing carriers to stop made the player revive on the same spot whether they chose to revive on the spot or the nearest carrier. Nonetheless, none of these methods could perfectly deal with the reviving mechanism. Even if all locations were blocked off, the target had to be at least online and not log off.

Hence, the only requirement for camping someone's corpse to succeed was… that the target had a lot of pride.

And from the ID of this pal who made the post, which was [Daddy Is Proud What Are You Going To Do], Han Xiao could clearly feel his unrestrained sense of manliness.

In the post, this [Daddy Is Proud What Are You Going To Do], who was an army player, explained what had happened to him.

"Just some time ago, I was doing a solo errand mission in the free competition zone and came to a transit planet. I met a group of stranger players from another organization, and the moment they saw me, they attacked me without saying anything and killed me.

"I asked them why, but they dared to tell me that they just didn't like my face! I don't know about the others, but there's no way I could put up with that. So, I revived on the spot and fought with them head-on, not intending to give up. These pieces of sh*t then actually really killed me time after time and finished all my revive counts for today. After that, they even private messaged me to mock me, f*ck!

"I was minding my own business, and out of nowhere, I got beat up. Who did I mess with‽ I've already posted the ID of these sons of bi*ches. My brothers, all of you are my fathers today. Please respond to my summon and help me greet their family. Let these *ssholes enjoy the bath of positive energy!"

Han Xiao looked at these IDs, which were clearly all American players of the Demon Race.

He then continued reading the comments and realized that this post had already become a sea of joy.

[Fast Horse: Shocking, agitated dude calls people father at the scene (っ°Д°;)っ]

[Human Hammer: I, your daddy, will avenge you!]

[Cold Sister: Senior keyboard warrior of thirty years reporting for duty!]

[I Can't Take It Anymore: When it comes to scolding people, count on us.]

Other than these chaotic replies, there were also army players who were complaining about experiencing the same thing. It seemed this had happened to quite a lot of people.

However, not everyone was so stubborn. More people were just attacked by a group of players from other organizations out of nowhere. Furthermore, it was not just the Americans; there were players from other countries too, and not all of them were guild members. It was almost like people were hunting the army players.

Han Xiao pondered about the reasoning behind this.

He felt that this was probably a butterfly effect he had caused. In his previous life, everyone was scattered without the Black Star Army. Now, the Black Star Army was the biggest player faction.

The winds howl around the highest peaks.

From the responses of the players, this most likely had nothing to do with NPC organizations and was completely initiated by the players. Maybe some people were hostile toward the army players, or maybe the foreign big guilds worked together secretly. There were only so many possibilities.

Currently, tens of millions of players were swarming into the Flickering World and onto the universal stage. They started attracting the attention of all kinds of organizations. Tens of millions of people was just a droplet of water in the vast sea to a Star Field, but if they were all Immortal Grade B Supers, it would be a force that could not be ignored.

As a part of the universe's ecological system, the players' actions now would affect the others too. Han Xiao's intelligence network had shown that more and more organizations were beginning to study the players, and even more were trying to use the players. The three Universal Civilizations had also moved the recruitment and studying of players up the schedule.

The fact that foreign players were willing to leave their own factions to join the Black Star Army attracted more attention as well. Many organizations were very curious about the source of influence Black Star had among the Immortals. Although Black Star was famous indeed, why was the top choice of so many Immortals the Black Star Army? They could not figure it out.

However, many players joined other factions too, so although the situation surrounding the Black Star Army was interesting, it was not too big a deal. If Han Xiao really had all the players in his army, the dynasty would probably have come to his door to question him the very next day.

"The other organizations did not target the army, but their players actually started causing trouble first."

Han Xiao carefully read all the replies and discovered that the biggest group of people who hunted his players were American, Japanese, and Korean players.

Also, when they attacked the army players, they avoided killing any army soldiers, so it was clearly targeted at the players.

Suddenly, he had a thought and started searching in the forums. As expected, he discovered some anonymous posts that were censored due to the aggressive language used, which were about the players of the other organizations bragging about killing army players and expressing that they were indeed targeting the Black Star Army. They were also very arrogant, mocking the Chinese players they killed by name.

"Interesting, so that's how they're going to play."

Han Xiao suddenly understood the reasoning behind this.

He was not unfamiliar with this method. This had happened among the players in the previous life too, also during Version 4.0.

This was a very shady method. The people behind this were undoubtedly the big clubs. Basically, they secretly gathered some of their local players to hunt the players of the target faction. Then, these players would be told to taunt and provoke as much as possible, as aggressively as possible on the forums, to trigger the rage of the target faction players, starting an insulting war. Afterward, they would then let people secretly guide the focus of the situation to race, nationality, and area discrimination, causing hatred.

The goal of this was to control their local players' faction preference by creating collective hatred.

Since the players these clubs could directly control were very few compared to the normal local players, who made up the majority, someone in his previous life thought of this extremely shady and low idea to influence the normal players' preference in picking factions.

For example, a faction had a million players, among whom there were 800,000 Chinese players and 200,000 American players. The American clubs would then start hunting the Chinese players, provoking and taunting to make the Chinese players retaliate and insult them too. They would then guide the topic into the hatred between the nations.

This way, the 200,000 American players in this faction would, of course, not be happy, so they would join the internet war. The clubs would then keep fanning the flames and making the situation worse.

The result would be, a lot of these 200,000 Americans would quit this faction out of their anger toward the Chinese players, and more American players would not want to join this faction. This was just one of the methods the big clubs used to manipulate the faction preference of their local players. They created hatred, and using that hatred, they increased the unity of the players of their country.

The reason for this was very simple—the clubs did not want their local players to work for the factions that the clubs of the other countries were in. They only wanted their local players to work for the factions they were in.

To normal players, the more players in one faction, the stronger the competition. But to clubs, local players represented cheap labor. Be it during normal developments or national wars, as long as the clubs made announcements, the normal players would most likely respond and become free manpower.

Normal players wanted to enjoy the game freely, which the professional players had to respect too. However, clubs and official guilds were commercial organizations; their goal was to gain achievements in the Pro League and make a profit.

Therefore, after Version 4.0 started in the previous life, with the Americans in the lead, some clubs started to manipulate their fans at all costs, using all sorts of dirty methods. This led to the forums' environment becoming contaminated to a certain extent, so the mainstream factions of the clubs of the other countries would be weakened, and they would become stronger… Simply put, they were robbing leeks from others.

Only clubs of a very few countries did not take part in such things, and the Chinese were one of them.

The Chinese had always been united, and now that most of the Chinese players were in the Black Star Army, there was no need to use such shady methods at all.

"Tsk, the first reappearance of this trick, and it's aimed at me. Plus, it's from the clubs of multiple countries."

Han Xiao thought about it and understood what these clubs were thinking.

It was basically because the foreign clubs did not want the army players' forces to keep getting bigger. Otherwise, the army would have too many advantages among the factions. Not only would that reduce the development space of the other faction, but it would also give the Chinese clubs free manpower, which was basically sending money to the enemies, to these foreign clubs.

"Just as I expected, the army is too outstanding, so the Chinese clubs became targets. Although these foreign clubs are not targeting me, if I let them continue doing this, my leek farm might shrink."

Han Xiao did not panic at all. Rather, he smiled.

"Isn't this a perfect opportunity to strengthen the sense of belonging of the new army members that is delivered to my doorsteps?"

Why were the Alliance and the Horde so united? One reason was their background story and the game setting, but the more direct reason was that the players of the two factions were fighting each other all the time.

Creating a shared target—this was a great way to rapidly increase the sense of unity of a group!

"Discrimination is a factor in the real life. I indeed can't deal with that right now, but I can target those main factions that you foreign clubs are in.

"You're manipulating players through nationality differences, so I shall make use of the difference between factions.

"When the foreign clubs gather people to hunt the army players, their factions won't reward them. Therefore, to them, this is just a matter between the players.

"However, if I announce a Bounty Mission, stating that as long as the army players kill the players of your factions, they'll be rewarded, what will happen?

"At that point, your local normal players might even beat you up!

"How can those people secretly hired by the clubs compare with the eight million warriors of our army‽

"You wanted to play dirty? You asked for it!

"Hehe, since you people can't be satisfied with peacefully developing your forces and play these dirty tricks all day, let me add more wood to the fire and make your business more popular."

Han Xiao grinned wickedly, sat up from the lazy throne, opened the faction interface, and started drafting the Bounty Mission.

At the same time, on a private player chat channel, the high position members of the professional clubs of many countries were online.

Among these were America's Devil and Key; Japan's Hydra, Amaterasu, and Werewolf; Korea's Kimchi and Triple Star Bomb; Italy's Classical and Pizza; and Southeast Asia's Red Bay, Island, and Titan. Many of the regular attendees of the international tournament were in this channel.

At this time, the topic these people were discussing was indeed related to the Black Star Army.

Just like Han Xiao guessed, as more and more players of the various countries changed factions and joined the Black Star Army, these guilds who were not planning to change their factions could not put up with it anymore. They secretly worked together and planned to restrain the Black Star Army's rapidly growing player base.

"… The people on our side are moving according to plan. The public opinion part is still in preparation. The players' emotions need time to be developed," a high ranking member of the Key club said.

"The circumstances are actually beneficial to us. China has managed to win two consecutive years. This is their pride, and they have this sense of superiority, so the public opinion will not be tough to manipulate. Steer the topic in this direction, toward how the normal players of the various countries are targeted because the teams of their country did not achieve optimal results, then let the Chinese players insult us. This way, more anger can be created."

"Actually, tricks like this are not difficult to see through. The players are quite smart…"

"Don't worry. Players will be players. Once it gets to their head, reasoning won't be important. The Pro League is a great conversation topic. It'll be easy to trigger their emotions."

"Let's hope it works. We're all in different factions. The biggest threat now is the Black Star Army. There are way too many players there. If we don't weaken them, the Chinese clubs will have way too big an advantage."

"It'll be best if we can isolate them."

As for the stand of the Black Star Army, it was not within their consideration. To them, all of this was just between the players. The NPC factions were just the background.

Chapter 1044: Exposing One's Fangs

At the frontline exploration base of the Black Star Army in the Emerald Star Cluster…

In the bright, empty training room, Hila was levitating in midair, her eyes closed and breathing slow. A red brilliance surrounded her body, and the energy fluctuations she emitted made the high collared cloak of the Crimson Snake uniform flutter like dancing black and red clouds.

In front of her floated a deep red ball of concentrated death energy, and suspended in the middle was a faint golden glow. Golden blood vessel-like threads radiated from that glow, spreading throughout the ball.

At this moment, Hila's brows suddenly frowned, and the energy ball in front of her boiled as though a violent chemical reaction had occurred. It exploded, the death energy reverberating across the room.

"We failed again, Sis."

Aurora's annoyed voice sounded in Hila's mind.

"It's okay. It's not your fault." Hila shook her head.

With the qualitative change in one's Esper Ability's strength, control, and other characteristics, the Esper would be able to bring out and develop more uses for this ability.

Because there existed an exclusive vitality link between the two, after Aurora entered the Calamity Grade, this link was further strengthened, giving birth to a two-way telepathic channel for them to communicate with each other.

As for the transmission of life energy, this was originally limited by the distance. Right now, their personal project was to develop an energy transmission channel that would ignore the factor of distance. However, they had not succeeded yet and were still looking for a method.

Now that Aurora had entered the Calamity Grade, Hila reckoned that she could protect herself. Thus, she no longer restricted Aurora, allowing her to utilize the abilities and life energy freely.

"Sis, actually, the life link that ignores distance already has an embryonic form. The life energy is constantly emitted from my side, but it cannot be transmitted to yours."

"It's not a complete failure." Hila nodded. "Actually, I did receive a small amount of life energy, but the energy loss is too severe, which limits me to only receiving one ten thousandth of it. The way I see it, most of your energy seems to be absorbed by an unknown secondary dimension, and that secondary dimension has a weak connection with me, which is why I could feel its presence."

"Is that so? I didn't feel anything." Aurora was surprised.

"I only sensed this when I advanced to the Beyond Grade A realm. I think that if we wish to complete the link, we need to first solve this obstacle. I previously sent my death energy into this secondary dimension, but once it entered, it was cut off from me entirely. I'm afraid I'll need to find time to go there in person. I always feel that it has some secret related to us. Call it the intuition of a Beyond Grade A."

As she spoke, Hila shook her head and lifted her finger. There was a bright golden light floating on her fingertip, about the size of a peanut. This was the life energy she had obtained from Aurora.

With just her eyes, she manipulated the sesame-sized particles of death energy into this cluster of life energy, and the next moment, a brilliant light flashed as the two energies melted together. The red and golden light spots merged into a light spot with the color of orange gold.

"Sis, did you succeed?"

"Nope, I'm still exploring the ratio needed to successful fusion. Right now, I can only merge this small amount of energy."

Hila lightly breathed out. She had tried to fuse their energies a long time ago, but due to their lack of control over their Esper abilities, they had never succeeded. At that time, they had thought that it was a conflict in their energy natures that caused this.

However, now that Hila was in the Beyond Grade A realm and Aurora had also entered the Calamity Grade, Hila reattempted the combination, only to find out that their energies were actually combinable, but they were unstable and required powerful manipulation abilities to maintain the balance.

After the fusion, it would turn into an orangey-gold light cluster, with different characteristics. Although the healing and killing effects were still present, these two characteristics were not strengthened but in fact weakened. Hila had not yet studied the special effects the fused energy would have.

At this moment, a communication request sounded.

Beep beep!

A virtual screen appeared, and the vice-captain's image popped up. The shock on his face had not faded as he said, "Your Excellency, the Pope of the Arcane Church wishes to speak to you. Should I transfer the call over?"

Hila's pupils shrank.

For someone seated at the very top to come knocking, Hila thought it was surprising.

She thought for a while before saying, "Transfer it."

Very quickly, the screen in front of her changed to the shadow of the Pope.

The three Universal Civilizations often had their leaders appear in the news, so Hila naturally knew who he was. Thus, her expression was indifferent as she spoke.

"May I know your intention in looking for me?"

Because of the conflict between the Arcane Church and the Black Star Army, Hila did not bother showing much respect.

The Pope did not bother beating around the bush either. "I would like to invite you to join our Arcane Church."

"The leader of a Universal Civilization actually came to personally invite me, I'm really flattered… If Black Star was here, that's what he would say." Hila remained impassive. "But I'm not him."

The Pope slowly continued. "We've looked into you, and you're someone who values and pursues strength. The Arcane Church can help to give you incredible strength. I…"

"It's alright. I reject your offer." Hila did not even wish to listen on and refused flatly.

"… So long as you join as an ally, you can state any conditions."

"Not interested."

The Pope paused, expressionless. "The reason you insist on following Black Star, is it because of your own personal feelings?"

"Nothing to do with you."

The Pope nodded. "My offer will stand. If you happen to have a change in heart, the Arcane Church will forever welcome you with open arms."

He then ended the communication.

Looking at the darkened screen, Hila could not help but frown.

The Arcane Church's Pope had personally appeared, which meant that he had more sincerity than the Crimson Dynasty. However, this could be because of their relationship as enemies, which would require him to step up if he wanted to poach her.

If it was an ordinary Beyond Grade A that had received such a treatment, they would likely have accepted it on the spot. However, she would not consider leaving the Black Star Army for the time being. Thus, no matter how good the offer, she did not hesitate to refuse.

…

On the other end, there was a fleet of spaceships making their way toward the Black Star stronghold in the Emerald Star Cluster.

The insignia of the fleet represented a small mercenary group, but it actually carried several Beyond Grade A combatants from the Arcane Church.

'Child of Light' Sagman glanced at his communicator. "The Pope's intentions have been conveyed. The poaching has failed. We can begin our operation."

The Arcane Church had long prepared both plans. During this time, the Beyond Grade As had assembled, and if the Pope failed to persuade her, they would strike and eliminate Hila, preventing any mishaps in the future.

"The situation now is beneficial to us, as both the dynasty and Black Star have yet to discover that we have assembled. It's best to do a quick battle and make no mistakes like before," Taylor said.

In the past, it would have taken the Beyond Grade As a long time to gather because of the different Star Fields, so any action would have been discovered a long time ago. However, because a large number of them were in the Flickering World, they were close to each other, facilitating their actions. Before their enemy discovered them, they could take action whilst they were unaware.

"It's best to shift Hila away from the stronghold. Otherwise, the allies of the dynasty can quickly support her through the stargate."

"Then we'll leave this job to you, Tolaen. You go provoke Hila and draw her out. The further the better," Sagman said.

Tolaen paused for a while, his heart unwilling. In the end, he gritted his teeth and said, "Let me try."

"Well, if Hila does not accept the challenge, we will first destroy the stronghold's stargate. It's a pity that Sun Hunter will not be able to participate in that activity. Taylor, you're a Mage with more flexible means. Destroying the stargate will be left to you and me." Sagman hesitated, before continuing in a deep tone. "As for the Lord's Avatar of Black Star that will be beside Hila…"

At this moment, the doppelganger of Kasuyi, which had always been silent, said, "I'll hold him off."

The Arcane Church had brought out enough benefits to allow Kasuyi to participate in this operation. However, he did not like the act of besieging others or bullying newcomers, so he merely sent a doppelganger over as insurance.

"Alright, we have no guarantee of beating Black Star's avatar. Only you will be able to suppress him." Sagman nodded.

"It's a pity that His Excellency Wuornos could not appear as well, or else killing Hila would only be a matter of seconds," 'Desolate Beast' Mercer muttered.

"Stop imagining things. Wuornos will never leave the Temple of God. He will not involve himself in vulgar mortal affairs." Taylor shook his head.

The six of them present were 'Child of Light' Sagman, 'World Gate' Taylor, 'Desolate Beast' Mercer, 'Red Devil' Tolaen, a doppelganger of Kasuyi, and a Lord's Avatar of a Mechanic.

The nature of Kasuyi's doppelganger was similar to the Lord's Avatar of the Mechanic class, which carried a part of the body's combat power. It could not be compared to the quasi-Beyond Grade A doppelganger ability of EsGod.

Such a lineup just to deal with Hila, this was truly overkill.

However, the difference between this and the battle at Planet Lighthouse was that the allies from the dynasty were missing, and Black Star's true body would also not be present, which meant the absence of the Spacetime Amber. The Arcane Church thought that this situation was favorable, not to mention that their target was Hila, who was easier to deal with than the cockroach that was Black Star.

Kasuyi's doppelganger turned his head away to look out of the porthole, declining to continue the conversation with the rest.

"Manison, you probably wouldn't make a move right… If Hila dies, Black Star will certainly go crazy… Hehe, such a difficult choice this time.

"You're not suitable to act, and I understand, so let me take your place in this show.

"With me around, she will not die."

Chapter 1045: Undercurrents

The Federation of Light's territory in the free competition zone was in another Star Cluster.

A fleet was hovering in space, with the total number of battleships amounting to two million. Among them, the largest flagship was the Eternal Light. Two humongous mechanical rings circled around the entire fleet, one horizontally positioned and one vertically positioned, perpendicular to each other.

These two mechanical rings, which were larger than the stargate itself, were the strategic Universal Treasure of the Federation of Light, the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device.

The components of the mechanical rings were intricate, and a large number of mechanical ships were being connected to each section of the ring for debugging and maintenance work.

On the bridge of the flagship, the gathered Beyond Grade A members of the Federation of Light stood in a row, looking at the scene outside.

"To actually utilize such strategic equipment, it seems like the federation's upper echelons really value the action this time." A muscular green-skinned man sighed. On his head was a purple runic turban that glittered constantly.

This person was Womre, with the moniker 'Energy Soul'. He was a pugilist based in the federation and was adept at energy-based attacks. As a Beyond Grade A descendant race, he possessed unique racial talents that gave him superior skills. Standing with his hands behind his back, he gave off the bearing of a grandmaster.

"This matter concerns the unlocking of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter's seal, so it is worth them investing the huge resources to activate the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device," Hades said. "The Arcane Church will definitely make some sort of move. When they begin to stall Black Star's avatar, we'll activate the teleporter to appear directly in the battlefield."

"That's right," the commander explained. "We also have another Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device in the fleet, so once we grab Hila, we'll be able to teleport back, and the operation will be a success."

The Federation of Light was different from the Arcane Church; their objective was to capture Hila so as to force Black Star to unseal the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. Because of their Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device, they had a natural advantage in allowing them the ability to escape the battle once they obtained their target.

The Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device was able to send someone away but could not bring them back, so the fleet equipped itself with a second set of teleporters, along with a self-destruct device. Once the teleportation was completed, it would destroy itself, preventing others from taking it and studying the technology.

If they could unseal the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, paying the cost of a Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device was acceptable to the federation. While expensive to build, a Universal Civilization did not lack money, and it was not difficult to build them if one had the relevant technology. They had quite a number of Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Devices lying in their warehouse, acting as a deterrent to other civilizations.

"It's easier said than done. While the fleet has brought along another set of teleporters, it takes a lot of time for it to be arranged and charged, and there will definitely be disturbances during this period," one of them in a mechanical suit said. His name was Jackornitz, a Beyond Grade A Mechanical Pugilist of the Federation of Light.

"Thus, the reason we're bringing this fleet along. There are a lot of unmanned ships within this fleet, which will speed up the deployment of the transmitter, and it will help to protect the transmitter from interference. There's also the mechanical army of Her Excellency Mornisa to aid us, enough to allow us to retreat," Hades replied.

"Yep." A machine by the side nodded. This was her Lord's Avatar, and she also brought along a mechanical troop, which was the best candidate to block off the enemy's path. She would not feel regret even if all of them were completely destroyed.

"Don't forget, Black Star is a Virtual Mechanic and can invade our fleet's controls."

"Romo and I will be responsible for the virtual defense remotely, and the main artificial intelligence of the federation will also invest the majority of its computing power into the firewall. While Black Star is a pinnacle Beyond Grade A Super, he can't break through our defense while being distracted by the fighting," Mornisa explained.

The Romo mentioned by her was a Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanic from the federation, responsible for guarding the quantum network and the main intelligence network of the federation. He was not participating in this operation, but he would provide some form of remote assistance.

"It's a pity that the Mechanic Emperor is not planning to take part in this operation. If he were in charge, we would not have to be afraid of the Virtual Intrusion of Black Star at all." Hades sighed.

At this moment, Sierron, who was standing with his arms crossed in the center of all the people, snorted before indifferently speaking. "Humph, Manison refuses to come, and Oulou is also in the Central Galaxy, so I have to lead this team. I don't care about the rest, just leave Black Star to me. If there's anyone from the Arcane Church who tries to stop us, I'll deal with the strongest too."

'Star Shatterer' Sierron, a pinnacle level Beyond Grade A Pugilist, was the head of the federation team for this operation, and he was also a member of The Ancient Ones.

On the other side, a multi-faceted crystal was suspended in midair, its body shining with a deep blue color. It sent out mental fluctuations. "The task of capturing Hila can be left to me."

This was a crystal life form called Crystal Soul. It was a Beyond Grade A Psychic.

The Federation was sending seven Beyond Grade As this time—'Energy Soul' Womre, 'Lone Ranger' Jackornitz, 'Mechanic Empress' Mornisa, Hades, Crystal Soul, 'Star Shatterer' Sierron, and 'Defender' Romo, who was providing remote assistance.

This lineup was stronger, with one additional participant compared to the Arcane Church.

…

In the Garu Star Cluster within the Flickering World, Sorokin stood at one of the branch offices of the Limitless Financial Group, overlooking the dense comet trails in space. These were the trajectories left by the spaceships coming and leaving the area.

This place was an interstellar transit station, located in the territory of the Black Star Army. Not far away was one of the stargate transportation hubs, so it was very prosperous and led to the surroundings of Black Star Palace.

Sorokin squinted and muttered to himself, "A good show should begin soon."

As the middleman who was responsible for the sending of messages to the federation and the church, he knew how they would act when Hila's data was given to them. There was a high probability of both civilizations taking action.

As he admired the scenery, he began to hypothesize the possible scenarios.

"The federation has the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device, which gives them the initiative. It is likely they will lurk behind and move later, waiting for the Arcane Church to first make a move. The Mechanic Emperor is likely not participating in this operation, so it is likely that Sierron will be the one at the helm. As for the church's side, whether it's Kasuyi or Sun Hunter that's leading, they will most likely be paddling and not really moving for real… Heh, the Meeting of the Gods really affected quite a few people this time, Black Star."

Just as he was speculating, a magic transportation door lit up in his room, and someone walked out. The person stood behind Sorokin and waved his hand, casually destroying the door.

Feeling the magical fluctuations, Sorokin turned around, and a superficial smile surfaced.

"Your Excellency Traveler."

The person was a humanoid creature, with a gray complexion and no nose. He had yellow, crystal eyes, with vertical slit-like pupils, messy gray hair, and a gold ring. He only had three fingers on each hand, with one holding onto a staff that was twisted like a branch. He wore a gold headband with a brown hooded robe.

The Traveler, a Beyond Grade A mage, spent most of his time travelling around the secondary dimensions, and he did not appear in the outside world often. On the surface, he was a neutral Beyond Grade A, but he actually maintained a secret relationship with multiple Super Star Cluster level civilizations. He was also present during the Meeting of the Gods, albeit remaining taciturn and almost non-existent.

"The Super Star Cluster Alliance has employed me to aid you." The Traveler looked at Sorokin with interest. "This is interesting. What sort of deal have you reached with them, to actually have them send me to challenge Black Star?"

"There are some matters that are currently happening, and if my predictions are correct, the federation and the church will appear in the next few days to attack Hila. During that time, I hope you will be able to go to Black Star Palace and announce that you wish to challenge Black Star." Sorokin blandly smiled.

He had secretly contacted the Star Cluster alliance and revealed some bits of news, reaching a new deal to interfere in the process.

"Ah, so what you mean is…"

"That's right. Go up for a challenge, and if Black Star spars with you, he will have to split his attention, which will cause the strength of his consciousness to drop, reducing the aid he can provide Hila. If he does not agree to the spar, it will mean that his true body is not in the camp, which means you will fight against Ames. I heard that he has a close relationship with Ames, which will leave him torn as to whom he should help first… No matter what, he will be restricted."

Traveler quietly listened before speaking up. "You seem to be very clear that this operation will be a success. What benefits will you obtain?"

"Hila's existence is a threat, and I believe the majority of Beyond Grade As do not wish to see such a character growing." Sorokin laughed. "Furthermore, even if she joins an alliance, she will definitely choose the Crimson Dynasty. Thus, this poses a danger to the other two universal civilizations."

"It doesn't just stop there, right?" Traveler refuted. "You even dragged the Super Star Clusters into the mess. You definitely have bigger objectives."

"Haha, alright, there's no harm in telling you." Sorokin narrowed his eyes. "Do you think the other two are kicking up such a big fuss over such one Hila? No, Hila is merely a catalyst. The bigger reason is the Meeting of the Gods that took place not long ago."

"Oh?" Traveler's eyes flickered.

"Think about it, the federation and the church sending their Beyond Grade As to do such a thing… once they succeed, how will Black Star respond? Both civilizations are trying to promote infighting among Beyond Grade As. If successful, then the Meeting of the Gods will only exist in name…" Sorokin's mouth twisted up. "But I dare to boldly guess that the aim of the federation and the church is to leave just one or two of the Beyond Grade A allies alive from this operation, using this grudge to fuel their hatred."

Traveler frowned. "It can't be, right? The situation isn't that bad."

"Who knows? Throughout my long lifespan, I've awoken to a fact… that you should never believe you're irreplaceable to the Universal Civilizations."

Traveler stared at him before slowly saying, "Then, what about you? You're also a member of the Beyond Grade As, but you're not on the same front as them."

"Aren't you the same?"

"I'm justified, but you're a true neutral."

"Hehe, if I really have to give a reason, it's just that I don't like the idea of having an individual rule supreme. I'm a businessman, and I believe in having a collective entity. I believe only in the market."

Sorokin revealed an insincere smile.

"No matter how strong a Beyond Grade A is, they are still an individual. Only the diversification of civilizations will be able to make the cold universe flourish. Civilization is the cornerstone of society itself, the protagonist of the universe. Individuals outside these specifications are merely dispensable parts of our interstellar society. Getting rid of them might even make the world more peaceful and prosperous.

"The Beyond Grade As have too many privileges. If you do not know how to be satisfied with what you have, you will reach out to places that you should not touch, causing new turmoil in the universe. I don't want to see this, so the fewer Beyond Grade As in the universe, the better."

Traveler was a little surprised. "I always thought you only knew how to make money. To think you had such a side."

"You can think of me as a warden, responsible for the balance of the universe."

Sorokin turned around, and after a momentary pause, he added another sentence.

"… Of course, money still has to be earned."

…

Somewhere in the Emerald Star Cluster, Han Xiao was hiding in the mechanical workshop within his spaceship.

"Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy Carrier, Test #17."

A silver and red mechanical carrier stood on the test bench. The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy cylindrical container was fixed on top of the mechanical body by four mechanical arms, connecting both the container and carrier with dense transmission wires.

Phillip sat on Han Xiao's shoulder, reporting, "The carrier has completed the self-diagnostics. Status is excellent. The state of Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy is currently well behaved, and the connection is stable. Should we begin the energy transfer?"

Han Xiao nodded. "Begin."

The instruments activated when he spoke, and the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy turned active, rushing into the mechanical carrier along the transmission wires.

Buzz!

The mechanical carrier jerked, its eyes lighting up with a red glow, becoming more and more glaring. Its body vibrated at a high frequency as it endured the load of the Primal Esper Ability Entity.

Han Xiao fully released his Mechanical Sense, staring closely at the carrier as he observed every detail.

In his eyes, the violent Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was gradually being constrained by the carrier and had begun to fuse with the special conversion components within the body. The function of this component was similar to that of the host's cells to contain and refine the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy.

After a long period of time, the final speck of energy merged into the carrier.

Hu!

The carrier released a crimson colored shockwave, creating a gale in the room.

"Fusion complete. Synchronization rate is 72%. Compatibility, 75%. Load on the carrier is at 41%…" Phillip began reading out the results.

"Finally, it succeeded." Han Xiao's expression was joyful.

The carrier could not even perform the first step of fusion before, but now it had finally merged with the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. While continuous optimization was required, this was a good start and could already be directly used in combat.

The creation of the carrier for the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was different from that of the mechanical soldiers. Its technical requirements were extremely sophisticated, not only needing to integrate the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy but also to prevent it from seizing control of the body.

Fortunately, Han Xiao had obtained the cell sample of Evans, which spared him from a lot of detours.

Chapter 1046: Enemy Spotted

The mechanical carrier played a similar role as a host, accommodating the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy and using its own Psionic core to exert a force in order to drive the Primal Chaos' abilities. It did not need to start from scratch like ordinary human hosts and could directly exert a strong combat power.

The combat power was wholly dependent on the performance of the carrier, as well as its fusion rate with the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy. In simple terms, this situation was similar to that of EsGod—an inherently strong host would allow the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy to burst forth with its fullest strength.

However, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy's main purpose was to provide energy, similar to a tool. It would be constrained within the carrier, and it would be the carrier itself or the artificial intelligence Sparta that controlled the body to fight instead.

Because this carrier was only the first prototype, there was still a lot of room for improvement, so Han Xiao did not turn it into an Apostle Weapon immediately.

"This model will be named [Mysterious Energy Host—First Generation]. I'll come out with a new code name when it becomes an Apostle Weapon."

Han Xiao was quite satisfied. He had a lot of skills that could increase the upper limit of his mechanical skills, so he still had vacancies to create Apostle Weapons.

"Noted, hum… The model name has been recorded, and its entry in the database is complete."

Han Xiao nodded. He then sized up the carrier carefully before saying, "How do you feel?"

The next moment, a mental fluctuation was released, and the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy said, "It's a little too cozy and uncomfortable. Give me a better carrier in the future."

"Relax, the model has already been created, and optimization will be a simple process." Han Xiao waved his hand casually.

"Humph, replace this carrier with a mechanical life form so that there will at least be someone to converse with me. Right now, I feel like I'm trapped within a prison." The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy was grumbling nonstop.

Han Xiao suddenly recalled something and interrupted, "Oh yes, do you think it's possible if I were to split you into eight equal pieces to create a team of Mysterious Energy Hosts?"

"Don't even think about it!" The Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy immediately lashed out. "I won't allow you to mutilate my body! Ab! So! Lute! Ly! Not!"

"What an intense reaction. Is it unbearable for your senses?" Han Xiao was a little curious. He could not help but ask that upon thinking of EsGod.

"Humph, it's equivalent to you dismembering a person and that person having to watch others use his body parts as weapons, playing with his body at will. Furthermore, the pain inflicted on the parts will still be transmitted back to the brain, so you tell me whether this is good or not," the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy grumbled in dissatisfaction.

"Cough, treat it as I never mentioned it."

Thinking about it, Han Xiao realized that the scene was a little gruesome and coughed to hide his embarrassment. He pretended that nothing of the sort had been spoken.

Next, he tested the combat power of the First Generation Mysterious Energy Host, applying many scenarios that would require the usage of Esper Abilities. The results only left him with satisfaction.

As a Super High Risk Esper Ability, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy definitely had a plethora of abilities. It could strengthen itself, radiate the powerful dual attributes of psychic and spatial energies, and fly at high speed. It could even shuttle through secondary dimensions and extract energy directly from the planetary cores.

Since it had yet to receive the bonuses offered by a mechanical life form and Apostle Weapon, its combat power was far lower than a Beyond Grade A, but once the Mysterious Energy Host turned into an Apostle Weapon, it would likely become the most capable existence among the Apostle Weapons. Even Psionic Prime, who had been continuously evolving for many years, might not be its opponent.

"As long as the optimization is completed, the Mysterious Energy Host will become my top fighter and might even defeat ordinary Beyond Grade As."

Obtaining another strong helper in battle left Han Xiao overjoyed.

At this moment, Phillip vibrated before saying, "Master, hum… There's news from Black Star Palace. A Beyond Grade A has come knocking."

"Who is it?" Han Xiao's eyes narrowed.

Since it was Black Star Palace, who would dare go and lay their hands on his home base?

This person's courage was really too great. With the resources he had poured into Black Star Palace, alongside the troops stationed there, one would require two Beyond Grade As to attack it in order to pose a threat.

"Uh, it's not an enemy. It's an ally of the dynasty, Silver Shadow."

Han Xiao immediately jerked to a stop, his expression a little puzzled.

Why did this guy come over to my base camp in secret to find me?

"Who's receiving him now? Did he mention his intentions?"

"Ames has received him. He came here with a gift and would like to request for an opportunity to use the Evolution Cube."

"So, that's what this is…" Han Xiao figured.

Previously, when he fought with Silver Shadow, he defeated him, thus robbing Silver Shadow of the chance to request to use the Evolution Cube. Thus, he had most likely been searching for bargaining chips that would allow him to do an exchange.

"What sort of presents did he bring for me?" Han Xiao was curious.

"It seems like he brought some rare blueprints and materials. I have no idea where he got them."

"Blueprints… that works."

Han Xiao had already decided to properly befriend this Uber, so when he asked about the bargaining chips, he had set the bar low. As long as he showed a favorable attitude, then he would lend Silver Shadow the Evolution Cube. In this regard, Han Xiao's style was to treat each individual differently. People like Heber who were always annoying him would not be able to borrow the Evolution Cube even if he gave the entire Bloodshed Land to him.

"What a coincidence, to come precisely when my true body is not in the base." Han Xiao tapped Phillip's round face with his finger. "So, where's the Throne now?"

"Reporting, it has almost arrived at Black Star Palace. The ETA is in a few hours, hum…" Phillip gurgled as he hugged Han Xiao's finger.

"Then let him converse up with Ames for the time being. I'll be there once the Throne has arrived."

With the King already crafted, Han Xiao had gotten his mechanical army to secretly transport the warp point 'Throne' as well as Evans back to their main camp, Black Star Palace. It had already been some time since they did so, and with the exclusive stargate passage of the Black Star Army, they took many shortcuts. They were already nearing Black Star Palace.

The moment the Throne arrived in his palace, he would be able to utilize the King to warp directly there. As long as he did not stay longer than three minutes, he would be able to re-activate the charge and return to his original position before the cooldown began.

At the same time, in the Army Commander's reception room in Black Star Palace, Silver Shadow placed both hands on his knees, sitting up straight, appearing cautious and polite.

And opposite him, Ames was seated on the main seat, one hand supporting her chin, while the other telekinetically brought three wine glasses to the table. She smiled. "No need to be polite. Let's have something to drink first."

By the side, Feidin smiled lightly. "Your Excellency Silver Shadow, the Army Commander has just gone to inspect the territories and will be back in a few hours. Please wait for a moment."

"Alright." Silver Shadow nodded before lifting the glass and emptying it.

Ames sized up Silver Shadow's gleaming body with some interest. "I heard from Black Star that you have good strength, and he's very optimistic about your potential."

"Thank you. I'm also deeply respectful of His Excellency Black Star." Silver Shadow hesitated for a while before continuing. "Actually, I have a question to ask…"

"What is it?" Ames lightly smiled as she lifted the glass to sip at her wine.

"Black Star is not here, but why is it you that is welcoming me?" Silver Shadow was a little hesitant as he spoke.

In his opinion, while the Black Star Army and Floating Dragon Island were allies, there was no need for them to replace each other to meet other Beyond Grade As. After all, the officers of the army were present, and the Dragon Emperor should be a guest. However, it seemed like she was treating this place like her house.

Unless… the rumors were true, that Black Star and the Dragon Emperor had… that sort of relationship?

"How is that surprising?" Ames raised a brow. "Black Star told me to come over to meet him, but he ended up going away, so of course I'm the one to welcome the Beyond Grade A guests instead."

Hearing this, Silver Shadow felt that there were a lot of hidden meanings within.

Such a natural tone… ha, the rumors were indeed true!

He had actually felt it strange at the start. Why would Ames come all the way from afar to visit Black Star Palace? But now it was all clear. If they really had such a relationship, it was no big deal for Black Star to call the Dragon Emperor over to spend some long and sleepless nights together.

Thinking about this made Silver Shadow subconsciously display an even more respectful attitude. While he was someone who did not enjoy small talk, he tried his best to accommodate Ames' requests.

After all, he had a request to ask of Black Star, and since a 'family member' had come out to greet him, it would be rude for him to snub them.

At the same time, in the Emerald Star Cluster, a spaceship flew over from the distance, slowly approaching the entrance of the Black Star Army's stronghold.

Seeing this, the defense force in outer space immediately separated two battleships, intercepting the ship and issuing a warning on the wide area channel.

"Visitor, please stop advancing and identify yourself!"

After the message was sent, the strange spaceship slowly switched off, hovering in outer space.

But the next moment, a tyrannical energy fluctuation burst out, and all energy detection radars in the entire stronghold instantly rang, sending out endless warning alarms.

Boom!

"Alert! Alert! High-energy fluctuations detected. The model is being matched… Match found. The source is determined to be an energy release from a Beyond Grade A!"

Swoosh!

A commotion erupted throughout the stronghold, and the fleet in outer space immediately gathered. The cannons on the ground also raised their muzzles toward the air, locking onto the spaceship, and a large number of battleships rose into the air. The stronghold instantly entered a state of combat.

The next moment, the figure of Tolaen appeared on the wide area channel, laughing arrogantly as his entire body blazed with Demonfire.

"Ahahahaha… Hila! I'm here to get my revenge! Last time, I was beaten by you, but today, I shall wash away my humiliation. Do you dare fight me once more!"

As he spoke, his Beyond Grade A aura slammed against the stronghold.

In the training room, Hila suddenly opened her eyes, her gaze cold.

The warning from Han Xiao a while ago reappeared on her mind, which made her more cautious in dealing with matters.

Seeing that the defeated person had actually come looking for another battle with her, she thought to herself, What a fraud… does he really take me for a fighting idiot?

At this moment, the Vice Commander contacted her.

"Your Excellency Hila, he's challenging you. What should we do?"

Hila had an indifferent expression, blandly replying, "What does the army manual say about how to deal with an enemy that's close to the stronghold? Do I still need to teach you? Just because the other party is a Beyond Grade A, you suddenly do not know what to do. What's the use of having you around?"

The Vice Commander shrank his neck. "I… I understand."

Being surrounded in the starry sky by battleships, Tolaen patiently waited after sending out his battle request. He sneered to himself. With Hila's character as a fighting nut, there's a high probability she will agree. Kasuyi and the rest are hiding in the vicinity. As long as I lead her over whilst pretending to fight with her, we can complete this ambush.

Just as he was planning his movements, he found out that his vision was gradually brightening.

Tolaen looked up in a hurry, only to see that the Black Star Army fleet surrounding him had begun to open fire without any greetings.

The light of countless energy cannons filled his vision!

Tolaen's expression paled.

F*ck me, you're not following the script at all!

Chapter 1047: Forced Attack and Acting

Boom!

The spaceship that was targeted turned into dust in an instant. Under the attacks of countless spaceships, not a single remnant could escape the fate of being completely annihilated. Not a scrap of the wreckage remained.

Not far away, an unstable transportation door opened, and Tolaen staggered out from it with fear.

Fortunately, he had prepared a teleportation spell long ago and dodged the attacks at the last moment. Otherwise, it would have been way too shameful for him to be heavily damaged before the fight even began.

"Shameless! Firing at me without saying anything at all!" Tolaen was both shocked and furious.

Who in the world would not even give any face at all in the event of a visit or request to spar between two Beyond Grade As‽

Even though I did indeed come to challenge you, isn't it too ill-mannered for you to start firing at me immediately without even saying a word‽

To him, even if the two Beyond Grade As had beef with each other and one went to challenge the other, they would at least be polite to each other on the surface.

We're all very important people with reputations to uphold. How can you just blast me away like that‽ What happened to the courtesy between Beyond Grade As‽ I'm not the only one that'll lose face for this, you will too!

At this time, Hila's voice appeared on the public channel.

"You've lost to me. Those I surpass will never have the chance to catch up. I have no interest in fighting you again."

Tolaen was instantly enraged by what Hila said. He thought he was arrogant enough, but Hila was even more arrogant than him.

After his expression changed a few times, he decided to put up with it for the time being.

"Humph, I have a mission to do, so I won't argue with you. You're already a dead woman anyway."

Tolaen snorted in his mind before activating a magical communication rune to contact his teammates who had set up an ambush somewhere else.

"Guys, our judgment was wrong. Hila did not accept the challenge and fall for the trap. She even shamelessly ordered her fleet to attack me instantly. The plan to lure her away won't work. Let's carry out a forced attack. At least we now know for sure that she's in the stronghold."

Very soon, Sagman's reply came through the magical communication rune.

"Okay, change of plan, start the forced attack! Tolaen, share your vision with us. Taylor, open the teleportation gate and attack the stargate. Also, prestart the spacetime stabilization device. Make sure that Hila has nowhere to run after we arrive and that everything goes according to plan."

Hila went all the way to the command room of the stronghold and looked at the image on the surveillance screen, where Tolaen was barely dodging the attacks from her fleet.

"Still not leaving, he must be up to something."

Hila frowned slightly, hesitated for a moment, and took out the communicator to send Han Xiao a message. She wanted to discuss this with Han Xiao.

However, the next moment, she intuitively felt an extremely strong sense of danger, piercing deep into her back and almost freezing her bones.

Hila's expression changed slightly as she looked up. She sensed a few Fixed Star sized energy sources suddenly appear nearby.

"Alarm! Alarm! High energy source detected!"

"Alarm! Alarm! Stargate is being attacked. Requesting reinforcements!"

The image on the screen changed, showing a magical teleportation gate suddenly appearing beside the stargate station afar and two people walking out of it. It was Taylor and Sagman.

The two of them started attacking immediately before the defense fleet could launch emergency fire. Tons of summoned monsters swarmed out and restrained the defense fleet, while countless arcane beams and shockwaves destroyed one stargate. The surprise attack was effective.

Beside Tolaen, another enormous teleportation gate appeared, and mechanical troops flowed out like a tide, quickly spreading out. The three at the front were Kasuyi's doppelganger, 'Desolate Beast' Mercer, and 'Mechanical Catastrophe' Francisco's Lord's Avatar, who was controlling this mechanical army.

Kasuyi and Mercer had known each other for a very long time, while Francisco was a direct member of the Arcane Church. His situation was rather unique, as his main body had always been serving a sentence in the Arcane Church's prison and was not usually allowed to go anywhere. The Arcane Church would only let him join battles using his Lord's Avatar when they needed his power, and the contributions he made would shorten his sentence.

His crime was related to his nickname, Mechanical Catastrophe. He had once caused a catastrophe that was machinery related. At the same time, this nickname was also a recognition of his strength. He was a Mechanic of the Energy Branch who had special talents. The cost of enhancing his machinery using his Mechanical Force was drastically lower than Mechanics of the same Grade, and the range of it was much larger. This meant that he could enhance a much larger army of machines compared to others.

Mechanical Catastrophe Francisco was there to deal with the fleet of the army stronghold, as well as to restrain Black Star's mechanical army that was stationed there. Otherwise, the few Beyond Grade As would have to waste a lot of energy dealing with the fleets.

As soon as he arrived, Mechanical Catastrophe immediately started controlling his mechanical army to clash with the fleet of this stronghold.

With the sudden arrival of enemies, the stronghold fleet's response was late for some time but quickly adjusted. The battle instantly entered the climax.

Mechanical Catastrophe's army also brought along several spacetime stabilization devices, wormhole restriction devices, and so on. They were all activated, stabilizing the spacetime of this area. Even teleportation spells could no longer be used.

Seeing this, Hila's expression became grave.

The enemies were well prepared, six Beyond Grade As including powerful ones like Kasuyi…

Do they want to kill me this much?

Despite how proud Hila was, her heart still shivered for a second.

Is this what Black Star faced back then?

No, this might be worse. It's almost a certain death situation.

However, her mindset was only shaken for an instant before she suppressed the negative emotions and turned them into the fighting will, making her feel as if all the blood in her body was boiling.

Boom!

The next second, Hila tore the ceiling open and flew right into the sky. She clenched her teeth and charged toward the few Beyond Grade As in outer space who were locking on to her.

During the charge, she released death energy continuously, which turned into a bright red cloud.

Seeing this, Red Devil, Desolate Beast, and Mechanical Catastrophe's Lord's Avatar dove down at the same time, quickly got past the defense fleet that was restrained, and clashed with Hila.

Boom!

A circle of red shockwaves exploded!

The scarlet cloud formed by death energy dissipated, and the red meteor fell toward the ground at an even greater speed than before.

Boom!

After crashing large areas of bases and leaving a rift-like trail behind, Hila was finally able to stop herself. Her surroundings were filled with dust.

"Ahem…"

Hila helped herself up with a fierce look in her eyes, casually wiped away the blood dripping from her nose, and stared at the three people in the sky.

Clearly, she could not fight the three of them head-on and was blasted away immediately.

At this time, a black tide rose into the sky not far from the stronghold and quickly approached. It was the mechanical army Han Xiao had placed there, and at the front was his Lord's Avatar.

However, the next instant, an ethereal voice appeared in everyone's mind.

"Black Star, your opponent is me."

With a flash of light, Kasuyi's doppelganger stood in the path of Han Xiao's mechanical army. He raised one hand and flipped it so that his palm was facing down.

Boom!

All the mechanical troops were instantly pressed onto the ground. Only the Lord's Avatar was still standing, surrounded by bright Mechanical Force, barely hanging on.

"Although these are machines and mental attacks that I'm best at won't be effective, I'm quite good at Psychic control too," Kasuyi's doppelganger said with a calm tone. He raised his hand and pushed forward.

A psychic wall appeared across thousands of miles and charged forward. All the buildings and machinery in its path were pushed away and pressed against it.

Some of the mechanical troops tried to attack the invisible psychic wall, but it was as if Kasuyi's energy was infinite. Even though cracks kept showing up on the wall under the attacks, he easily patched them up in no time.

The advance of the psychic wall seemed unstoppable. It wiped away a large area of the planet surface like an eraser. Countless pieces of debris from buildings and machines were pushed away from the planet's surface and into outer space.

Other than the Lord's Avatar and some highly mobile mechanical soldiers that backed away, the rest of the mechanical army were all pushed off the planet and away from the battlefield, only able to form a formation again in the cosmic space.

At the same time, Kasuyi's avatar followed them over and stopped in front of Han Xiao.

"Such powerful psychic powers." Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar's eyes sparkled.

"I can absorb energy from the Void Dimension, so my Psychic energy is infinite. In terms of energy volume, only the Federation of Light's Oulou might be able to match up to me," Kasuyi said coldly. "I heard you have the blood of the Void Race too. When your God's Trait Transformation reaches a certain point, you might awaken a power like this."

Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar looked around at the entire battlefield.

At this point, the planet stronghold could be divided into three battlefields.

First, there was Hila fighting Red Devil, Desolate Beast, and Mechanical Catastrophe, in which she was completely overpowered. It was too difficult for Hila to fight three of them at the same time, and she looked like she could be defeated and killed at any moment. However, Han Xiao knew what she was capable of. Although Hila would not be able to beat the three of them, she would be able to hold on for a short period. After all, her life-steal ability was quite powerful. Plus, her ability to reduce the enemy's lifespan would make the three of them fight more carefully and not dare to exchange blows.

Second was the large-scale army battle between the mechanical army controlled by Mechanical Catastrophe and the defense fleet of the stronghold. It was a very intense battle. The defense fleet's goal was to help Hila, while the Mechanical Catastrophe's army's goal was to restrain them.

The third and the last battlefield was Sagman and Taylor attacking the stargate stations to cut off Hila's path of escape and prevent reinforcements from arriving. When the two of them destroyed all the stargates, they would join the fight against Hila, and Hila would not be able to hold on any longer.

Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar wanted to stop the two of them, but the distance between the stargate and the stronghold planet was quite far, so he could not make it.

Furthermore, with the mechanical army he had there, he might not even be able to break away from Kasuyi. His largest mechanical army and the Apostle Weapons were all with his main body and were rushing there, but they would take some time to arrive.

This isn't looking very good… Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and looked at Kasuyi.

"Are you sure you want to keep me here?"

With an expressionless face, Kasuyi sent Han Xiao a unidirectional psychic message, saying slowly, "This Lord's Avatar of yours has to stay here with me."

He emphasized the words 'Lord's Avatar'.

Han Xiao observed Kasuyi's emotions. Suddenly, he had an idea. He controlled his Lord's Avatar and his mechanical army and charged toward Kasuyi.

Kasuyi was a Psychic, but not only did he not back off, he instead charged toward the Lord's Avatar and fought with it at melee range. The battle was very 'intense'. It looked like they had very deeply rooted hatred for each other.

The mechanical army around fired nonstop, which looked very accurate but actually barely hit Kasuyi at all.

Kasuyi did not stop this from happening and let these attacks land on the battlefield between Hila and three enemies behind him, occasionally stopping their attacks, forcing them to dodge and give Hila more chances.

At the same time, the mechanical army spread out, trying to get past Kasuyi. Kasuyi symbolically controlled his psychic wall to stop them, but the strength of it at some places was visibly weakened and was easily torn apart as the mechanical soldiers passed through the wall.

It looked like Kasuyi's doppelganger was forced to fight Black Star at close range and could not maintain his psychic wall at full power, leading to some of Black Star's mechanical army breaking away and heading in Hila's direction.

Han Xiao finally confirmed that this guy was deliberately doing this.

Why is he helping me?

Han Xiao suddenly had a flash of insight and softly whispered the code words in the unidirectional mind link.

"Meeting of the Gods? Acting?"

"Focus, acting."

Han Xiao immediately felt assured.

Damn, the opponent's boss is an actor!

He had already requested reinforcements from the dynasty. Although the stargates at the stronghold might be destroyed, the dynasty's reinforcements could still go to the nearest stargate. They would not be able to arrive right away, but it would not take too much longer.

The church has made its move, so there might be others waiting for an opportunity. I shall wait for the reinforcements and my main body to arrive first, Han Xiao thought.

With Kasuyi's 'help', some of the mechanical army successfully arrived at Hila's battlefield to support her. Once enhanced with Han Xiao's Mechanical Force, these mechanical soldiers were very powerful. Despite their low quantity, Tolaen and the others could not ignore them.

With help having arrived, Hila was relieved. The situation became much better, and she did not have to fight solely on her own anymore.

Her death energy, which had the ability to reduce one's life span, made Tolaen and Mercer very afraid. Usually, they were both tank-type fighters, but Mechanical Catastrophe's Lord's Avatar was the one taking on the role of the tank.

The fragile mechanical body had to endure pressure that was not supposed to be bestowed on this class. 'Mechanical Catastrophe' Francisco was completely speechless seeing how these two muscular men, Tolaen and Mercer, fought so cowardly.

Come on guys, try harder! I'm not Black Star. My Lord's Avatar isn't that tanky, okay‽

"Sh*t, Kasuyi's letting enemies pass on his side. Is Black Star's avatar so tough to deal with?" Mercer was surprised.

"After all, it's Kasuyi's doppelganger that's here, and he just used a powerful attack earlier to divide the battlefield, so it's normal for him not to be at full power." Francisco's tone was calm. "What's surprising is how strong Black Star is. Not only is he fighting Kasuyi head-on, but he's still able to use Virtual Intrusion on my troops at the same time."

On the other side, just as 'Red Devil' Tolaen was about to speak, his shield was suddenly shattered by cannon fire, and he was hit by one of Hila's death energy shockwaves.

Tolaen could not help but look at Kasuyi far away, who was in the middle of an 'intense battle', then complained in his mind, My life span's been shortened again…

"W-what's going on‽"

In the fleet outside the stronghold, the army players inside the battleships were stupefied by this sudden event.

Although many players had already formed or joined guilds and were moving in the free competition zone as subsidiary organizations, there were also some players who chose to move along with the main fleet of the army.

Due to the faction war order that the army had recently announced, many players had gathered in this stronghold at the frontlines and chosen this to be their temporary main city to form teams and pursue the players of enemy factions.

Unexpectedly, while they were enjoying their time in the stronghold, this place was suddenly attacked by multiple Beyond Grade As and became a battlefield of eight Beyond Grade As!

What's going on? Aren't Beyond Grade A all very difficult to see?

Have we… run into another huge event‽

Many players thought of the Planet Lighthouse event in the previous version and quickly started to record the battle, trying their best to capture the Beyond Grade As.

"This might be a huge event of this version! We're here to witness it!"

"Quickly, record it. I have a feeling that this will lead to something big!"

Many players had their fill of being rubberneckers and were very excited.

Hasty footsteps came closer and closer.

Bang!

The gate of the reception room was rammed open. Ames, Silver Shadow, and Feidin, who were chattering in the room, looked toward the gate. It was Aurora, who quickly ran in with an anxious expression.

"Teacher, bad news!"

"What happened?" Ames asked.

"My… my sister is being attacked by the Arcane Church. They've sent many Beyond Grade As to kill her. I saw it through our mental link!"

"What‽"

Ames immediately stood up. Her Force Field erupted and blew away the furniture around her.

After training together for more than a decade, she already had a strong bond with Hila. Once she heard that her student was in a dire situation, Ames was enraged.

At this time, a virtual screen appeared in the room. It was a call from a management officer.

"Your Excellency Ames, Your Excellency Feidin, there's a situation. A Beyond Grade A has arrived at Black Star Palace. He calls himself the Traveler, and he has challenged the Army Commander by name. How should we deal with this?"

"Tell him that His Excellency Black Star isn't here," Feidin replied.

"Er… he said that if Black Star isn't here, he'll fight his Lord's Avatar."

"Tell him, Black Star is very busy now and has no time to fight him."

"… Your Excellency Feidin, he said that he won't waste this trip here. If he can't fight Black Star, he can challenge Her Excellency Dragon Emperor too… He's refusing to leave. He's a Mage, so it'll be very difficult to chase him away without using special means."

Feidin frowned and was about to reply.

Ames patted his shoulder, interrupting him, and frowned. "This person did not come with friendly intentions. He probably has some ulterior motives, which might be related to what's happening to Hila. I'll test him. Tell him that I'll accept the challenge."

Hearing this, Silver Shadow, who had been silent, felt that this was a great opportunity to gain a favor—if he helped Black Star's family, he would probably benefit a ton from it.

He approached and said, "Your Excellency Ames, how about I take the challenge?"

"How can we let our guest help us in matters like this? Feidin, take Silver Shadow to the watchtower to observe the battle."

Ames waved and rejected him. She then turned around and walked out of the room with large strides, her skirt swaying like a black flower.

Her tall back disappeared from everyone's sights, only leaving her voice behind.

"Don't worry, I'm not that easy to deal with."

Chapter 1048: Movements

Outside Black Star Palace, Traveler crossed his legs in midair with his staff floating in front of him. He looked at the heavily guarded Black Star Palace from afar, and before him was the highly alert defense fleet.

Seeing this, Traveler's eyes narrowed slightly. "I've come at the right time."

According to the information provided by the Super Star Cluster alliance, Black Star was someone who loved accepting challenges. Yet, he was not coming out, not even sending out his Lord's Avatar to fight him. This meant that Sorokin's information was right. Hila was being attacked at this very moment, and Black Star had to protect her with his Lord's Avatar. He could not focus on too many fights at once.

Apostle Weapons and mechanical armies could fight multiple battles at the same time, but one could only descend onto one Lord's Avatar at a time.

"Black Star isn't even using his Apostle Weapons to fight me, so it looks like Sorokin guessed correctly. Black Star has taken his main army away and has been pretending to be in his base.

"Since Dragon Emperor will be the one accepting the challenge, I'll have to quickly deal with her and force Black Star to fight me. Even if he only sends a mechanical army to fight me, I'll still have achieved my goal and divided his attention."

In order to be done with the battle quickly, he had to use special tactics that would not be considered inside the perimeters of sparring. He would definitely offend Black Star by doing this.

However, Traveler did not care much about it. His relationship with some Super Star Cluster Civilizations was very special, exceeding the importance of his personal interests. On the surface, he was accepting a mission and doing his job. However, the truth was that as long as this would help the Civilization he belonged to, he would do everything in his power to succeed.

The Super Star Cluster alliance hoped that the church or the federation's mission would succeed. They wanted these Beyond Grade As to fight each other and did not want to see them united. The Beyond Grade As being united looked like it was problematic for the three Universal Civilizations but beneficial for the Super Star Clusters, but that depended on the timing of it. For now, this was not what the Super Star Cluster civilizations wanted to see.

In the eyes of the Super Star Cluster civilizations, Beyond Grade As were important tools they could make use of, but there were not enough Beyond Grade As in this era. Therefore, even if they were united, they had very limited value to these Super Star Cluster civilizations.

The Super Star Cluster alliance hoped to find a more suitable timing where the universe had more than enough Beyond Grade As. By then, they would even encourage and aid the Beyond Grade As to be united. Therefore, they did not want this opportunity to come this soon when the timing was not right.

Other than to balance the power dynamics, there was another reason the Super Star Cluster alliance wanted to do this—they were worried that if the Beyond Grade As became united too early, it would force the three Universal Civilizations to carry out another elimination, another 'Tragedy of the Pinnacles'. If and when that happened, the three Universal Civilizations would definitely deal with the outsiders first. Therefore, the allies of the Super Star Cluster alliance would be massacred with an excuse once again, and they would be the ones suffering from it.

Traveler silently waited for a while. Finally, Ames flew out from the base.

"You want to challenge Black Star? What's your motive?" Ames narrowed her eyes.

"It's nothing but respect for the strong. I want to challenge those standing at the peak. There's no motive to speak of." Traveler remained calm.

"You're related to what's happening to Hila, aren't you?"

"I don't understand what you're talking about." Traveler shook his head.

"Humph, chat sh*t."

A green light flashed past Ames' eyes, and a Force Field erupted from her body, grabbing onto numerous satellite tiles to bash onto Traveler.

Traveler remained calm and held his staff with both hands. Fog-like magic energy splashed out and turned into rune arrays of different sizes, fusing together and forming an enormous rune shield that looked as complex and exquisite as the mechanical parts of a mechanical watch, blocking the path of the satellite tiles.

Ka-cha!

Multiple satellites clashed onto the rune shield, creating cracks, but could not go further. At the same time, Ames extended her arm forward from afar, aimed at Traveler, and pulled heavily. A powerful force of absorption suddenly appeared and pulled Traveler toward her.

While being dragged through midair, energy sprayed out from Traveler's body as he stabilized himself. He then cast a string of powerful spells instantly. Multidimensional energy turned into spells that quickly dashed past where Ames was standing but missed.

With a space ripple, she had already changed her location using Void Hyperdrive and approached Traveler's back. She raised her brows, glared at Traveler's back, and shot a shockwave from between her brows.

The next second, Traveler's body was fixed in midair, and he could not move.

Force Field: Gaze of the Dragon!

The moment she locked the enemy's movements, Ames's long leg whipped horizontally, sending out a wave of Force Field right toward Traveler's back.

Force Field energy that was sent out from her own body was the most powerful, and she had condensed this wave of Force Field into a thin line, rendering it dangerously sharp. It looked like she used her leg to launch a blade shockwave.

Force Field: Sweeping Blade!

Swoosh!

The blade Force Field slashed right across and actually cut Traveler in two.

However, the next moment, the two halves of Traveler suddenly shrank and turned into mojo puppets, while further away, a small puppet that looked to be made of clay appeared out of nowhere and quickly shapeshifted into Traveler.

"Puppet Replacement Spell, a simple little trick," Traveler said calmly.

Ames, however, was slightly frowning. She had known Austin for a very long time and had some knowledge about magic.

The Puppet Replacement Spell was a little known spell of the Alchemy and Curse Branch, but it had a massive side effect. When reflected in the interface, every time someone cast the Puppet Replacement Spell, their health and energy would decrease by fifty percent, and all their attributes would also decrease by twenty percent. This was an extremely costly spell.

Due to its limited value, usually, only low-grade Mages would use it to save their own lives, while high Grade Mages had many defensive methods and would not use spells like this at all.

For example, a Beyond Grade A would have dozens of methods to dodge or block that attack earlier, and even getting hit by it would not be as horrible as the side effects of the Puppet Replacement Spell. Therefore, Ames felt that Traveler had done this for a reason.

As she observed more carefully, she realized that Traveler was strangely giving off a different vibe. He seemed to have a very faint creepy smile on his face, and she felt he became more corrupt and eviler.

"Tsk, Force Field Control is one of the most common Esper Abilities. It's very rare for someone to be able to become a Beyond Grade A with it. You're really talented in controlling your Esper Ability. One day, maybe you can improve this Esper Ability to its extreme form, the Super High Risk Esper Ability—Force Control. Although the difference is only one word, its meaning is a world of difference." As Traveler gave off a different vibe, he became more talkative too.

"Something's off." Ames became more cautious and alert. She clenched her fist, shattering a corner of a satellite tile, and then controlled the broken pieces to fly out like a meteor rain.

Force Field: Dragon's Breath Shooting Star Fist!

While using spells to block the attacks, Traveler was also observing a faint mark on the back of his hand. There was a faint purple evil glow inside his crystal yellow eyes.

"There's not enough life force. More is needed…"

The two of them fought intensely outside Black Star Palace. Traveler's way of fighting was extremely strange. He occasionally seemed to purposely get hit by Ames' attacks. Ames showed the multiple uses of Force Field, including restraining, explosions, and slashes.

While training with Hila around the universe, Ames had improved as well. She had better control of her Esper Ability.

While the two of them were fighting, Herlous, who was watching in the watchtower, secretly commanded the fleet to leave in different directions and form an enormous encirclement.

"Everyone focus," Herlous said with a deep voice. "Preheat the spacetime stabilization device. When I give the order, activate it and trap Traveler here."

When the matter involved their Deputy Army Commander, no one cared about nobility anymore. Even Ames did not want to fight Traveler by herself.

It did not matter whether this was a misunderstanding; it was best to deal with Traveler first. Ames' main goal in fighting him was to force all his attention on her so that the fleet would be able to deploy traps secretly, in case he opened a teleportation gate and escaped.

…

At the same time, the dynasty received Han Xiao's message and started moving instantly. The Beyond Grade As who were in the dynasty's territory received their missions, departed from their own territories, and headed toward the stargate stations.

Inside Kant's ship, the few Beyond Grade As who had gathered urgently this time were all discussing their mission.

"The church really doesn't learn. During the Planet Lighthouse battle more than twenty years ago, I… and Black Star taught them a lesson, and less than thirty years later, they're here causing trouble again." Beyoni curled his lips. A few fire sparkles jumped out between his teeth.

"This movement by them is very sudden. Their target is Hila, and we're the only ones close by. It's best for us to quickly head over." Kant was serious about the matter.

Most of the dynasty's allies were given territories in the Flickering World and were taking part in the free competition. They were too far away and would not make it in time.

Currently, the Beyond Grade As remaining in the dynasty's territory would be able to reach the battlefield the quickest, and they were Kant's Lord's Avatar; Ravenlaude, who was recovering from his injury; the slacker, Beyoni; and Kohler, who had nothing to do.

"I heard Kasuyi's doppelganger is there too. Isn't that a little dangerous?" Kohler whispered.

Kant's huge eyes glared at him and said, "Don't be such a coward. With me here, what's there to be afraid of? I can fight the entire church on my own!"

"Really?" Kohler's face was filled with doubts.

"Of course not, but can you just let me say it?" Kant rolled his eyes. "If I were that capable, even Clotti would be my follower."

Ravenlaude stayed silent with a conflicted expression.

Not long ago, he had been beaten up by Han Xiao, so he was not very willing to help.

However, the dynasty would give very generous rewards and merits for every reinforcement mission…

So…

Forget it, I heard the Black Star Army is in a dire situation this time. If I help him get through this, he'll owe me a favor. Then, I can ask Black Star to get me a Universal Treasure…

Having thought of this possibility, Ravenlaude was suddenly very motivated.

…

At the same time, after the dynasty had sent out the reinforcements, the upper echelons continued paying attention to this matter.

Inside the conference room of the political building on the dynasty's mother planet, Ruler Urranrell was watching the broadcast of the battle provided by the Black Star Army. Beside her were the remote projections of the dynasty's upper echelons, who were also watching silently. The atmosphere was very serious.

"The church has yet to give up, and they have now assaulted our ally once again." Urranrell looked around with a cold expression on her face. "What do you all think about this?"

The people exchanged looks. After a while, Bekorodi raised his hand and slowly said, "Your Excellency, according to the data, the church's target is Hila, and Hila isn't one of our Beyond Grade A allies."

"Hila is the Black Star Army's Deputy Army Commander, and the Black Star Army is our ally."

"But she has personally rejected joining the dynasty… Your Excellency, I suggest drawing a clear line. Matters involving Black Star and matters Hila should be treated differently. Now that Black Star has requested help personally, and we have agreed to help because of our agreement, this means that he's using the dynasty's power to benefit his own faction. My thoughts are that… we can help our allies, but we can't be used by them without any cost. Protecting Black Star is what we should do, but protecting a Beyond Grade A who isn't our ally? I think we need to bring up the terms and not provide support without any compensation." Bekorodi's reasoning was logical.

"So, what ideas do you have?" Urranrell frowned slightly.

"If Black Star only gets through this with our help, I think we need to make one demand—Hila has to join the dynasty. Of course, she can remain in the Black Star Army, but she has to be the dynasty's ally too."

"Hmm… makes sense." Urranrell pondered for a while. "What if Hila is killed?"

"It's a loss to the dynasty, but there are benefits to it too. If Hila dies, Black Star will undoubtedly be on the opposite side of the church, the Meeting of the Gods will basically be completely meaningless, and the Beyond Grade As won't be able to unite. This means that one threat is eliminated. At the same time, with a shared external enemy, it's beneficial to building a closer relationship between the dynasty and Black Star. His loyalty will be firmer. Therefore, whether the rescue ends up successful or not, it will be beneficial for the dynasty one way or the other," Bekorodi analyzed.

Many of the upper echelons nodded. Logically speaking, they felt that Bekorodi had analyzed it very well.

Urranrell did not express her stand on this issue. She tapped her fingers on the table, and seeing that no one else had anything to say, she said, "No matter what, provide full support to the Black Star Army first. We'll deal with the rest later."

"Understood."

The remote projections disappeared one after another.

Urranrell left the conference room, and 'Dark Lord' Clotti, who had been waiting outside the door, draped her coat over her and followed behind.

After walking for some time, Urranrell suddenly said, "Clotti, how likely do you think it is that Hila will survive this?"

"Very unlikely," Clotti said with a poker face.

"Even with the dynasty's help?"

"That's right."

"Why?"

"The federation won't watch and do nothing."

"How do you know that?"

"The Mechanic Emperor told me."

Urranrell had no response for that.

Okay, that's one powerful and good reason. I have nothing to say about it.

"Looks like the Mechanic Emperor takes the shared battlefront of Beyond Grade As very seriously."

Urranrell stopped in place and turned to look at Clotti.

"You're a Beyond Grade A, too. Don't you have any thoughts about this?"

"My identity as a member of the Crimson Dynasty comes first, the dynasty ruler's Guard Captain comes second, and the Beyond Grade A part comes only third," Clotti replied with a calm expression.

Urranrell shook her head and turned back around.

She stayed silent for a moment and then softly said, "You've spent too much time as my personal guard by my side. Go take a break from your job. Go out and kill a few Beyond Grade As before coming back. Don't let the universe forget the name of Dark Lord."

"Okay," Clotti replied calmly.

…

At the same time, in Beast Ancestor's stronghold…

"Hahaha, they've made their move as expected!"

Inside the palace, Gorutan laughed loudly. His lungs were so strong that his laughter formed almost solid sonic waves, causing the entire base to tremble.

Just now, he had heard from Sorokin that the information he had exposed had put Hila in a desperate situation.

As his plan succeeded and he got his revenge, Gorutan felt very satisfied.

Sorokin's manifestation stood before him with a smile on his face. "Your Excellency Beast Ancestor, your territory isn't far from the battlefield. Why not go watch it live?"

Hearing this, Gorutan's laughter stopped. His sharp eyes stared right at Sorokin as he said with rage, "Are you trying to trick me again?"

"I wouldn't dare." Sorokin quickly waved his hands.

"Humph." Gorutan snorted. He then lifted his specially made enormous alcohol glass and gulped it down. "No matter what, I'm going to stay here to wait for the news of Hila's death. I'm not going anywhere."

"Don't worry. I'm not trying to convince you to join the battle. The dynasty will have already sent reinforcements. If the dynasty's reinforcements arrive, Hila might be able to escape her doom. Therefore, rather than staying here and doing nothing, it's better to secretly provide some help."

"What kind of bright idea do you have then?"

"Hehe, according to my estimates, the church will prioritize destroying the stargate stations when attacking Black Star's stronghold, activate spacetime stabilization devices, and eliminate Hila's path of retreat. Therefore, if the dynasty reinforcements want to come, they can only use the nearby stargate… Your Excellency Beast Ancestor, if the nearby stargate stations are turned off or destroyed, the dynasty's reinforcements will have to take a detour. This way, Hila will have to remain alone for an even longer time, and the possibility of the plan succeeding will increase drastically."

A flash of light appeared in Gorutan's eyes. He put down the glass and said, "Hmm, what you're saying does make sense…"

Sorokin smiled faintly.

…

In the Primeval Star River, Manison slowly opened his eyes and sent a message in the encoded secret communication channel.

"Mornisa, have you guys departed?"

"Teacher, the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device has already started preheating. We can depart any time."

"Okay."

Manison nodded, swapped the channel, and spoke to his Apostle Weapon team.

"Keep your eyes on Beast Ancestor. He might make a move. No matter what he wants to do, stop him."

"Understood."

After a few more orders, Manison closed his eyes again and softly murmured, "Black Star, that's all the help I'll give you today. Don't disappoint me."

Chapter 1049: Cultural Talent

Boom!

Like a crimson tsunami, the death energy swept across the ground and clashed with an energy shield, creating countless electrical sparks.

'Mechanical Catastrophe' Francisco's Lord's Avatar opened his arms to maintain the shield against the death energy. All the patterns on his mechanical body were glowing with psionic light, and the thruster on his back was working at full capacity, shooting out six deep blue flame trails. But he still could not stop himself from moving backward.

He turned around and saw that 'Red Devil' Tolaen and 'Desolate Beast' Mercer were hiding behind his shield while occasionally shooting ranged Shockwave Blasts or spells, then quickly running back behind him right after. Francisco was infuriated.

You guys are the melee warriors, yet you hide behind me?

Are you two using me as a cover?

Stop messing about!

Francisco was very annoyed.

The battle had already lasted for quite some time. The situation in the various battlefields had all changed. Black Star and Kasuyi were still having an 'intense battle', and mechanical soldiers continued to 'penetrate' Kasuyi's defenses to help Hila.

As Hila gained more help, she could focus more on her attacks, which led to Tolaen and Mercer acting more cautiously. Originally, the three of them had the firm upper hand, but now, the situation had shockingly started to move toward a stalemate. The main reason for that was the mechanical soldiers that Kasuyi let past. They were enhanced by Black Star's Mechanical Force, so they were quite powerful and made the battlefield very chaotic.

The fleet battlefield in outer space was not looking too good as well. The mechanical army controlled by Francisco was being attacked by Han Xiao's Virtual Intrusion, so mechanical soldiers were turning into traitors here and there, fighting their ex-teammates. This led to part of the fleet being able to provide help to Hila using ranged attacks, further diverting the energy of Mechanical Catastrophe and the other two.

'Mechanical Catastrophe' Francisco had to be the one dealing the damage, taking the damage, restraining the fleet, and even guarding his army on the virtual field, all at the same time…

My life is so difficult. I can't even serve my sentence in peace!

Only Sagman's side could give him some comfort, as they were almost done destroying all the stargates.

When the two of them are done, they'll be able to come over and help. Then, the stalemate will be broken, and Hila will be completely overpowered, doomed to die! Francisco thought.

He knew that the Arcane Church had given Taylor a special trump card secretly that would be able to restrict Hila's movements. According to the plan, when the five of them gathered, they would use it to launch a lethal attack on Hila.

This trump card was a few one-time use magic scrolls that stored extremely powerful church special forbidden spells, fused with the powers of Divine Spells.

Among them, the strongest was [Forbidden Spell—Wailing Nun's Embrace]. This forbidden spell normally needed multiple people to use it together and took a long time to activate, but it could be activated instantly when stored in a magic scroll.

The Arcane Church once had a stage where their Mages were blooming, so there were many Beyond Grade A forbidden spell scrolls that got passed down. This scroll had been created by four Beyond Grade A Mages. One of them was even a peak Beyond Grade A Mage, so the strength of this spell was extremely high.

Only Taylor, Sagman, and Francisco knew about these scrolls; the rest had no idea, even Kasuyi. The Arcane Church knew Kasuyi's personality very well, that he was not willing to bully a new Beyond Grade A with so many teammates. If he knew that the church planned to use this kind of one-time mass destructive weapon, it might lead to something unpredictable. Therefore, the church did not tell him about it, and their request to Kasuyi was only to stop Black Star's Lord's Avatar.

As for why only Taylor, Sagman, and Francisco knew, it was because the three of them were the most trustworthy and shameless, so they would work together the best. Anyway, once they activated the scrolls, the other teammates would follow up with more attacks as well.

On the other side, Crimson Snake had already turned into combat mode and shrouded Hila's face. She swiftly moved around the battlefield, shooting out death energy while trying to hide her anxiety.

She understood her situation. Although she could last some time against the three enemies with the help of the mechanical army, she knew that this stalemate would be broken very soon. As soon as Sagman and Taylor joined the battle, she would not be able to last for sure.

If I don't do anything, it'll just be a slow death.

Although Han Xiao had sent a message to her earlier saying that his main body was on the way, due to her personality, Hila did not expect to rely on others in times of despair. Instead, she would do her best to save herself.

The reinforcements have yet to arrive, my means of retreat has been cut off, and there are two other powerful enemies who will soon join the battle. In order to survive, I have to hold on while facing the attacks of five of them. That's a desperate situation even with the help of the mechanical army and the fleet. I'll have to rely on myself one way or another. What other trump cards do I have here?

Hila remained calm and quickly thought about how to resolve this situation.

Ideas were born and filtered out one after another. Very soon, there was only one idea left in her mind.

I'll have to do my best to try this…

Hila clenched her teeth.

…

An enormous beam penetrated the last stargate station. Debris flew everywhere, and shockwaves from the explosion made the shields of the defense fleet nearby flicker.

"The stargate stations have been destroyed, let's go!"

Sagman did not hesitate. He quickly turned into a mass of bright, golden light, which shrouded Taylor, and instantly sped up, turning into a stream of light and leaving the battlefield, heading right toward Hila.

As they knew that the spacetime stabilization device would be activated, they knew that summoning type spells would be affected too. Taylor had made preparations in advance; he had prepared a ton of summoning scrolls, which he started tearing open right after the teleportation gate appeared, forming an army of summoned creatures. Taylor himself, however, swapped from summoning style to artillery style to adapt to the environment.

He was good at summoning spells, but that did not mean he did not learn other types of spells. He was just not as good at those in comparison.

A Beyond Grade A would have multiple combat styles. This was especially true among Mages, who were known for their versatility. No matter what style they were good at usually, they could all switch to a different style when needed.

With Kasuyi holding back, a small number of mechanical soldiers were also let past, trying to stop the two of them.

However, Sagman was extremely mobile in light form. He made countless turns to avoid fighting the mechanical soldiers head-on, showing how experienced he was. Luckily, Taylor was a Beyond Grade A as well, or he would have been vomiting his guts out.

Sagman's Esper Ability was related to light energy, so his turning speed was extremely fast. He went in a huge circle to get rid of the mechanical troops and entered Hila's battlefield, floating in midair above the planet.

"You guys are finally here. Quickly, help!"

Francisco was done with his teammates and was exhilarated to see help arrive.

Sagman and Taylor exchanged looks and saw what each other meant.

Create an opportunity to use the forbidden spell scrolls!

The two of them joined the battle without saying anything.

Light energy shockwaves and magic spells were thrown out like they were free, exploding everywhere.

Boom!

The sound of explosions never stopped. Mechanical soldiers were being destroyed one after another. Hila was in a dire situation once again, so much so that she had to stop all her attacks and focus on defending herself.

After the two of them joined the battle, it became completely one-sided.

…

At the same time, Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar scanned through the difficult situation Hila was in. He then said in the chat window with Kasuyi exclusively, "Hila won't be able to fight against five of them. Stop blocking me and let me past."

"How do you want to act that out?" Kasuyi replied.

"Give me a powerful hit, throwing my Lord's Avatar and part of my mechanical army over."

"The church wants me to stall you. I can't possibly throw you into that battlefield. Plus, if you join that battle, I'll have to follow too, and then, I'll have to fight Hila as well. She'll be in an even more dangerous situation." Kasuyi shook his head slightly.

The acting was one thing, but he did not want to offend the church. No matter how much he was holding back, there was no way he could make it this obvious.

"How about… you use a large attack when you're in a dire situation, and that stops your teammates' attacks? Just say it's collateral damage."

"I have complete control over my psychic power. There's zero chance something like that would happen."

"Then… might as well let me destroy this doppelganger of yours. That's the easiest way."

"No, not mentioning whether your Lord's Avatar has the ability to defeat my doppelganger, I have to stay here to prevent accidents. That old man, Mechanic Emperor, said the federation wants to make a move. I'll have to act like I'm fighting with them for Hila to keep some of them busy."

Han Xiao did not even know what to say.

What's the courtesy of an actor? This is!

You're so passionate about your job that even the church would be touched!

"No this, no that, what should we do then?"

"The federation might appear at any moment. When they do, I'll turn to fight them, and her situation won't be so dangerous. If Hila can still hold on for now, it's best to wait for the change that's certainly going to come," Kasuyi said.

"I'll have to think about it…" Han Xiao pondered.

While these two actors were going through their script together, a change suddenly happened!

Swoosh!

Under the nonstop attacks of five enemies, Hila finally showed a flaw. 'Mechanical Catastrophe' Francisco captured the opportunity, clapped his hands, and released an extremely condensed plasma electromagnetic field that passed through the gaps between the death energy.

Buzz!

Electric sparkles appeared all over Hila's body, and her movements showed even more flaws.

Sagman and Francisco then continued throwing out more powerful controlling abilities to restrain her.

"Weird. Ever since we joined the battle, she's seemed less focused…"

This doubt flashed through Sagman's mind. Before he had time to think about it carefully, he yelled at Taylor in the mind communication channel, "Use the scrolls!"

"Ready long ago!"

Taylor tore open a white magical scroll with black words, the scroll then suddenly glowed extremely brightly.

Swoosh!

As if a prison was finally opened after a thousand years, countless white magical runes shot out from the scroll like wild dragons, all landing on Hila.

The next moment, the surface of Crimson Snake was crawling with eerie pale-white runes, which had an overall shape of a seductive woman. The woman-shaped pattern slowly opened its arms and did a hugging posture.

Buzz!

An unknown power appeared as Hila realized that she could not move her body. She was locked in midair. The boiling energy in her body quickly calmed down, and she was completely unable to move.

Forbidden Spell—Wailing Nun's Embrace!

"Focus fire!"

The duration of this scroll was limited. Sagman did not dare waste any more time. He yelled in the communication channel to tell everyone to use all their attacks and throw them at Hila.

Tolaen and Mercer responded instantly. Although they did not know what happened, they would not let such a good opportunity pass.

Boom!

Hila's silhouette was instantly buried by colorful energy explosions.

It looked beautiful, but it was extremely powerful as well!

Kasuyi's doppelganger suddenly turned around.

"A forbidden spell scroll‽"

The church hid this and did not tell me about it‽

Seeing this, he did not want to discuss the script any longer. His psychic energy grabbed onto the mechanical army, including Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar, and threw them to the battlefield Hila was in.

"Damn, what a decisive man."

Flying in midair, Han Xiao rushed toward Hila's position with the help of Kasuyi's push, but he was not in a hurry.

Kasuyi did not know much about Hila and thought Hila was in danger. However, Han Xiao knew that Hila had the ability to be able to 'revive' herself. This wave of focus fire looked powerful, but it could not kill Hila. It would only trigger her reviving ability.

However, if that's the case, I'll have to use the backup plan. Han Xiao frowned slightly.

If Hila's one-time reviving ability was not triggered, he would take more risks. Now, however, Han Xiao felt like he needed to change the plan.

However, before he arrived at the battlefield, a powerful life force energy erupted in Hila's location!

Wu!

The gold life energy shot into the sky like a fountain!

The liveliness of this energy startled everyone.

Sagman and the other four suddenly realized, although they had been dealing heavy damage to Hila all this time, those injuries seemed to have recovered within seconds!

With the effect of the forbidden spell ending, Hila escaped. Crimson Snake was already worn out, showing large portions of her sky that was covered in opened wounds with visible flesh.

However, with vital energy regenerating her body, those open wounds closed in the blink of an eye, not even leaving any scars, turning back to her smooth skin.

Sagman and the others' eyes widened as they were astounded.

Impossible!

Such a powerful regenerative ability…

Why does she have this kind of power?

Also, why does this look familiar?

The next moment, everyone turned around and looked at Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar with a shocked expression.

Isn't this… Black Star's ability‽

Why does Hila have it too?

In terms of the similarities between the two of them…

Could this be the people of Planet Aquamarine's cultural talent‽

This time, Kasuyi's voice appeared.

"Black Star, are you people of the Planet Aquamarine… all unkillable?"

"That's really not true. We don't have that kind of talent…" Han Xiao smiled awkwardly.

If his main body was there instead of his Lord's Avatar, he would probably have taken a very deep breath.

What Hila did was successfully building a vital link with Aurora. How else could so much vital energy erupt out of nowhere‽

Being able to obtain a new ability during battle, sis, are you a protagonist type character too?

That doesn't make sense. You're supposed to be on the evil side.

With this vital link activated, Hila became drastically stronger. Her basic combat capability did not increase, but she basically had an extremely powerful healer with her at all times. As long as Aurora still had stamina, Hila's regeneration ability would be terrifying!

Han Xiao's heart was hurting so badly he almost wanted to report this to the officials.

I thought I was powerful enough, but I never expected you to cheat!

If Hila had this 'external software' in his previous life… Han Xiao could not even imagine what would have happened.

Sadly, before Hila's cheat finished installing in his previous life, the Germinal Organization's leader had already destroyed it.

"Again!"

Hila's will to fight was boiling.

Currently, Aurora was already able to fight along her side in this way, which helped her escape lethal danger. Hila's mindset was different from before; she did not reject Aurora using her abilities to help her.

Beyond Grade As needed more vital energy to regenerate, but Aurora was now a Calamity Grade as well, so she was more than able to be Hila's healer.

Hearing Hila's yelling, Sagman and the other four were hesitant as to whether they should continue fighting Hila.

Han Xiao, however, stopped in midair and did not continue approaching. Kasuyi was watching from afar as well.

Everyone stopped doing what they were doing and exchanged looks. The situation became awkward.

However, everyone suddenly felt something and looked over in that direction.

Buzz!

Not far from the stronghold, a Federation of Light fleet penetrated the limitations of the spacetime stabilization device and suddenly appeared on the battlefield.

At the front of the fleet, seven Beyond Grade As stood in a row, looking at everyone there.

Kasuyi looked up and said calmly, "They're here."

Chapter 1050: Oscar Winner

At Black Star Palace, the battle between Ames and Traveler was reaching the climax.

Under the Force Field, the satellite tiles shattered Traveler's magic shield time after time like enormous fists, slapping him around everywhere like he was a baseball.

It looked like Ames had the complete upper hand and was totally overpowering Traveler, but not only was she not relieved, she was even more cautious.

There was a reason Traveler was getting beaten this badly—for unknown reasons, he used the Puppet Replacement Spell multiple times, decreasing his attributes, health, and energy time after time. It was like he was looking to be tortured.

At the same time, that uncomfortable evil vibe he was giving off gradually became stronger too.

"I can't keep doing this." Ames looked at the base far away and nodded.

The officers in the watchtower saw this action of hers, which was a hint to activate the spacetime stabilization device to cut off Traveler's path of retreat.

Herlous instantly gave the order.

"Ambush team in position. Everyone, activate…"

Before he finished, the situation suddenly changed! A purple and green energy wave as thick as flowing liquid erupted from Traveler's body. It had suction cups and looked like the tentacles of an octopus. It also looked like a boiling and bubbling potion that kept expanding.

The energy condensed into almost solidified translucent green and purple energy tentacles. Instead of saying that Traveler released them, it was more like these energy tentacles tore Traveler's body open and forced their way out!

Ames did not have a habit of waiting for someone to finish transforming. Without saying a word, she focused her Force Field once again.

Circular Force Fields spun around her like small tornados, quickly turning into the shape of drills. They then stopped for an instant before rocketing toward Traveler.

However, the next moment, the purple-green energy on Traveler's body moved and covered Traveler completely, forming a coating around him. The Force Field landed on it but was shockingly not able to penetrate it, only pushing him back slightly.

"Hahaha. Useless useless useless!"

Traveler laughed maniacally like he was a different person, giving off an indescribable sense of evil from all over his body.

Tons of army soldiers felt their legs tremble just by looking at him… In the interface terms, all of them had undergone a will judgment.

Ames kept attacking, but the purple-green energy around Traveler was extremely tough and blocked all her attacks. It was unknown what kind of energy this was.

At this time, Traveler suddenly held both his hands up, and a strong sense of passion appeared in his eyes.

"This powerful person here is the sacrifice I, your husband, have given to you. Answer my call, my lovely wife!"

Boom!

The energy around his body suddenly bloomed and spread out like it was infinite, painting the black cosmic space purple and green.

The properties of this area changed in this instant.

"Alert! Alert! Spacetime coefficient is fluctuating drastically. The wave peak has exceeded the reality safety line!"

"Spacetime stabilization device overloading… Alert! Stabilization anchor broken! Stabilization failed. Requesting more spacetime stabilization devices!"

"Analyzing event model… Analysis complete. 100% match. Event: Advent of a secondary dimension!"

If the spacetime was a piece of paper, the spacetime coefficient would be the extent to which this piece of paper was folded. The more stable it was, the neater and flatter this piece of paper would be. At this moment, this piece of paper was crushed into a ball, and another piece of paper representing a secondary dimension was wrapped around it.

Secondary dimensions were dangerous yet amazing. They were all born due to various reasons. If they appeared in the main universe, they would change the spacetime properties of a certain area and turn it into the secondary dimension. Most of the time, this would be a disaster.

Han Xiao had once seen an item called the Shadow Lantern in the dynasty. Its core was the fragment of the Shadow Dimension, and it could summon the Shadow Dimension. What Traveler was doing now was similar to that.

This evil filled secondary dimension gradually expanded outside Black Star Palace. Ames and the various fleets were all inside this dimension as if they were swallowed into its stomach.

Countless energy tentacles extended and appeared out of nowhere, each one at least a hundred thousand meters long, flapping and moving around randomly. The fleets' formations were immediately broken, and their shields were attacked continuously.

Ames frowned as she controlled her Force Field to keep shattering one tentacle after another. However, new tentacles appeared in this secondary dimension like there was no end to them. Seeing this, she had no choice but to keep aiming her Force Field at Traveler himself.

Boom!

Traveler did not even dodge. He just hovered in the same place and kept waving his hand that had the purple mark on it. Following the movements of his hand, purple green energy tides appeared out of nowhere like it was infinite, easily shattering Ames's Force Field attacks.

"I once lost to Oulou and witnessed his terrifying abilities, which motivated me to take the path of searching for secondary dimensions." Purple and green patterns extended on Traveler's face as he became more and more excited. He laughed like a lunatic and said, "Eventually, I found a new power! Let me introduce you. This secondary dimension is called Evil Convergence. It's my wife! Inside its body, I can absorb an infinite amount of energy! Call Black Star out. You're no match for me!"

"You haven't beaten me yet."

Ames narrowed her eyes slightly.

Traveler looked around and saw that countless fleets were rising from the Black Star Palace to deploy more spacetime stabilization anchors around.

Seeing this, he did not care and smiled coldly.

After causing such a big fuss, Black Star would definitely have to do something. He had already achieved his initial goal. All that was left was when would Black Star come.

However, he had to add more flames and give Black Star more pressure.

Having thought of that, Traveler looked at Ames and licked his lips.

"I shall chew you up into pieces first then."

In the Emerald Star Cluster, the arrival of the Federation of Light attracted the attention of everyone present. They all stopped moving with different looks on their faces.

There were six Beyond Grade As who appeared there, while 'Defender' Romo, who was providing ranged support, did not come.

"One, two… six Beyond Grade As."

Hila's heart sank. The excitement from creating a vital link that ignored distance quickly dissipated.

If all those people were there to kill her, she felt that there was no way she would survive.

Aurora's stamina was limited; it would run out sooner or later. With so many Beyond Grade As working together, they would be able to kill her countless times over.

To her, no matter how strong her regeneration ability was, being killed was just a matter of time. Furthermore, regenerating fast did not mean that she would not be captured by the enemies.

"Sis…" Aurora's anxious call came through the mind link.

Hila felt the vital energy that kept flowing out in her body. The sharp look in her eyes gradually softened as she subconsciously turned to look at Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar floating in midair.

When she was surrounded earlier, she had analyzed the situation and felt that the only way to survive was to successfully link with Aurora. Hence, she had diverted her attention during the battle to keep trying to build a link with Aurora.

Whether it was her potential exploding in a time of life or death or some other unknown reason, that obstructing secondary dimension gradually stopped absorbing the vital energy. With this obstacle gone, the link between the two of them was built smoothly, and Aurora could finally share her energy with Hila through the blood and soul connection between them.

While everyone was observing the situation, the federation's fleet moved.

A ton of unmanned spaceships and mechanical troops headed to attack the defense fleet of the planet stronghold, while the other spaceships quickly changed formation. The engineering ships came to the edge of the formation and released arc-shaped machinery that connected with each other, starting to assemble the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device.

The six Beyond Grade As of the federation quickly approached the battlefield Hila was in. Sierron crossed his four arms and looked down at Hila, Sagman, and the rest from above.

"Looks like we arrived at just the right time," he said coldly.

Kasuyi's doppelganger slowly flew over. "The federation is going to be involved in this too?"

"Humph, you people of the church really are useless. You still haven't killed Hila," Sierron said coldly.

"Since the federation is here, I suppose you have the same goal as us. Why not work together to kill Hila?" Sagman said with a deep voice. "She has just exposed that she has a similar regeneration power to Black Star. We will only have a higher chance of killing her by working together."

Hades suddenly said, "Okay, since everyone's goal is the same, let's form an alliance."

Sierron paused, thought about it for a second, and did not explain their true goal.

There were quite a number of people from the church as well; it was not a suitable time to show all his cards. Working together was the best choice.

Hearing this, Sagman and the others were overjoyed, but Hila's heart sank.

Looks like today is the day I die.

This time, Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar landed beside her and stood by her side. He took out a compressed orb for a new Crimson Snake, instantly expanded it out, and helped Hila change her mechanical suit.

Hila turned and looked at him, hesitated for a moment, and said softly in their communication channel, "Black Star, if I die today, take care of my sister for me."

"You won't die today." Han Xiao shook his head.

"You don't have to comfort me. There are ten or so Beyond Grade As here… This is more terrifying than what you faced back then. You won't be able to save me even if you come in person… Don't bring your original body here. Go, don't save me. You'll be in danger too."

"You won't know till you try it," Han Xiao replied.

Hila shook her head, paused, and said softly, "I owe you too much. You've been taking care of us all these years. I really appreciate you a lot."

Han Xiao looked at her. "Why are you suddenly saying your will? It's not like you."

"Hehe, don't worry, I won't give up resisting. Even if I die, I'll hurt my enemies as much as possible. I've always been chasing after your shadow, and before I die, I can finally fight alongside you. I'm already satisfied."

Hila subconsciously reached out her hand but stopped halfway. She hesitated and changed it into a pat on Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar's shoulder before softly sighing.

The next second, her face returned to her cold ice-like expression. Energy erupted from her body as she charged fearsomely toward the Beyond Grade As before her!

She just hoped that Han Xiao's main body was not the one standing beside her now.

However, before I'm killed in a battle, I should be able to see you one last time…

"Know your place." Sagman snorted and brought his teammates to once again fight Hila.

Just as Sierron was about to bring his teammates and join the battle, they suddenly felt a sense of danger.

"Boom!"

An extremely powerful psychic energy wave swept over them. The members of the federation were shocked as they quickly activated their defense measures but were still blown away. The attack also contained a powerful mind attack. Many of them shivered and felt an overwhelming painful headache.

This made everyone shocked. Sagman and the other four stopped as well and looked up. The attacker was their leader, Kasuyi's doppelganger.

Aren't we temporary allies now? Why did His Excellency Kasuyi attack the federation's men?

Hila's movements paused as well. She was confused too.

That's weird. Why are they suddenly fighting each other?

Sierron got rid of the slight headache, stared at Kasuyi's doppelganger, and yelled, "What is the meaning of this‽"

With hands behind his back, Kasuyi said, "The federation's goal isn't just to kill Hila, is it? You people want to capture her and use her as a chip to force Black Star to do something for you."

Sierron's expression changed. Given how certain Kasuyi was, he definitely knew about this from somewhere or someone, so there was no point faking it anymore. He did not deny it and said coldly, "How did you know that?"

"According to how you people do things, I could've easily guessed," Kasuyi said calmly. "You people only came into the battle midway and even brought a Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device. Compared to killing someone, this is more like a kidnapping. The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter is still in your hands. If I'm not wrong, you want Black Star to open the seal of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter in exchange for Hila."

Suddenly, the psychic energy around Kasuyi's body erupted like he was furious.

"If it was something else, it would not be a big deal. However, the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter is the church's treasure. It definitely needs to be prioritized before Hila. Even if I must give up my mission today, I'll stop you people from kidnapping Hila. The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter can't be used by the federation no matter what!"

Feeling Kasuyi's skyrocketing presence, Han Xiao was astonished.

Damn, are you an Oscar winner? How are you able to act this well?

Even if what he did now was reported to the upper echelons of the church, they would only compliment him for doing a good job.

Han Xiao suddenly thought that maybe this was not acting but his real thoughts…

What a pro! This was the highest level of acting—even the actor himself believed it!

If you don't receive the tiny gold man, it's definitely rigged!

Chapter 1051: Main Body's Arrival

The federation wants to capture a hostage to force Black Star to unseal the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter?

As expected, upon hearing this, the expressions on Sagman and the others' faces changed. They looked at the federation's men with more hostility and caution.

They did not doubt Kasuyi's judgments at all, not only because he was the leader of this mission but also because his speculation made sense.

The Arcane Church's people always had problems with the Federation of Light. If not because the federation jumped back and forth on the side they were on during the Planet Lighthouse battle, the church would not have lost Ninjia and the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. Now that Kasuyi said the federation wanted to take a captive, Sagman and the others were reminded of how the federation did things and agreed with Kasuyi's speculation. They felt that this was totally something the federation would do.

On the issue of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, the church and the federation had been arguing about it for a very long time. The church could only endure it all this time because they knew that the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was sealed and the federation could not use or study it as well. Thus, they could put up with the federation possessing the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter for the time being.

However, if the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was unsealed, the church would definitely not take it any longer.

Compared to Hila, the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was clearly more important. They could not let the federation have their way!

Of course, Kasuyi did not guess this; the Mechanic Emperor had told him about it.

Although the federation was the Mechanic Emperor's long-time boss, in terms of his plan, he naturally would not want something that was especially powerful against Beyond Grade As such as the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter to be used by any civilization. In his eyes, being sealed was where it belonged.

"Since that's the case, let's talk with our fists." Sierron's expression turned cold, and powerful Pugilist flames blasted out as his voice echoed like thunder. "You guys go deal with Hila first; I'll deal with Kasuyi. This is just a doppelganger. When I'm done with it, I'll help you guys."

Then, he released a thick and blinding Shockwave Blast from his fist like a mini sun.

Like his nickname, Star Shatterer, his Pugilist style was known for overpowering his enemies head on.

Kasuyi also fired powerful psychic energy to take on the attack.

Boom!

As the two attacks clashed, it was like the sky shattered!

In a blinding light, the world seemed to have turned white entirely.

Boom!

Sierron and Kasuyi fought head-on for the first attack, then turned into two phantoms entangled together. Pugilist flames and Void psychic energy clashed hundreds of times every second, emitting waves of aftershock as they fought at higher and higher altitudes, creating another battlefield in outer space.

At the same time, the five federation Beyond Grade As quickly descended and stood opposite Sagman and the others, while Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar and Hila stood on the side.

The three sides stood in a triangle shape.

This could turn into a battle between three sides at any time.

"So, these are the five sent by the federation…"

Han Xiao sized the federation's people up and nodded in his mind.

He had a rather clear understanding of the strength of these people. Not only did he remember what they had done in the previous life, but he also had the detailed data of them collected during the Meeting of the Gods.

The five people from the federation there were all mid-level combatants. Among them, the strongest should be Crystal Soul, who had a Universal Treasure named 'Star Crown' and had a similar position as the church's Sagman. The weakest among them should be Hades, who had only joined the federation recently. He had similar strength to Tolaen.

What was worth paying attention to was Mornisa. Han Xiao remembered that she was once the Mechanic Emperor's student and followed alongside the Mechanic Emperor to study machinery before she became known. She had only become a Beyond Grade A later. Han Xiao was wondering if she was an actor as well.

While Han Xiao was secretly analyzing the situation, Sagman and the others were in a dilemma as well. They did not know if they should fight Hila or the people of the federation first.

If they fought Hila first, the federation's people would disturb them, and the federation might achieve their goal if they were not careful.

However, if they fought the federation first, they would feel stupid for leaving Hila on the side after fighting her half way, only to help her fight others.

At this time, the federation's Hades suddenly spoke in the public channel.

"People of the Arcane Church, although we have different goals, we can't waste our trips here. If you turn to fight us, we will all become a joke. So, we might as well first get rid of Black Star's Lord's Avatar, then beat Hila till she can't fight back, control the situation, and then discuss what to do with her."

In Hades' eyes, Sierron would definitely be able to handle Kasuyi's doppelganger. If they got rid of Black Star's Lord's Avatar, they would still have Sierron while the church would not have Kasuyi. With the two sides no longer balanced, they would be able to control the situation and take Hila away.

Hearing this, Sagman was a little hesitant. He then looked up at Kasuyi, turned to look at Black Star's avatar and Hila, and made up his mind, nodding with clenched teeth.

"Okay, take down Hila first."

At this moment, he made the decision not to listen to Kasuyi's order from earlier.

Just as Hades said, if they suddenly turned to help Hila right after they were beating her up, he would indeed feel stupid, and they would become a joke throughout the universe.

Another reason was, unlike Kasuyi, Sagman was not willing to waste all this effort. Therefore, he wanted to take a gamble—if they could kill Hila while working together with the federation, they would also shatter the federation's plans. If they killed the hostage, they would never have to worry about the enemies taking her hostage. Perfect.

This was also partially personal. Being locked inside the Spacetime Amber did not feel good. He could still remember it vividly even now, and he was ashamed of it. He had always hoped to hurt Black Star deeply, so from the bottom of his heart, he was not willing to give up this opportunity to kill Hila and hurt Black Star.

Earlier, Hila had shown her powerful regenerative ability, so dragging the fight out was not optimal. If ten Beyond Grade As worked together, their explosive damage would counter Hila's regenerative ability to a certain extent. This was also why Sagman thought about killing Hila while working together with the federation.

He knew that both sides had ulterior motives. Even if they worked together, they would still secretly hold each other back. However, he was confident that he could create an opportunity to kill Hila right under the federation's nose—he had a few powerful forbidden spell scrolls that were yet to be used!

With a little bit of discussion, the two sides barely came to an agreement. The next second, the ten Beyond Grade As of the federation and the church turned around, their hostile sights focused on Hila.

A horrifying pressure arrived like a tsunami!

Hila's face turned slightly pale, but her expression remained cold.

At this time, the broad back of a machine stepped before her and blocked away all the eyes filled with hostility, as well as all the pressure.

"Don't worry. I'm here beside you." Han Xiao's calm voice appeared.

Hila almost dazed.

It was this familiar scene once again, this back that protected her every time. Her emotions were difficult to soothe.

"Black Star…"

"What?"

"… When will your main body arrive?"

Han Xiao turned and gave her a glance. He then said with a meaningful tone, "No hurry, let me fly for a while."

…

Inside the palace of the Beast Ancestor's stronghold, Gorutan drank while chattering with Sorokin's manifestation, waiting for good news.

After waiting for quite some time, Sorokin placed the glass down and asked, "Your Excellency Beast Ancestor, how far have the troops you sent gone?"

"What's the hurry? Do you not trust my subordinates?" Gorutan replied impatiently.

After experiencing Sorokin's confident words, he was persuaded. As long as he was not in danger, Gorutan was more than happy to make the situation worse for Hila.

Not long ago, he had given the order for some of his officers to take a fleet and destroy the stargate stations nearby, attempting to cut off the route that the dynasty's reinforcements would arrive in so that they would not reach in time and Hila would not have reinforcements.

"It's an important issue. If the dynasty's reinforcements arrive, the situation will become more complicated. Killing a Beyond Grade A that's in the Black Star Army but not an ally of the dynasty isn't a problem as long as it's done quickly, but the church and the federation might not be willing to commit to it if they had to face the dynasty's forces head-on," Sorokin said.

"Tsk, you have a lot of interesting ideas as always."

With an impatient expression, Gorutan placed the glass down, took out the communicator to contact his officer, and asked, "Where are you? Have you arrived at the stargate station?"

"F-father… " The officer on-screen was shivering. "We were intercepted by someone."

"Hmm?" Gorutan's expression suddenly changed as he yelled, "Who dared intercept my men‽"

"It's the Mechanic Emperor's mechanical army, and he brought his Apostle Weapons along. We weren't able to win him…"

Gorutan suddenly stood up, accidentally toppling the glass and spilling the alcohol.

"Why did he suddenly intercept my men?

As a peak Beyond Grade A as well, Gorutan was not afraid of Manison. There was just a difference in class styles. He was not willing to mess with someone with such an enormous army like the Mechanic Emperor. They had intercepted his men, which did not look friendly at all.

Sorokin was surprised as well. He softly tapped the table and had an idea.

"I have a rough guess. From the Mechanic Emperor's attitude during the Meeting of the Gods, he definitely does not support this mission targeting Hila, so he probably guarded against it earlier. As you're the first one to let this message spread, it can be said that you started this. Hence, the Mechanic Emperor must have targeted you long ago, and by fighting you now, it should be to stop you from destroying stargates."

Having thought of that, Sorokin frowned as he felt a slight headache.

The Mechanic Emperor had also interfered in this event, which meant that a lot of things might be different. Initially, he felt that the federation or the church would most likely succeed, but now, he was uncertain.

Sorokin had known the Mechanic Emperor for a very long time. He knew that this guy was also very cunning. Once Manison decided to interfere, it would definitely be more than just dealing with Gorutan's troops. If he guessed correctly, Manison would have made other arrangements.

"I thought he would be just watching and not doing anything, but he actually secretly restricted the movements of the federation. He's got guts. I'm afraid the chances of this mission succeeding…"

Sorokin started pondering. Among the hundred or so Beyond Grade As in the entire universe, very few were strong enough for him to take seriously, but the Mechanic Emperor was one of them.

While he was pondering, Gorutan directly contacted the Mechanic Emperor and questioned him.

"Manison! Why did you hold up my men‽"

Manison's face appeared on the screen. "Did you forget the agreement we made in the Meeting of the Gods?""

"Hila reduced my life span and killed quite many of my subordinates. Are you telling me to just let it go?" Gorutan said coldly. "The agreement is all you talk about. Am I, a peak Beyond Grade A, less valuable than Hila? You don't want the others to totally offend Black Star, but are you not afraid of offending me?"

"She's already facing a dire situation because of you. I hope you can stop here. If she really dies, it won't be beneficial for you." Manison shook his head.

Gorutan snorted. "Humph, are you saying that Black Star will take revenge? You think I'm afraid of him? He's the one who messed with me first. If he wants to play, I'll play with him till the end! I'll get rid of one of his most important comrades and teach him a lesson."

Every time he thought of how big a loss he had taken and how he had been threatened by Black Star, he became more furious.

"I hope you can think of the bigger picture," Manison said with a deep voice.

"I'm not the one that's making the move right now. Plus, that's your big picture, not mine," Gorutan sneered coldly. "I'm giving you face by playing along with that shared battlefront thing. This is between Black Star and me; it has nothing to do with you. Yet, you're here to interfere… What, you really think you're the leader of the Beyond Grade As and have the right to control what I do? Let me tell you, don't get ahead of yourself!"

Manison narrowed his eyes, giving him a deep look before hanging up.

Gorutan snorted, shattered the communicator, and threw it aside as he walked to the door.

Sorokin regained focus and hastily asked, "Where are you going?"

"Humph, the Mechanic Emperor is holding up my men. I'm not going to wait here for him to let them go. I'm going to bring my men back, and if I have time, I'll destroy a few stargate stations on the way." Gorutan walked out directly.

…

At the Black Star Army's stronghold, the battle had lasted quite a while and become a fight between three sides.

After the Federation of Light's fleet and Mornisa's mechanical army joined the battle, the defensive fleet of the stronghold was once again restrained. The two sides fought intensely around the planet. The scale of the battle could already be considered a galactic battle.

Sierron and Kasuyi's doppelganger were still fighting. Kasuyi was strong. Relying on his enormous mana pool, he temporarily stalled Sierron with just a doppelganger while dividing the battlefield at the same time.

This award-winning actor was the most important part in helping Han Xiao to stall the federation. He was of great use.

Han Xiao was secretly glad about this. If both parties had focused on Hila, the situation would have been close to impossible to get out of alive. In that case, he would have had no choice but to execute the final plan.

However, even though there was an actor on the enemy's side, Hila's situation was still extremely tough. The attacks from a total of ten Beyond Grade As filled her vision. It was horrifying.

Despite having successfully linked with Aurora, Hila still could not fight back. It had nothing to do with her regeneration ability; she was just completely overpowered. If not because she was absorbing Aurora's vital energy, her one-time reviving ability would have been used long ago.

And this was with Han Xiao forcefully taking on part of the pressure that she was facing without considering his losses.

With so many Beyond Grade As working together, the power of their attacks would not just be additive. Han Xiao's mechanical soldiers were destroyed countless times and reaching the limits of [Waste Modification]; he would not be able to rebuild them if this kept going.

'Mechanical Catastrophe' Francisco had set up a space stabilization anchor and wormhole disrupter, and the Federation of Light fleet had set up another layer after they arrived. The spacetime of this area was way too stable, so Han Xiao could not open his secondary dimensional army box and Dimension Factory. All he could use was the troops stationed in the stronghold. Hence, he had no choice but to deal with the spacetime stabilization device through Virtual Intrusion.

However, both the federation and the church had measures against this. That was especially so for the federation. Not only did they have Mornisa, they also had another Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanic who was providing ranged assistance and protection for their artificial intelligence.

If the mechanical army was destroyed, just one Lord's Avatar would not be able to fight ten Beyond Grade As.

Fortunately, they're not so united. The church and the federation are cautious of each other, which somewhat decreases the power of their attacks, Han Xiao thought.

He turned around and glanced at Hila. Currently, he was separated from her, and not far away, countless attacks were being thrown at Hila. The situation she was in was extremely dire. She was receiving tons of damage every second. The glow of vital energy never disappeared and kept regenerating her health.

Aurora won't be able to hold on for long even though she's at the Calamity Grade now. It won't be long before she gets completely exhausted.

At the same time, Sagman and the others surrounded Hila to attack her while he reminded his teammates, "Later, when the next round of the federation's focus fire heavily injures Hila, Taylor, use all those scrolls, some to stop the federation's people and some to aid our following full power attacks. We will eliminate Hila before she can regenerate and shatter her soul!"

"Got it."

Taylor nodded and prepared to use the scrolls.

While everyone was highly focused, suddenly, an enormous energy source rocketed into the senses of everyone present and quickly approached at an astonishing speed.

"Someone else is here‽"

Everyone was shocked. Their movements paused as they looked up.

A mass of light streams were approaching at an extremely high speed from afar, dragging trails of flames behind. It was a mechanical army that was extremely huge, dozens of times larger than all the mechanical troops that were present there!

At the front of it was a silhouette shrouded in deep blue flames, heading right toward Hila's location like a meteor.

"Who is that? They're so fast! Are they here to help Hila?"

Sagman was confused. He looked around and realized that the federation's people had the same confused looks.

At this time, they suddenly saw that Sierron had left his opponent behind and headed right toward that quickly approaching dark blue meteor, attempting to stop it and not let whoever had arrived reach Hila.

The two silhouettes clashed into each other, but the next moment, everyone present watched on with disbelief!

Boom!

A blood fog exploded!

It was Sierron who was blown away like a baseball. He flew out while spraying blood, together with… a shattered arm covered in blood!

Sierron had a total of four arms, and one of them had been blown off!

"What‽"

Everyone had a look of disbelief on their face.

Heavily injuring Sierron with one hit? Who is this guy‽

This time, the silhouette was also forced to stop in midair after clashing into Sierron. The flames around them disappeared, exposing the man inside, whom everyone there was familiar with. He was looking down at the ten Beyond Grade As who were surrounding and attacking Hila.

At this moment, other than Kasuyi, all the Beyond Grade As of the federation and the church were completely astounded.

Black Star!

How can he be here‽

Isn't his main body in his base? How did he arrive here‽

Many Beyond Grade As there did not notice that the moment they saw Han Xiao's main body arrive, more than half of their confidence in this mission instantly vanished.

They would happily bully Han Xiao's Lord's Avatar, but many were instantly afraid to face Han Xiao's main body.

Han Xiao had an extraordinary combat history. He had proved his strength as a peak Beyond Grade A long ago through battles.

Seeing Han Xiao's arrival, everyone felt a strong sense of pressure and became hesitant. Hila made use of this opportunity to flee from the encirclement and gasped for air.

"This is not good…" Sagman was reminded of how it felt to be sealed by the Spacetime Amber, and he shivered.

At this time, facing everyone, Han Xiao slowly spoke.

"I'm here." He coldly looked around at the Beyond Grade As who had extremely uncomfortable expressions on their faces and said with a calm but pressurizing tone, "Now… it's your turn to run."

Chapter 1052: Explosion

The expressions on the Beyond Grade As' faces changed. They remained silent and did not respond while quickly analyzing the situation in their minds. They all felt that the situation had become truly difficult.

The reason they had surprise-attacked the stronghold was because they wanted to eliminate Hila when Black Star's main body was not present. They did not want to fight Black Star's main body face to face.

Black Star had peak Beyond Grade A strength, and his Indestructible Body was extremely tough to deal with. Plus, his position was very special. He had the Evolution Cube, so he was very important to the dynasty. At the same time, since his main body was there, he had definitely brought along the Spacetime Amber.

It would be drastically more difficult to kill Hila with Black Star's main body present.

"There's probably no chance now. To think that his main body actually came…" Sagman stared at Han Xiao with fear.

If it was any other Beyond Grade A Mechanic, the main body arriving would have been a risk. However, Black Star had proved long ago that he was a breath of fresh air among the paper Mechanics.

For the time being, everyone was hesitant and did not know what to do.

Sierron finally stopped his body from being blown away. His face was filled with rage, as well as a tint of shock. He pressed on the cut on his arm and glared at Han Xiao.

As a peak Beyond Grade A, I could not even block the charge of a Mechanic and was heavily wounded in one hit‽

Thinking of the power of that attack, Sierron was filled with shock.

Such a powerful single target attack was rare even for him.

At this point of time, Sierron only had one thought in his mind.

What kind of martial art did Black Star use?

He's been hiding this trump card all this time…

Han Xiao's threat in Sierron's heart increased several levels.

He turned to look at his missing arm, controlled his muscles and veins to instantly stop the bleeding, and used his Pugilist energy to speed up cell generation. A new arm grew out in no time. Compared to the rest of his body, though, its skin tone was visibly lighter.

Sierron casually blasted his broken arm that was floating in the cosmic space into atoms before slowly flying back to the battlefield. He suppressed his shock and rage and did not act immediately. Instead, he observed everyone's expression and pondered.

Kasuyi was floating quietly on the side while looking at Han Xiao. He did not look like he wanted to speak either.

The battlefield became strangely silent. Han Xiao, Sierron, and Kasuyi, these three peak Beyond Grade As, formed a triangle while the rest of the Beyond Grade As fixed their attention on the three of them.

Everyone knew that what happened next depended on the discussion between the three of them.

Black Star's main body had made a threatening comment right after his arrival, but he did not do anything after. The various Beyond Grade As were not surprised by this. After all, they had the complete advantage in numbers. Even if Black Star had finally arrived, he would not dare act recklessly.

He was alone and had no help, so he was probably not willing to face the ten or so Beyond Grade As on the two sides at the same time. Thus, he probably had no choice but to endure his rage and solve the problem through negotiations.

Having understood this, the Beyond Grade As present all looked much more relieved.

Now that the Black Star's main body had arrived, they did indeed have to retreat. However, that was not because they were afraid of Black Star but because there was no need to stay there anymore as the success rate of the mission had decreased drastically.

Although they feared Black Star's main body and his Universal Treasure, there was no need to be afraid of him given how many Beyond Grade As were present. In the eyes of Sagman and the others, Black Star alone would be sufficient to protect himself but not enough to cause much trouble.

While everyone was secretly speculating, Han Xiao waited for the mechanical army behind to catch up with him while looking at the interface.

When Hila was attacked, an Urgent Mission had been triggered on the interface. It was similar to the mission for the Planet Lighthouse battle.

_____________________

Urgent Mission—[Rescue Hila]

Mission Introduction: Hila's Esper Ability is seen as a threat by multiple Beyond Grade As. With powerful talent comes disaster. The church and the federation have decided to eliminate this threat.

Mission Requirements: Hila surviving in the attack.

Reward: 75 – 92 billion EXP, +1 Legendary Point, 4 Random Rewards, 4 Unknown Character Summon Cards, 1 Blank Character Summon Card.

Bonus Mission Requirements: Working together with the dynasty's reinforcements, capture the enemy Beyond Grade As.

Bonus Reward: For every Beyond Grade A captured, draw one ability from the target.

_____________________

This is the most difficult mission I've ever seen… Han Xiao was amused.

The number of Beyond Grade As present was similar to the Planet Lighthouse battle, but Han Xiao now only had Hila on his side, and they had to face more than ten Beyond Grade As. The last guy to face this kind of situation was EsGod, and he ended up receiving a free 500 years lease for a luxurious single person cell inside the dynasty's prison.

Nonetheless, the mission rewards were the best he had ever seen. For every person he captured, he would be able to draw an ability from that person. The more he captured, the more abilities he would be able to draw.

Now that my main body is here, there's not a high chance the church and the federation will try to forcefully kill Hila in front of me. They'll probably retreat very soon, and it's still unknown when the dynasty's reinforcements will arrive. Therefore, in order to complete the bonus requirements, I'll have to rely on myself.

Han Xiao had already made plans when he was on the way, and he did not change his mind now.

He focused his thoughts and was reminded of something else.

On the way there, he had received a report from Black Star Palace; there was a Beyond Grade A who arrived on his doorstep to challenge him, and Ames had accepted the challenge. This incident was strange in every way.

The Great Mechanic Han always maintained connection with the base and knew the situation of the battle over there. That Traveler guy was showcasing his true powers and maintaining the upper hand, but there could only be one Lord's Avatar at a time. If Han Xiao diverted his attention to what was happening at his base, his main body would have a tough time.

"Interesting, deliberately diverting my attention so that the church and the federation will have an easier time… Hmm, Traveler."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

Traveler was a neutral Beyond Grade A on the surface but actually had a very close relationship with Super Star Cluster civilizations, which only very few people knew.

However, to him, Traveler's identity was no secret. It had been exposed long ago in the previous life.

Did the church and the federation work together with the Super Star Cluster civilizations on this matter?

"No, it can't be." Han Xiao overthrew this speculation.

Traveler's identity was a secret to the outside world. Even if the federation and the church worked with the Super Star Cluster civilization, they would not have sent Traveler, or his identity would have been exposed.

"Looks like there's more to this…" Han Xiao slightly frowned.

He was not concerned about the truth for the time being. What he knew for sure was that the Super Star Cluster behind Traveler definitely had something to do with this.

The others did not know Traveler's background, but he knew it clearly. There was no need to even investigate it; it would never be wrong to blame the civilization behind Traveler for this, and it would be simpler and easier.

Causing trouble at my house, they've got guts. The Throne is still on the way. When it arrives at the base, I'll deal with you.

Hila flew to Han Xiao's side.

The other Beyond Grade As did not stop her but only followed her over and waited beside their captains.

"You… shouldn't have come." Hila had a complicated look in her eyes.

From the way she looked at it, in order to save her, Han Xiao's main body had deliberately rushed here into this trap, gotten surrounded by more than ten Beyond Grade As, and taken so many risks.

Hila knew that compared to her, the church and the federation wanted to get rid of Black Star even more. Plus, he had the Evolution Cube and the Spacetime Amber with him. If these enemies changed their plan to make Black Star the target… she would be the reason.

Originally, Hila thought that she would definitely die and really wanted to see Han Xiao one last time, but when he really came, Hila could not help but worry about Han Xiao's safety.

All this time, Hila always lived by being straightforward and direct. Very rarely was she ever caught between such conflicted thoughts.

"If I didn't come, who'd save you?" Han Xiao turned to give her a gentle smile. "You're safe now. Why? Because I'm here."

Hila softly bit her lips and suddenly held Han Xiao's hand.

Han Xiao raised his brows and was about to say something when he suddenly felt waves of vital energy being sent into his body through Hila's hand. He received a ton of enhanced statuses on the interface.

After holding his hand for a few seconds, Hila let it go, adjusted her hair, and coolly said, "Aurora's ability can now enhance the strength of living beings. I can't do much, only share the vital energy with you."

"…Thanks."

At this time, Sierron said with a deep voice, "Black Star, since you're here, I'll give you face. I have come up with a deal. Are you interested?"

He felt that Han Xiao was stalling time to wait for reinforcements, so he did not plan to continue waiting and started the conversation.

Hearing this, Han Xiao turned to look at Sierron, wiped the smile of his face, and said coldly, "Go on."

"If you agree to unseal the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter for the federation, not only will we retreat, but we can even fight these people from the church with you." Sierron's hostile sights moved around Kasuyi.

Han Xiao's hit earlier had combined [Charge—Endless Potential] and Silver Shadow's Character Summon Card [Comet Rush].

In fact, he had arrived around the battlefield long ago but had been farming distance travelled to make this initial hit stronger. Originally, he wanted to first eliminate a more ordinary Beyond Grade A, but Sierron unexpectedly came to stop him, so he had no choice but to vent all this power on that thick-skinned Pugilist.

Although the power of this attack was far from being enough to make a peak Beyond Grade A Pugilist lose his combat capability, it still made Sierron feel threatened. Seeing that the plan would be very difficult to pull off, he had given up on capturing Hila as a hostage and attempted to reach his goal through a deal.

Sierron did not know that Kasuyi was an actor yet; he felt that Black Star needed help.

Kasuyi did not mind at all, "Then, our church will definitely retreat instantly, so you won't achieve your goal. In the end, Black Star will still be the one benefitting from it."

Then, Kasuyi suddenly said, "Since the federation has an idea, I shall suggest a deal on behalf of the church as well."

"Go on." Han Xiao gave him a calm look.

"Black Star, I know your Spacetime Amber is very magical and can even imprison Beyond Grade As. How about this? We work together and capture these Federation of Light Beyond Grade As, then you sell them to us, and we will have chips to exchange for the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. What do you say?"

Sierron's expression became grave as he glared at Kasuyi.

While the two of them faced off with each other, Han Xiao took a deep breath and said, "No need to make things so troublesome. I'm rejecting all of your deals… You came to beat up my men, yet now you want to make a deal with me? Don't even think about it! All of you, come at me together."

Sierron's eyes widened with disbelief as he looked at Han Xiao.

Kasuyi was surprised too. This was not in the script.

Not just the two of them, all the Beyond Grade As of the federation and the church were shocked and stared at Han Xiao in disbelief.

Has this guy… lost his mind‽

He wants to fight more than ten Beyond Grade As alone, including two peak Beyond Grade As? Is he looking to be killed?

After extreme shock, wrath followed.

You think us Beyond Grade As are all made of glass‽ Don't underestimate us!

Are you not clear of the situation? Sure, your main body has arrived, but do you really think you can fight us all alone and that we took a step back because we're afraid of you?

"Are you serious?" Sierron's expression sank completely.

"You destroyed my stronghold, tried to kill my Deputy Army Commander, but want to retreat right in front of me… Do you think that's possible?"

Boom!

Han Xiao's tone was firm as his energy increased gradually.

Hearing this, the look in everyone's eyes became even more hostile.

Sierron was completely furious. "Think about this clearly! Given the current situation, we won't hesitate to make you the target!"

Hila tensed up and quickly stepped in front of Han Xiao. Death energy spread out once again as she was on full alert.

No matter what decision Han Xiao made, no matter what strong enemies they had to face, she would always fight alongside Han Xiao without any hesitation.

This time, Han Xiao held onto her shoulder and pulled her behind him. "Don't have to be so nervous. I alone am enough."

Before anyone could vent their rage, a sky trembling energy impact exploded from Han Xiao's body.

Buzz!

Violent golden Mechanical Force flickered and danced like lightning whips. Han Xiao's energy seemed to be increasing infinitely.

Facing so many Beyond Grade As, even Han Xiao did not dare hold back. He instantly used the trump Character Summon Cards in his inventory!

[Mechanic Emperor Character Summon Card—The Ancient Ones]!

[Tyrant Character Summon Card—Polar Channel Flow—Cellular Overdrive]!

[Dragon Emperor Character Summon Card—Force Field—Dragon Body]!

[Nero Character Summon Card—Perfect Mechanical Sense]!

With the stacked effects of multiple Character Summon Cards, the energy Han Xiao was giving off looked horrifying even for peak Beyond Grade As. It even stinged everyone's senses.

Sagman and the others' expressions changed drastically from rage to shock!

The strength Han Xiao was displaying at this moment far exceeded what they knew about him!

Even Kasuyi, who had always remained calm, was moved at this moment!

Han Xiao's eyes glowed brightly like two mini blue suns.

"Let me see how many of you can escape!"

Before the Beyond Grade As could regain their focus, Mechanical Force lightning shot out from Han Xiao's body, instantly connecting to the mechanical army like an endless web of lightning.

The next moment, the metal tsunami formed by the mechanical army came crashing down!

Chapter 1053: I, Black Star, Am Not Cheating!

Sagman and the others were stunned by Han Xiao's extraordinary energy levels. They did not expect Black Star to really strike. Shocked, they quickly took defensive measures.

Boom!

The next moment, the opposing Beyond Grade As were submerged under the sea of mechanical army.

As the battle started, they became even more astonished. They felt an incomparable level of pressure even from the mechanical army.

If it was the army of a normal Beyond Grade A, they would have been able to easily move in and out of it while destroying everything in their way. However, Han Xiao's mechanical army made them feel like they were trapped in a swamp and could hardly move, not to mention breaking out of it. Only Kasuyi and Sierron were able to move freely.

This was not only because the mechanical army Han Xiao's main body brought was dozens of times larger than the two other Mechanics' armies present but also because the mechanical army's strength far exceeded what they could imagine. The Mechanical Force gave the mechanical soldiers incredible levels of enhancements!

Han Xiao already had the [Perfect Mechanical Sense] talent, and now he activated Nero's Character Summon Card as well, stacking the two Perfect Mechanical Sense talents, increasing his Machinery Affinity to a completely new territory.

Facing such crushing pressure, the Beyond Grade As of the federation and the church had no time to think about anything else other than to subconsciously work together to fight the mechanical army.

Boom!

As soon as the battle erupted, it entered the climax and became a huge war.

Inside the endless mechanical army, there were over ten spheres of light moving within. Countless beams and attacks were gathering toward these light spheres, and these light spheres were the battlefields where each of the Beyond Grade As was under intense fire.

"How can he be this strong‽" Sagman said with a shocked tone.

"The last time Black Star went all out was during the Planet Lighthouse battle. After more than two decades, this is the second time he's used his full strength. It's shocking to think that he's become this much stronger!" Taylor was both panicking and jealous.

More than two decades ago, the few of them who had taken part in the Planet Lighthouse warfare still had a vivid impression of Han Xiao's performance back then. Now that more than two decades had passed, they knew that Black Star had definitely become stronger, but they never expected him to become so much stronger!

"This level of pressure is starting to feel similar to the Mechanic Emperor…" Kasuyi's expression was grave.

He was within Han Xiao's attack range as well, and he was mainly dodging attacks and slacking while thinking about the rest of the script.

He could understand the reason behind Black Star's sudden attack—being the party that was being attacked, Black Star could not just let them retreat easily and had to, at the very least, display his intention to counter-attack. However, the strength Black Star was displaying now exceeded Kasuyi's expectations.

At this time, Sierron said with a dumbfounded tone, "This is… Polar Channel Flow—Cellular Overdrive!"

Hearing this, everyone was shocked.

Isn't this one of the explosive abilities of the Pugilist class. Why can Black Star use it too? Isn't he a Mechanic‽

"I'm definitely not mistaken. The aura Black Star is giving off feels exactly like this ability. By squeezing out his own future potential, he's exchanging it for higher power!" Sierron said with a firm tone. "Not thinking about how Black Star can use this ability, its concept remains the same!"

This was quickly accepted. Everyone's expression became complicated. Their sights passed through the mechanical army and looked at Han Xiao with shock and astonishment.

This means that… in order to keep us here, Black Star is willing to burn his own potential‽

He could have totally made us retreat. Did he really have to do this much‽

If that was the case, they were not surprised as to why Black Star became this much stronger. After all, it was only temporary.

Nonetheless, such explosive power was still quite horrifying!

Seeing how firm Han Xiao was, many people intended to retreat.

Kasuyi sighed in his mind.

Initially, when he saw Han Xiao suddenly taking the spotlight and going off-script, he was a little unhappy and wanted to stop him. However, when he saw Black Star's firm attitude, he decided not to go all out.

Since Black Star had given his all, he planned to give him face and cut him some slack. After all, he believed that Black Star knew where to draw the line.

On the side, when Hila saw Han Xiao displaying his incredible power, she was excited and shocked, but when she heard this explanation, she was stupefied.

The next second, Hila's eyes turned red, with burning rage and murderous intent!

She did not think that Black Star would burn his own potential. Looking at the reason behind all of this, was Black Star not doing this just to save her‽

A stinging pain suddenly struck her heart and flooded her entire body.

Hila turned around stiffly. The way she looked at Han Xiao was different now. There was only remorse and apology deeply embedded in her bones.

"I…"

Hila was just about to say something, but Han Xiao waved and interrupted her.

"You don't have to say anything. I'm fine."

"… I'm so sorry."

Hila bit her lips, clenched her fists, and charged into battle without saying anything else.

Death energy rushed toward the church's Beyond Grade As together with her like a tornado. Her burning rage was all vented on the enemies!

Looking at Hila's uncontrollably murderous intent, Han Xiao did not know what to say.

The side effect of using Polar Channel Flow—Cellular Overdrive was a seven-percent permanent increase in the cost of leveling up his character and abilities, which was equivalent to burning his potential. However, what these people did not know was that Han Xiao was using the Tyrant's Character Summon Card. Although it only had one usage, the Character Summon Cards had zero side effects.

Sierron's misjudgment made everyone misunderstand the situation.

Let it be. Not like it's a bad thing. In fact, it's actually beneficial for me. Han Xiao shook his head. Of course, he was not going to explain this to anyone.

Some of these Character Summon Cards could only be used once to grant him extraordinary strength, and using them in exchange for permanent abilities was definitely worth it.

He was filled with a sense of power he had never felt before. The Tyrant's Character Summon Card made his basic attributes and energy strength far beyond the normal, reaching the standard of the next Promotion. While the double Mechanical Sense talents made the power of his mechanical army skyrocket. With these two together, he became terrifyingly strong.

Those that received the most enhancements were elite combatants such as the Apostle Weapons.

…

Swoosh!

Red Devil Tolaen's leaned back and barely dodged Psionic Prime's ordinary spear strike, which slashed his thick magic shield in half and opened a deep wound on his bone-spike-covered chest, exposing his dark brown chest bone.

Tolaen hastily swung the bones on his tail toward Psionic Prime's mechanical body, which Psionic Prime calmly blocked with his spear.

Bang!

As the bones and the spear clashed, a shockwave exploded!

Tolaen was a powerful melee combat mage with tons of spells that enhanced his various combat capabilities, yet Psionic Prime, who was covered in gold Mechanical Force, fought him head-on without even taking a single step back.

"Help! Quickly! His Apostle Weapons are too strong!" Tolaen yelled.

With the enhancements of two Perfect Mechanical Senses, just Psionic Prime alone gave him enough pressure.

Plus, Psionic Prime was not the only one fighting him—Heaven-Suppressing Banner, Purple Sky Spirit, Silver Flash, Scarlet Flame, and many other Apostle Weapons were all focusing their fire on Tolaen.

The strategy Han Xiao used was to restrain others with his mechanical army while focusing his elite troops on one target to defeat them one by one.

"Useless!" Sagman was heavily surrounded as well. He was frustrated to hear Tolaen's cry for help.

However, he could not possibly ignore his ally. He had no choice but to squeeze out some energy to provide assistance, launching some powerful light shockwaves toward the Apostle Weapons who were attacking Tolaen.

Buzz!

At this time, countless nanoparticles swarmed out in the middle and suddenly turned into an enormous fortress, splitting Tolaen's battlefield away from the others.

This enormous mechanical fortress was surrounded by streams of light that quickly merged into a light gold translucent curtain that stood in the path of Sagman's attacks.

Boom!

Sagman's attacks were all stopped by this light-gold curtain, and countless blinding light arcs erupted!

Very soon, the blinding light dissipated, showing the absolutely unaffected flickering light curtain, leaving the mechanical fortress completed undamaged.

"Such strong defenses!" Sagman was shocked.

This mechanical fortress was one of Han Xiao's Apostle Weapons. His name was Heaven's Wall. This light curtain was somewhat similar to the Psionic Prime Spear; it was also a weapon that was created together with the birth of the Apostle Weapon. This light curtain's name was 'Wall of Defense', and as its name suggested, it focused on blocking attacks.

Heaven's Wall had more than one weapon. He also had 'Ion Green Flame', which was used to attack.

Suddenly, a large number of barrels extended from this fortress, shooting out beams of green light at Sagman and the others. This was a special type of ion energy attack. It was not only destructive but also had many other attributes.

"Sh*t, I'm isolated." Tolaen was frustrated by this situation. Just as he was about to attempt to escape, he felt a chilling sense of danger.

In the blink of an eye, a tiny beam of light crept through the gaps between the mechanical troops around and easily penetrated his magical shield. Tolaen hastily tried to dodge it, but it still ended up landing on his shoulder.

Boom!

The next moment, an enormous wound suddenly appeared on Tolaen's shoulder. This attack had dealt True Damage to him.

He quickly pressed on his wound and dodged around the other attacks. In moments of panic and horror, he looked in the direction that the beam of light came from, where he saw a human-shaped Apostle Weapon aiming a special firearm at him.

The moment Tolaen looked over, this Apostle Weapon suddenly disappeared without a trace.

Dark Shadow was a sniper-type assassin Apostle Weapon. His weapon was 'Godly Camouflage', which gave him extremely powerful stealth and infiltration abilities. The firearm in his hands was also a highly condensed sniper that could deal a ton of damage to single targets.

"Damn it, what weapon is that? My regeneration ability is suppressed…"

Before Tolaen could catch a breath, Mysterious Energy Host arrived. He launched a huge beam of light at Tolaen from far away, and Tolaen could only barely activate his magical shield to block it.

However, Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy had psychic attributes as well. Although Tolaen blocked the physical attack, his mind was shocked, and his channeling was interrupted.

With this golden opportunity, Hila did not hold back at all. She bombarded death energy beams on Tolaen like a thunderstorm. Tolaen was soon covered in wounds and bathed in blood.

"Why are they all attacking me?" Tolaen was frustrated.

Looking around at the entire battlefield, the one in the worst situation was none other than him.

I'm just a young new Beyond Grade A. This is bullying!

As Tolaen was in grave danger, Sagman and the others were also troubled and discussing what they could do.

"Black Star's mechanical army is way too large and powerful. We can't be restrained by him here. We have to make moves on Black Star himself. Taylor, use the forbidden spell scroll on him."

"He has an indestructible body. Will that be able to damage him?"

"It's not like we have any better choices. Let's focus our fire together with the forbidden spell," Sagman said furiously.

Taylor then tore open an attack-type forbidden spell scroll without any further hesitation.

Whoosh!

Magical meteors dashed out from within the scroll one after another, penetrating the multiple layers of psionic shields in their path, heading directly toward Han Xiao. This spell had an excellent penetrative ability. It was originally planned to be one of the trump cards to heavily wound Hila.

At the same time, Sagman and the others focused their fire at Han Xiao together with the forbidden spell. Light energy shockwaves, Pugilist Impacts, spells, psionic cannon beams, and other forms of attacks formed a tide of attacks thrown right toward Han Xiao.

The enormous energy here attracted the attention of the people of the federation not far away. They all looked over at this wave of attacks and were shocked. When facing attacks like this, most of the Beyond Grade As would have no choice but to try to escape.

With the ferocious attack dashing right toward him, Han Xiao, however, was not affected at all. All he did was raise his hand, and many sphere-shaped mechanical discs quickly gathered and formed two layers of shields that stacked on top of each other in front of Han Xiao. There was a piece of the Spacetime Amber on each and every one of those discs.

Swoosh!

Like a river stream hitting a reef, all the energy attacks slid away on the surface of the Spacetime Amber, not dealing any damage to Han Xiao at all, making the others feel both grave and jealous.

The existence of the Spacetime Amber was no secret. The fact that Han Xiao's main body was there meant that this Universal Treasure was there too.

It could even block the attack of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, so the threat of this wave of attacks was negligible to Han Xiao. Furthermore, even without the Spacetime Amber, he was tanky enough to take on all these attacks.

It was way too difficult to hurt Black Star's main body!

"We can use psychic attacks on his main body," Hades said hastily.

Both Crystal Soul and Hades were Psychics. They quickly summoned their maximum psychic energy output and attacked Han Xiao. Kasuyi thought about it for a moment. He then decided to do his job on paper as well and used psychic energy attacks on Han Xiao while holding back.

Psychics were professionals in terms of psychic attacks. They could attack the target's soul from afar, which was very difficult to guard against.

"I fixed my weakness long ago."

Unaffected, Han Xiao immediately activated Psyker's Character Summon Card, [Wall of Mind]!

The result of that was, he was completely unaffected, while Crystal Soul and Hades were both suddenly heavily wounded mentally. Their body shivered, and they became much weaker.

Psyker's Character Summon Card could reduce the attack damage dealt by psychic attacks while reflecting some of its damage. Hades and Crystal Soul did not hold back at all, so they ate their own attacks. On the other hand, Kasuyi, who deliberately held back, was not so unlucky.

It was not too horrible for Crystal Soul, as he was stronger and even had the psychic type Universal Treasure, Star Crown, so he was only a little wounded.

"He can even reflect psychic attacks‽"

Hades' face was pale. He was horrified.

Does this guy not have any weaknesses‽

Unconvinced, the two of them continued to attack. However, the more they attacked, the more damage they took from Han Xiao's damage reflection. Han Xiao remained at ease while the two Psychics kept receiving damage.

With the Great Mechanic Han's Psychological Resistance, he could actually block a lot of those psychic attacks. However, reflecting the damage was clearly much better than him just enduring the attacks. In the face of more than ten enemies, he was not going to give up any opportunity to weaken them.

…

As the fight lasted for a while, the many members of the federation and the church still had yet to get out of their difficult situations. Moving inside the mechanical army was extremely difficult.

The impact of such an enormous mechanical army, which continuously procced Han Xiao's True Damage talent, was much larger than being able to merely restrain Beyond Grade As. If they did not deal with it cautiously and got focused on, they would die right on the spot. Therefore, everyone was on edge.

If they were facing an ordinary Mechanic, they would have rushed to him long ago. However, there was absolutely no point in doing that when facing Black Star.

He was too tanky, so much so that they did not even think about closing the distance on him!

However, Sierron was the exception. As a peak Beyond Grade A Pugilist, he could easily be unstoppable in the midst of the mechanical army.

Just like the Tyrant, he also had a True Damage immunity talent, so he could ignore the focus fire of the mechanical army. However, the damage he could deal to the mechanical army was nothing given the sheer scale of the mechanical army.

The muscles on Sierron's arms expanded as he sent a Pugilist shockwave strong enough to obliterate an entire planet right toward Han Xiao, but it was still reflected by the Spacetime Amber. Seeing this, he clenched his teeth, suppressed his anger, and spoke with Kasuyi.

"Let's work together. You restrain the mechanical army to help me get close to Black Star. I'll try to restrain him instead of killing him.

"I'm out of energy," Kasuyi replied.

Sierron was speechless.

You were so energetic earlier when you fought me as if you had infinite energy, but now you're saying that you're out of energy? Who the hell are you trying to fool‽

Sierron was furious, so he left Kasuyi alone and charged toward Han Xiao alone, destroying the mechanical soldiers in his path. All four of his arms were covered in highly condensed Pugilist flames like they were coated with black paint.

"Humph, I knew you were going to do this."

Han Xiao was prepared. He activated his ability instantly. Some of the mechanical soldiers flew toward him and quickly assembled.

In the next moment, the Mechanical Deity descended!

As soon as it appeared, the Mechanical Deity swung its arm and launched its fist toward Sierron. It was shrouded in a white light energy field that was created by psionic energy and force fields.

Four black fists clashed with the mechanical fist that was millions of times larger.

Boom!

A gigantic shockwave exploded and expanded in the cosmic space!

The Mechanical Deity's arm quickly shattered, and tons of mechanical parts exploded. Sierron, on the other hand, due to his size disadvantage, was sent flying at a speed even faster than before.

Shockingly, the two sides' strength was on par.

"This punch of mine would have even destroyed the core of a planet, yet Sierron took it head-on. That's the power of a peak Beyond Grade A Pugilist, I suppose."

At this time, 'Mechanical Catastrophe' Francisco saw the Mechanical Deity and quickly contacted the federation's 'Mechanic Empress' Mornisa.

"He has used the Mechanical Deity. This is our chance. You, me, and Romo, the three of us shall use Virtual Mechanic on the Mechanical Deity right now. Even though Han Xiao is a Virtual Mechanic, he still has to deal with that carefully."

"Okay." Mornisa nodded.

At this crucial point, the Beyond Grade As of the federation and the church had no choice but to work together temporarily to fight Black Star, who was 'burning up his future potential'.

The three Mechanics quickly formed an alliance and attacked Han Xiao's virtual firewall.

Han Xiao noticed this instantly and smiled with mockery.

"Oh, they're trying to hack me?"

With all the bonuses plus the fact that he was a Virtual Mechanic, Han Xiao's ability in the Virtual Technology field was extremely high.

Among the three enemies, only Romo was a Virtual Mechanic, and he did not even send a Lord's Avatar.

In the virtual world, Han Xiao confronted the three of them. The three of them kept trying to break through Han Xiao's defenses, while Han Xiao's firewall stood strong.

Instead of being attacked, Han Xiao even followed the connection to use Virtual Intrusion on the three of them. The two members of the federation could barely stop Han Xiao's hacking with the help of their main artificial intelligence, but the same could not be said for Francisco.

Francisco was alone, and he was not even a Virtual Technology professional. His defenses were weak and were shattering by the second.

His machinery became traitors one after another and turned on their former teammates.

"I'm going to lose!" Even the movements of Francisco's Lord's Avatar started to stagger.

At this moment, an enormous mechanical hand appeared and grabbed Francisco's Lord's Avatar before he could dodge.

Ka-cha!

Francisco's Lord's Avatar turned into a pile of trash instantly.

Han Xiao curled his lips.

"Hehe, paper."

Mechanics who were using Lord's Descent could deactivate their ability any time they wanted, so there was no way to catch them. In order to get rid of them, one just had to destroy their Lord's Avatar.

After all, not every Mechanic's Lord's Avatar was as tanky as his.

Seeing this, Mornisa reluctantly gave up on the idea of trying to hack into Han Xiao's army and focused on strengthening their defenses to not let Han Xiao break through.

Suddenly, the situation of the battle took a turn.

Under the focused fire of many Apostle Weapons and Hila, Tolaen could not hold on.

The damage output of the mechanical army around him was the main source of damage he received. After all, he was not immune to True Damage. His health plummeted under the focus fire of the mechanical army, and his teammates had no way of helping him.

Bang bang bang!

"Ahhh!"

Tolaen was flooded by bullets and cannons once again. This time, he was at his limit.

Not one area on his body was unharmed. His demon horns were broken, and his mind was fuzzy from the attacks of Hila and Mysterious Energy Host. He had lost the ability to fight.

Just as Hila was about to end him, Han Xiao's Mechanical Deity stopped her.

"Don't."

"Why? They made you…" Hila clenched her teeth and dared not complete the sentence.

"He's more valuable alive."

Han Xiao shook his head and grabbed Tolaen, who had almost lost all his senses. He absorbed him into the Mechanical Deity and brought him to where his main body was.

Han Xiao took out the Spacetime Amber and sealed Tolaen right away.

Looking at the agony on this guy's face that was now fixed, Han Xiao smiled with satisfaction like a farmer counting the harvest of an entire year.

"That's one."

…

"Tolaen's been captured!"

Sagman was enraged. He looked at the Mechanical Deity, which had captured his teammate, and a sense of panic appeared in his mind.

He did not even have to think to know that Tolaen was definitely going to get a taste of the Spacetime Amber, and he felt bad for him.

Due to how uniquely tanky Black Star's main body was, they could not deal with Black Star the same way one would deal with other Mechanics. There was only one path in front of them, which would take the most effort—to eliminate Black Star's mechanical army.

However, Black Star was fighting on his own grounds. He had even burned his future potential. Given the unique combat style of Mechanics, he was extremely powerful at this point, which was due to three key components—his Mechanical Deity, his elite Apostle Weapons, and his enormous mechanical army.

The strength of Mechanics in the later stages depended on their ability to fight multiple battles at once, creating a numerical advantage in one or more battles through the suitable distribution of their troops. In this battle, the Mechanical Deity had fought Sierron on even ground, restraining a peak Beyond Grade A; the mechanical army had restrained the many Beyond Grade As; and the Apostle Weapons had focused their fire on one target at a time to defeat them one by one.

If this lasted any longer, he could not even estimate how many of them would be left there.

In the past, Black Star's only strength was his regenerative ability. Now that his attack had become this strong, Sagman's impression of him became someone who was on a completely different level that gave him nothing but despair!

"Your Excellency Kasuyi, what should we do now?"

Sagman looked at his captain.

In times like this, the person he trusted most was the leader of his team… but he did not know how much Kasuyi was holding back.

"Black Star only obtained this strength through burning his potential. It won't last long. The operation has failed. There's no point to continue fighting. We're retreating," Kasuyi said slowly.

"What about Tolaen?"

"Even you might not even be able to walk away. Why are you thinking about others?" Kasuyi shook his head.

Although he was the leader, he did not mind Black Star capturing some of them to vent his anger. The way he looked at it, since Black Star had burned his potential, the Universal Civilizations should give him some compensation. He was not the one paying for it anyway.

All these Beyond Grade As coming to kill Hila had already insulted Black Star. If he could not vent his emotions, it would not align with Kasuyi and the Mechanic Emperor's plans.

Chapter 1054: Retreat

While the Arcane Church was tempted to retreat, Sierron, who was fighting intensely with the Mechanical Deity, received the same suggestion from his side.

"Your Excellency Sierron, we should retreat now. The situation will only become worse for us. There's no point in fighting Black Star here while he burns his potential." Hades' tone was hasty.

"That's right. Although more than ten of us being forced to retreat by Black Star alone will damage our reputation, by analyzing the current situation, this is the best plan for now. Since he's paid such a huge price, it'd be best if we don't continue to fight with him." Mornisa agreed as well.

Sierron and the Mechanical Deity's attacks clashed a few more times before he backed away with a long face.

Although he was not willing to admit it, the explosive power Black Star was displaying now was more than enough to match up to him. They would not be able to do much to each other any time soon. The Mechanical Deity's energy consumption was terrifying, so normal Mechanics would not be able to make it last this long, but Black Star could keep it running for a very long time. This meant that even if the battle between the two of them came to an end, it would take a very long time.

The church's side seemingly intended to retreat as well, so if they remained there to fight Black Star, they would receive all the pressure.

Sierron was not afraid, but he could not fight in multiple areas like a Mechanic could, so he could not help his teammates.

The federation never planned to fight Black Star head-on. Since the plan to capture Hila alive had failed, continuing to fight would only be a waste of effort. Sierron made the decision instantly and said with a deep voice, "Retreat. Preheat the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device."

After he said that, he no longer continued fighting the Mechanical Deity and headed into the mechanical army. Using continuous Pugilist shockwaves, he created an empty area within the countless mechanical soldiers.

On the other side, Kasuyi stopped his act as well while helping his teammates to escape. His psychic energy swept all the mechanical army in his way to the side.

The escape routes of the two sides were different. The federation had brought their fleet along, so the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device was their way out. The church had a small team, so only the Beyond Grade As had to escape themselves. As soon as they left the area affected by the spacetime stabilization device, they would be able to escape with teleportation scrolls.

Han Xiao instantly noticed the shift in the targets' goals. Both sides were heading out of the mechanical army in two different directions.

The federation and the church both hoped that the other side would hold Black Star back, so of course, they would not be helping each other. There was also no way the church would take the federation's Uber, or they would basically be leaving the wolf's den just to enter the tiger's cave.

"Their alliance is broken."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. He controlled the Mechanical Deity and chased after the federation's people.

The mechanical army split in two, while the Apostle Weapons and Mysterious Energy Host left the church's Beyond Grade As behind and focused on the federation.

Gathering all the combatants to focus on one side would have a better effect. One reason he chose to chase after the federation was due to Kasuyi's favor, and another was because it would be too difficult to chase after the church.

If Kasuyi stopped acting, his ability to restrain him would be incomparable. If he headed to chase after the church's people, he would most likely not be able to capture anyone at all. Kasuyi was just a doppelganger, so he could totally secure his teammates' escape without having to worry about his own safety, and his psychic energy would be more than enough to stop his entire army for some time.

Comparatively, Sierron was just a Pugilist who was powerful as an individual but had very limited AOE skills. He was not good at protecting his teammates and was there as his main body, so he could not miss his ride. With these factors all adding up, the federation was clearly easier to deal with.

Once the target was decided, Han Xiao locked onto a federation Beyond Grade A and threw out an ability without hesitation.

[Virtual Paramount]!

'Lone Ranger' Jackornitz was using all kinds of mechanical weapons to fight the Apostle Weapons when his body suddenly became stiff, and his soul was trapped in the virtual world by Han Xiao. He had lost control of his body.

In such dire situations, even the slightest carelessness would be fatal, not to mention being defenseless for more than ten seconds.

As a Mechanical Pugilist, the defense of his physical body could not match a true Pugilist, nor did he have any True Damage Immunity talents. When the mechanical army and the Apostle Weapons swarmed toward him, his health plummeted.

Han Xiao had chosen him because he was paper according to his data from the Meeting of the Gods.

Swoosh!

The Mechanical Deity extended its arm and grabbed Jackornitz. It then absorbed him into its body.

When Jackornitz escaped from the control effect of Virtual Paramount and returned to his body, he instantly felt a strong sense of weakness. What he came back to was a body that was heavily wounded and completely controlled by the traps inside the Mechanical Deity, unable to move.

"Impossible…"

Jackornitz could not believe how quickly he had been defeated.

He would be able to last longer even against the Mechanic Emperor's army. He knew that Black Star was extremely tanky, but why was his damage output so high too‽

Han Xiao was not surprised. The damage output of his mechanical army was definitely not low.

Being a Molding Talent, [Legendary Battle Technique] could tear through any Beyond Grade As without a True Damage Immunity talent once his mechanical army could penetrate the shield and focus fire on the target. Even with how much health Beyond Grade As had, they would still not be able to handle this much damage.

Jackornitz was sent beside Han Xiao's main body inside the Mechanical Deity. Han Xiao turned and glanced at him. "You won't be able to run now that you're inside here. If you don't want to suffer more, don't resist."

As soon as his sentence ended, countless barrels extended from the interior walls of the Mechanical Deity and aimed at Jackornitz.

Under the mechanical helmet, Jackornitz could not help but smile bitterly.

Alright then, I couldn't beat Black Star to begin with, and now he's even sacrificing his potential for all this. I'd better accept my fate.

At the same time, the federation's Beyond Grade As outside witnessed the entire process, seeing Black Star easily capture Jackornitz like catching a newborn chick.

"Your Excellency Sierron, this…" Womre could not help but say.

"Leave him. We can't save him." Sierron's expression was gloomy. He was seething with anger.

Unlike Kasuyi, his main body was right there, so he could not afford to ignore his own safety. If he tried to save his teammate, he would not make it in time for the federation's teleportation. And when the dynasty's reinforcements arrived, he would probably be done for.

Therefore, no matter how furious he was, Sierron could only put up with it.

…

At the same time, the church's members who were fleeing from the mechanical army in another direction also saw this.

Initially, when Tolaen was captured, Sagman and the others were all quite unhappy. So, when they saw that the federation was suffering just as much, they felt much better.

Like a great man once said, when something unlucky happens to someone, the best way to comfort him is not to pity him but to make him see others just as unlucky as him.

This was exactly how the church was feeling.

This time, Kasuyi's eyes flickered slightly. He contemplated for a while but suddenly stopped and said, "You guys go first. I'm staying to do something."

"What are you going to do?" Sagman was curious.

Kasuyi turned to look in the federation's direction, smiled faintly, and said, "The federation has yet to return the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. This is a good chance to teach them a lesson and take some interest from them."

The others understood immediately. This was something only Kasuyi's doppelganger could do.

What Kasuyi wanted to do was restrain the federation's people and help Black Star capture even more Beyond Grade As of the federation.

He hoped that Black Star would capture more captives to vent his anger and get more compensation from the Universal Civilizations. Plus, it would be best for him not to sell out his teammates. Hence, the federation was the best target.

Furthermore, this was a very justifiable reason. He had been acting the whole time, but the church would still compliment him for doing a great job, while at the same time, it would cancel out the loss they suffered through failing the mission and having one of them be captured. It was killing multiple birds with one stone. This was clearly the move of an experienced actor.

Having thought of that, Kasuyi left Sagman and the others and headed right toward the federation's people. At the same time, he privately communicated with Han Xiao.

"Still remember the deal I suggested earlier? How about we work together?"

Han Xiao was chasing after the federation's people when he saw Kasuyi charging toward this battlefield. He was initially planning on trying to stop him, but when he heard this, even he was stunned and almost speechless. He had tons of things he could say, but he did not know what to say, so it all fused into one single sentence.

On behalf of the federation, I thank you!

With Kasuyi joining the battle, the situation changed instantly. Kasuyi's psychic energy swept past the members of the federation one after another. Having been hit by such powerful mind attacks, many of them trembled all over, allowing the mechanical army to create an even tighter encirclement around them. The speed of them pushing through the mechanical army suddenly slowed down.

Seeing this, Sierron was furious.

Kasuyi!

When I invited you to work together with me to fight Black Star, didn't you say you were out of energy, you piece of sh*t‽

You goddamn actor!

He did not expect the Arcane Church to play this dirty and help Black Star.

"Don't look at me like that." Kasuyi's tone was calm. "During the Planet Lighthouse battle, you also stabbed us in the back. The situation back then was so similar to now. I'm simply doing the same thing you lot did."

During the Planet Lighthouse battle, due to the federation, the church had been left in a passive situation. The federation had even killed one of their Beyond Grade As and taken the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter.

Hence, Kasuyi felt no guilt doing something like this.

Sierron's expression was raging. With a furious roar, he headed back. Highly condensed Pugilist flames appeared all around his body as he forced open a path. No mechanical soldier could stop him.

He blew away countless mechanical soldiers and made his way to Crystal Soul. He then grabbed him and turned around to leave instantly, not caring about his other teammates.

Sierron clearly knew that with Kasuyi helping Black Star, the federation would undoubtedly suffer a huge loss, so he could only take damage control measures.

Crystal Soul was a Crystal Life, so he was tiny. Plus, he had a Universal Treasure, so he was prioritized. Sierron brought Crystal Soul along and escaped right away. As for the others, there was nothing he could do.

Mornisa saw this and stopped fleeing. She controlled her mechanical army to secure the retreat instead. Although she could not match Han Xiao's army at all, it still more or less slowed down Han Xiao's mechanical army's speed.

This way, those facing the most pressure became Hades and Womre, who were left behind.

"Damn it…"

Hades was bleeding from his every orifice. He was also a Psychic, but he was completely powerless in front of Kasuyi. He could no longer maintain his cool, and his face was filled with resentment.

At this time, the Mechanical Deity's palm suddenly slammed down. Hades looked up. His vision was covered by this metal sky.

It had not been long since Hades became a Beyond Grade A, so he was not very clear about the strength levels of the Beyond Grade As. When he saw this, he only had one thought in his mind.

This is what true power looks like!

The next moment, he blacked out and lost all his senses as the mechanical palm landed on him.

"Third."

Han Xiao absorbed the unconscious Hades into the Mechanical Deity, then looked at Womre.

At this point, all the Apostle Weapons were attacking just Womre.

This Pugilist's style was different from Sierron and Gorutan. It did not look rough and powerful but very smooth and natural, like a martial arts master. Instead of melee combat, he seemed to be better at mid-ranged shockwave attacks. His Pugilist flames never stopped burning, as if they had no end.

The light-blue flames circled around him like a shield, continuously repelling the Apostle Weapons' attacks. His movements were neither fast nor slow. Every move he made launched a shockwave. Even in such a dire situation, Womre did not look like he was being overpowered. However, with no chance of turning the tables, his defeat was just a matter of time.

Seeing that Sierron and Crystal Soul were escaping further while he had no way out, he decided not to escape and stay there to secure their way out with Mornisa.

The Mechanical Deity waved its hands, shattering tons of enemy mechanical soldiers and the unmanned fleet of the federation, quickly destroying Mornisa's fragile Lord's Avatar.

Womre was left alone, and not long after, he was also captured alive due to the attacks of the Apostle Weapons, Mysterious Energy Host, and Hila.

Nonetheless, them staying there was not meaningless. Sierron and Crystal Soul had already escaped into the Federation of Light's fleet, and the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device's preheating was complete.

Hu!

Two enormous mechanical rings span at an extremely quick speed, faster and faster, till the afterimages formed a sphere that shrouded the area around the fleet.

Sierron turned back one last time, glared at Kasuyi, and then looked at Han Xiao.

"Black Star, you captured our people. The federation won't let this go easily! Just you wait!"

Buzz!

The speed of the two rings suddenly stopped, and the fleet inside the sphere area disappeared, leaving only the unmanned fleet and the mechanical army behind.

The next moment, the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device activated the self-destruction sequence and exploded.

As the federation's people left, the atmosphere became much quieter.

"Only two escaped on the federation's side." Han Xiao stopped. His eyes sparkled as he looked in another direction, where the few Beyond Grade As of the church had already fled.

This time, Kasuyi's voice sounded in his mind. "What, after capturing three federation Beyond Grade As and one church Beyond Grade A, are you still not satisfied?"

Han Xiao looked at Kasuyi and saw his calm expression.

"Thanks." Han Xiao deactivated the Mechanical Deity and nodded at Kasuyi.

Without Kasuyi's help, he would have captured three Beyond Grade As at most. He had managed to capture four and destroy two Mechanic avatars, meaning he basically defeated half of all the enemies.

The main reason he had achieved this was the Character Summon Cards he used, but other than that, Hila's help and the Spacetime Amber were also crucial factors. That was especially so for the Spacetime Amber, which blocked a ton of long-range attacks, so he could put more effort into attacking, at the same time discouraging everyone from rushing his main body. Furthermore, he also had to rely on it to seal Beyond Grade As. Basically, at least twenty to thirty percent of the battle merit belonged to the Spacetime Amber.

He had to say, Ravenlaude's should-be treasure was really very useful.

Although two of the four Beyond Grade As captures were newborn noobs and the other two were not particularly strong, they were still Beyond Grade As. They all had Molding Talents, so it all depended on Feidin this time.

All kinds of thoughts flashed through his mind. As Han Xiao saw that Kasuyi had been staring at him, he retrieved the mechanical army that was chasing after the church's people.

The spacetime stabilization device was already gone by this point, so he directly activated the secondary dimensional army box and stuffed his remaining mechanical army in. He then used Dimension Factory to collect the parts all over the place to do repairs.

While doing this, Han Xiao casually asked, "What are you going to do next, continue to escort the church's people out?"

"Hmm, when they arrive at a safe place with teleportation scrolls, I'll release this doppelganger. You won't chase after them anymore, will you?"

Kasuyi smiled faintly while sighing in his mind.

When was the last time anyone achieved something this incredible in this entire universe?

When the results of this battle spread, god knows how much of a sensation it will cause.

"I've promised you, so I won't go back on my word… By the way, let me show you something."

Han Xiao waved and called Hila over.

"Are you okay?" Hila stared at Han Xiao's face and did not bother looking at Kasuyi at all.

Although Kasuyi had come to help earlier, from the way she looked at it, the people of the church were still enemies. She did not know this was an Oscar-winning best actor.

"I'm fine." Han Xiao shook his head and said with a serious tone, "Ames is being attacked in Black Star Palace. Go back to help her and then send Silver Shadow over."

Hila was confused. "What do you mean? How am I going to go back to help her?"

"I have some new technology that can teleport you back."

Han Xiao's entire body started to glow. The King left his body with loud clanks and attached itself automatically onto Hila while still being connected to Han Xiao's Mechanical Force.

After many private tests, Han Xiao knew the mechanics of the King like the back of his hand. The King itself was a Mechanic-only equipment, and the teleportation function of the Throne was targeted at the user who was wearing the mechanical suit. However, if he maintained his Mechanical Force link to the King through the Quantum Infinite Distance Transmission Channel, even if someone else was in the mechanical suit, Han Xiao would still be able to activate this function and teleport the wearer of the mechanical suit to a fixed location.

The Throne was about to arrive at the Black Star Palace, so Hila would be teleported right back to his base.

Han Xiao turned around and realized that Kasuyi was looking at this with interest. Hence, he purposely activated a spacetime stabilization device to cover the area.

Then, Han Xiao snapped his fingers, and the King disappeared without a trace right under Kasuyi's nose.

Kasuyi's expression suddenly changed into shock. "This is… Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation? When did you learn the federation's technology?"

"It's not Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation. It's another technology, but the results are similar. It can also penetrate the restrictions of spacetime stabilization devices and disruptors," Han Xiao said calmly.

"Why didn't you use this earlier?" Kasuyi said with resignation. If we knew you had this technology before, why would we even come to attack Hila?

"I only recently obtained this technology." Han Xiao nodded. Looking at Kasuyi's expression, he knew that he had achieved his goal.

He deliberately showcased the teleportation ability of the King to let others know that he had this technology. Otherwise, if the federation and the church did not give up, they might attack Hila again in the future, and he could not possibly always keep Hila hidden.

Showing this trump card at this time would let the outside world know that Hila could escape anytime when attacked by enemies she could not win against. This way, the federation and the church would give up on this plan, and this incident would not repeat itself.

In that case, Hila would be in a much safer situation, and no one would want to target her.

Swoosh!

At this time, the King appeared once again. The mechanical suit opened, showing Silver Shadow, who was still lost.

"Hmm? Black Star? What is this place?"

Silver Shadow was still confused as to what was happening.

"Stop talking. I don't have much time, and I need to borrow your body. When I'm done, I'll let you use the Evolution Cube."

Han Xiao patted Silver Shadow's shoulders, dragged him away, and was about to leave.

Kasuyi was a little surprised.

"It's all over. Where are you going now?"

"It's not over for me yet. While my explosive powers are still here, I have another target I need to deal with."

"Who?" Kasuyi was curious.

Han Xiao turned his head sideways and said with a deep voice, "Beast Ancestor, Gorutan."

Chapter 1055: Silver Shadow Uber

A few minutes prior…

Evil Convergence had appeared outside Black Star Palace, gradually changing the properties of the space around while continuously expanding.

Within the affected area, the defense fleet continuously fired at the countless tentacles around, destroying one after another, only for more to appear again like they were endless.

According to some studies that supported the energy conservation theory of all energy in the universe, the conservation of energy operated between multiple dimensions. In many tests in galactic civilizations, there would be examples of energy suddenly disappearing or appearing out of nowhere, and most of those were caused by the energy shift between the main universe and other dimensions.

There were many ways a secondary dimension could be projected into the main universe. The method that Traveler used treated the secondary dimension like a bucket of water, and he opened a hole at the bottom of it to let the water inside flow into the main universe, causing corrosion.

Traveler did not put much effort into it; he only opened a hole. The rest came naturally from the secondary dimension itself and exceeded the capabilities of individual power. Therefore, this was extremely difficult to stop, and the fleet at Black Star Palace would not be able to solve this problem very soon.

In the middle of the battlefield, Ames was fighting intensely with Traveler. Powerful Force Fields clashed with the energy of Evil Convergence time after time, creating enormous aftershocks.

The Force Field Esper Ability was good with defense and controlling. Together with her Void Talents, despite Traveler having the upper hand, he could not penetrate Ames' defenses. However, Ames was not happy about it at all.

The Evil Convergence is his territory. He has infinite energy here and can make me use my energy without fear. Dragging the battle out isn't beneficial for me, Ames analyzed. She had to admit that Traveler was quite strong. He would be among the upper-middle tier even in the three Universal Civilizations.

Although she had also become stronger in the past twenty years, she was still not strong enough to fight someone this powerful alone.

"Your resistance is futile; your defeat is just a matter of time." With increased corrosion of the Evil Convergence, Traveler's aura became more and more evil.

Ames ignored him and focused on controlling the force field to deal with the purple-green energy tentacles everywhere.

In Black Star Palace's watchtower, the various officers had serious looks on their faces. With the defense measures of Black Star Palace, they were not worried about the damage the Traveler might cause. What they were worried about was how Ames did not look like she was in a good situation. They kept commanding more fleets to join the battle to provide support.

Silver Shadow had a poker face but was very tempted deep down. Although the Black Star Army's officers did not ask him for help, seeing that Ames was at a disadvantage, he felt that it was time for him to put on a show.

At this moment, a few spaceships with the Black Star Army's symbol appeared from afar and approached.

"Have these transport ships steer away from the battlefield and return from another direction," Herlous said.

These returning spaceships had been marked as transport ships long ago. Everyone's attention was focused on the battlefield at the moment and did not bother with the transport ships. They only glanced at them and went back to watching the battle between Ames and Traveler.

However, the next moment, an alarm rang on the radar!

"Alert! Alert! Beyond Grade A energy source detected!"

"What‽"

The various officers present were shocked. They quickly looked at the radar and realized that the energy source was in the transport ships.

"Another enem…"

They were instantly nervous.

However, before they could respond, what happened next stunned all the officers.

Buzz!

The familiar death energy gushed out from the transport ship like a tsunami. Hila stepped on the tide and quickly approached Black Star Palace.

"Deputy Army Commander Hila!"

"Sis‽"

They were stunned, and Aurora was even stupefied.

Aren't you at the frontlines? How did you suddenly appear here?

If not because of the mind link, Aurora might have thought that this Hila was a fake.

However, the most stunned person was Traveler. When he saw this, the maddened laugh he had on his face stiffened instantly.

What the hell, why is Hila here‽

His mission was to divert Black Star's attention and help those who were attacking Hila to restrain Black Star… But since Hila was there, what were those people attacking? Air?

What am I even trying to restrain here‽

He could not figure out what was going on at all, so in the end, he blamed it all on Sorokin…

What a scam! Giving me false information!

Since Hila had appeared there, there was no point continuing the mission. He did not want to continue fighting the Black Star Army.

Traveler decisively gave up on attacking Ames and instantly fled. Of course, Ames was not going to let him leave easily. Her focus shifted from defense to attack instantly.

Hila glared at Traveler but did not instantly join the battle.

She remembered Han Xiao's words and quickly entered the watchtower. She had no time to talk to the confused officers and headed right to Silver Shadow.

"Wear this mechanical suit. Black Star wants to see you."

"Huh?" Silver Shadow was at a loss.

"No time to explain, get in."

Hila deactivated the King, and it automatically attached itself onto Silver Shadow.

The next moment, Silver Shadow disappeared without a trace.

After this was completed, Hila finally had the time to take a deep breath.

The officers around approached her immediately.

"Why are you here? Where's His Excellency Black Star?" Hadavy asked.

When this matter was brought up, Hila felt a pain in her heart, and her expression sank.

The impression she gave to the army officers had always been cold, proud, and powerful. Therefore, when she looked this hurt, the officers were all shocked and started guessing with a pessimistic mindset.

Did… something horrible happen to their commander‽

"Sis…" Aurora noticed Hila's sorrowful emotions and held her hand with a worried look on her face.

"I owe him… too much." Hila closed her eyes and clenched her teeth as if she was talking to herself. "How can I ever pay you back for what you've done for me?"

…

At this time, Han Xiao led Silver Shadow away from the wrecked frontline stronghold. The players and the other warriors would take care of cleaning up the battlefield. He wanted to make some trouble for Gorutan while the effects of the Character Summon Cards still lasted.

Hila was attacked, and the information had come from Gorutan. Although, given how unique Hila's ability was, she would have experienced this sooner or later, this did not mean that Han Xiao would let Gorutan off easy.

On the way to Gorutan's territory, Han Xiao gave Silver Shadow his request…

"You want to use my body?"

Silver Shadow's face was filled with dismay.

He could not understand the King's effects, nor did he dare ask. He was originally confused as to why he had been summoned there by Black Star. Now, when he heard what Han Xiao said, he panicked completely.

So, this is the kind of person you really are, Black Star! My body is what you wanted!

"That's what I meant, but I feel like you've misunderstood something," Han Xiao said with resignation. "I just want you to help me. Treat it as a deal to use the Evolution Cube."

"You startled me. I thought you wanted to capture me and make me a special weapon like the Mechanic Emperor does." Silver Shadow was relieved.

"Oh, that's not entirely wrong." Han Xiao coughed, changed the topic, and said seriously, "Your body has a hidden characteristic. When you awaken it, you can turn yourself into a special Universal Treasure. This is exactly what I need you to do, to transform and help me."

"How do you know that?" Silver Shadow was curious. Even he did not know about that himself, so how did someone else know more about his own body than him?

"Remember the first time we met? When we sparred, I controlled your body and did a detailed scan. Back then, I noticed that there's a secret hidden in your body. You might have undergone some kind of mutation when turning into a Beyond Grade A." Han Xiao started to use his talent for deception without breaking a sweat.

The truth was, he had poked Silver Shadow long ago and seen his attributes, which already had the ability to become a Universal Treasure inside.

However, normal people did not have the interface, so they could not know all their own abilities like the players, and Silver Shadow was one such example. He did not know that he had such an ability.

In a situation like this, as long as he guided him to make him notice this hidden ability, he might be able to use it straight away.

"Alright then, what should I do?" Silver Shadow barely accepted this explanation.

"Try to sense while thinking about it?"

Han Xiao did not have an exact method. In the past, Silver Shadow did not think about anything related to this at all, but now that he made him realize that, he might be able to awaken this ability instantly.

Doubtful, Silver Shadow held on to the thought of transforming into a Universal Treasure and controlled his body to slowly change shape.

His silver body quickly turned into a pile of liquid metal that constantly changed shape as he looked for the right feeling.

After some time, the pile of liquid metal suddenly gave off a strange energy. Silver Shadow actively crawled up Han Xiao's body. The silver liquid metal shrouded Han Xiao's entire body and turned him into a silver man.

"I really do have this ability!" Silver Shadow was shocked by himself.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. He looked at the notification on the interface and smiled with satisfaction.

"Didn't I tell you? You did have hidden potential."

The interface was showing that Silver Shadow had already turned into Universal Treasure grade equipment and he was wearing it, which allowed him to share Silver Shadow's incredible defense and speed, while at the same time giving him quite a few new abilities.

Furthermore, wearing Silver Shadow felt very comfortable, like sitting inside a luxurious car.

On the other side, experiencing this new feeling, Silver Shadow made a decision.

He had to become closer to Black Star. This guy easily saw his potential, which he did not even see himself. If he could get Black Star to help him explore the mysteries of his body, his growth would definitely be much quicker.

Having found his hidden potential, Silver Shadow was very content. He did not mind lending his body to Han Xiao and letting him control it as he wanted.

The two of them practiced for a while. Han Xiao gradually familiarized himself with the controls of this luxurious car, and he loved it.

"Let's go!"

Then, he dashed right forward.

Bang!

Silver Shadow's speed up ability erupted. Han Xiao speed increased as if it had no limits as he turned into a silver meteor and disappeared into cosmic space.

…

Somewhere in the Star Cluster, a teleportation gate formed in the cosmic space and spat out three people.

"Hu, we've finally escaped."

Sagman's tense body finally relaxed. He looked toward the battlefield with a complicated expression.

Black Star's explosive strength was really scary. If I ran only a little slower, I would have been captured…

They could not help but be glad that Black Star had chased after the federation instead of them.

He turned around and exchanged looks with Taylor and Mercer. The three of them had the same thought.

That was close to being captured a second time.

"His Excellency Kasuyi is so wise. He turned around to help Black Star deal with the federation, which not only restrained Black Star but also caused more damage to the federation. Although the mission failed, His Excellency Kasuyi definitely made a huge contribution," Taylor said.

Every time they thought of how tragic the result was for the federation, the three of them felt joy in their hearts and more respect for Kasuyi's wise decision.

"But… Tolaen has been captured by Black Star too, which is a problem." Sagman shook his head.

"Hehe, that's nothing. He'll just suffer a little. When he's released, we'll have something else to talk about."

"Haha, you're right."

Although they had lost a teammate, the three of them did not mind it too much. The atmosphere was lively and uplifting.

However, on the federation's side, it was the complete opposite.

After the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device brought the federation's fleet back to their territory, the upper echelon who was waiting at the location to receive Hila was stunned to see the state of the returning team.

"Six Beyond Grade As left, but only two of you returned‽"

Hearing the outraged question from the upper echelon, Sierron was extremely ashamed.

If he had fought Black Star head-on without considering the consequences, he was certain that he could have matched up to Black Star even in that state. Sadly, Pugilists were like sharp blades. All their strength was condensed in their bodies, so protecting his teammates was something he really was not good at.

Thinking of the fact that so many Beyond Grade A teammates had been lost under his lead, Sierron was trembling with rage.

This is beyond embarrassing!

Manison will surely laugh about this!

The upper echelons will definitely feel that my ability to lead a team is much weaker than Manison's, so they will have to rely more on him…

And that *sshole Kasuyi. If not for him, the federation would not have suffered this much of a loss.

Sierron clenched his teeth.

Kasuyi, just you wait. Manison will certainly come for you!

…

Near a certain stargate station in the Emerald Star Cluster, a fleet was fighting a mechanical army. The most conspicuous thing on the battlefield was a silhouette that was covered in dark brown Pugilist flames. It was 'Beast Ancestor' Gorutan.

His opponents were more than a dozen Apostle Weapons of the Mechanic Emperor that had various appearances and were quite powerful. When working together, they were able to stall Gorutan.

Ever since Gorutan came to rescue his fleet, the two sides had been embroiled in a bitter fight.

"Mechanic Emperor, there's no point trying to stop me!" Gorutan said while fighting with the Apostle Weapons. "Black Star's frontline stronghold was attacked. Hila might already be dead. Even if you don't let me destroy the target stations, the dynasty's reinforcements won't make it in time. Hila's death is certain."

At this point, he still did not know what had happened, and his impression of the situation there remained at when Sorokin told him Hila was in a dire situation.

Destroying the surrounding stargate stations felt unnecessary to him. He still did not think Hila would have any chance of getting through this disaster.

Manison did not respond at all. The Apostle Weapon simply did their job and fought Gorutan.

Seeing that Manison did not respond, Gorutan was even more irritated. "Are you going to let my men go or not‽"

Again, Manison did not respond.

"You really don't know when to give up, do you? Just wait, the news of Hila being killed will get here very quickly. By then, you'll know that everything you're doing now is meaningless." Gorutan was extremely annoyed.

Manison still did not respond, but he quietly blocked all information sent to Gorutan from the outside world using his virtual technology.

It was not that no one had told Gorutan what happened, but he could not receive any messages from the outside world!

The abilities of a Virtual Mechanic were extremely difficult to notice, so Gorutan had no idea at all. He was still submerged in the joy of having successfully gotten revenge.

Manison ignoring Gorutan made him clench his teeth. Just as he was about to say something, he suddenly had a feeling. He looked into the distance with a confused expression.

A silver meteor entered his sights at an unbelievable speed and quickly approached!

A strange sense of danger appeared in Gorutan's mind.

Chapter 1056: The Root

"Such powerful energy, what is that? It seems to be coming for me?" Gorutan was shocked.

This silver meteor clearly did not come with friendly intentions.

Gorutan's expression changed slightly. He did not want to allow this strange object to get close to him. While dealing with the Mechanic Emperor's mechanical army, he was able to send a dark brown Shockwave Blast toward the silver meteor.

However, this silver meteor dodged the shockwave easily using its speed advantage like a race car with a professional driver.

Seeing that ranged attacks did nothing to this silver meteor and that it was still locked onto him, Gorutan suddenly released energy around him, blowing the Apostle Weapons around him away. He then compressed his Pugilist flames to increase his strength and charged toward that silver meteor.

Two meteors with different colors got closer at an extremely high speed, colliding.

In that instant, the radars on all the Beast Ancestor's spaceships reacted to it, showing that the energy impact had exceeded the peak!

At the location where these two clashed, a blinding light appeared like a flickering sun.

The thick, dark-brown Pugilist flames suddenly exploded like a rock that was shattered by a hammer.

Gorutan's body then flew out, spinning like a gyroscope. The blood he spat out was evaporated by the energy aftershock created from the clash.

The moment of the clash, Gorutan's mind seemed to have stopped working for an instant. All he could feel was a blinding light, and when he regained focus, he realized that his body was being pushed out uncontrollably.

Ever since he became a peak Beyond Grade A, he had rarely come across anything that he could not stop. However, the terrifying kinetic in this silver meteor made him feel as if he was an ordinary man trying to stop a train.

Pugilists were used to enduring direct hits, but the power of this clash still exceeded Gorutan's expectations. He could feel every nerve in his body trembling and sending the signal of pain to his brain. He was appalled.

Such terrifying strength!

"Who is this guy‽"

Gorutan had no idea. After flying quite far, he finally stabilized himself and quickly checked his condition. He realized that this clash had dealt him some damage, which made him very serious and cautious.

As he looked over and finally saw the appearance of the silver meteor after it stopped, his expression changed drastically.

"Black Star‽"

After ramming Gorutan away, Han Xiao had stepped on the breaks and told Silver Shadow to open the car windows to show his handsome face. He was coldly looking at Gorutan's astounded expression.

"We meet again, Beast Ancestor."

"How can you be here? Aren't you in Black Star Palace?"

All kinds of possibilities flashed through Gorutan's mind. Could it be that something happened to the mission targeting Hila?

Seeing Han Xiao's strange silver shell, Gorutan was filled with questions. The progress of the matter seemed to have deviated from his expectations. He was dying to know what had actually happened.

What's Sorokin doing? Why has he still not notified me of what happened?

"I know what you've done," Han Xiao said slowly. "Hila is safe now, and your plan has failed. Stop fantasizing about it."

Gorutan frowned.

Although he had no idea how Hila had managed to survive, Black Star had no need to lie to him about something like this. Plus, seeing how calm Black Star was, he knew that this was most likely true.

Gorutan instantly became unhappy. Knowing that Hila was not dead, he was disappointed.

"So, you came just for me?"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. "Back then, you provoked us to start a fight. Then after you realized your life span was reduced, you leaked this information to the federation and the church, hoping to borrow their power to aid in your goal. Now that this is exposed… you know what's going to happen, don't you?"

Gorutan frowned.

His secret plan did not succeed, and now he had been completely exposed. Even though he saw Han Xiao as an enemy, he still felt embarrassed.

Gorutan was not one to explain. Since the enemy had found out, he did not plan to hide it any longer. He suppressed his emotions and snorted. "What, have you come to make me pay?"

"Like I said, if you want to play, I'll play with you all you like. You don't look like someone who doesn't have the balls to play, so there's only one way to solve this problem, and I'm sure you know what it is." Han Xiao's tone was calm.

"Humph, so it still ends up being a conversation with fists."

Gorutan knew that a fight was unavoidable, and flames appeared once again on his body.

In the end, conspiracies and plots just aren't my thing as I expected. Fighting enemies head-on is still the best.

Although he had taken some damage earlier, Gorutan was not afraid at all. They were both peak Beyond Grade As. They all hand trump cards, so there was no reason for him to be scared.

He took a deep breath and used his energy to enhance the production of cells, quickly healing his wounds. Pugilists had extreme control over their bodies, and when they reached the peak Beyond Grade A level, their regenerative ability could not possibly be horrible.

"I did not fight you last time. Today, I can make up for it. What you've done has spread throughout the universe. Now, show me what you're really capable of." Gorutan's eyes were glowing as he spoke in a tone that was overflowing with his will to battle.

He still did not know about how Hila was rescued and had no idea of what Han Xiao had just been able to achieve, so his impression of Han Xiao remained as Han Xiao's strength in the past.

This time, Gorutan suddenly recalled Manison, who was at the side, and his heart sank a little.

Gorutan was not afraid if the enemy was just Black Star, but if the Mechanic Emperor participated too, it would not be good for him at all.

He uncontrollably looked over and was glad to see that Manison's troops were retreating, clearly expressing he had no intention to interfere with this battle.

Han Xiao also looked at the Mechanic Emperor's army that was gradually leaving and murmured in his mind, "This Manison sent me Gorutan's coordinates but didn't pick up my call. Is he trying to show a friendly gesture while at the same time letting me deal with Gorutan for him so that he can remain uninvolved in all this?"

Han Xiao shook his head. It did not matter what Director Manison planned to do. He had to fight this battle. There was no way he would let the root cause of all this off easy.

The effects of the Character Summon Cards could still last for quite some time, so he should be able to deal with Gorutan in his current state.

Swoosh!

As the secondary dimensional army box opened, the sea-like mechanical army swarmed out.

Gorutan was fearless as he charged into the endless mechanical army.

As soon as the battle started and the overwhelming pressure came, Gorutan immediately felt that something was wrong.

"Wait, why is your army…"

Gorutan's eyes opened wide with surprise.

He had once felt Black Star's energy level personally and had a rough estimate of Han Xiao's strength. Now, however, the actual strength Han Xiao was displaying far exceeded his estimate and shocked him.

How can this be? How has Black Star become this much stronger in just one or two months‽

At this time, Han Xiao's main body advanced instead of backing off and went into melee combat range.

Fists clashed with each other, and a powerful force was transmitted through Gorutan's arm. Feeling the energy that was almost as strong as his, Gorutan was even more shocked.

"Why is your strength also…"

"You have too many questions!"

Han Xiao's movements were so fast, as if he had become a phantom. While Gorutan was shocked, he whipped his leg and kicked Gorutan, sending him flying.

Just as riders could become stronger using their horses, Han Xiao also received attribute bonuses while riding Silver Shadow.

Silver Shadow was a Pugilist, so both his Strength and Dexterity were high. He also had a special defensive advantage.

Boundless power came from Silver Shadow's body. Han Xiao's main body temporarily received attribute bonuses that were comparable to a Pugilist. In addition to his own attributes, his melee combat capabilities were dramatically enhanced. Although still not as strong as a peak Beyond Grade A Pugilist, it was more than enough.

In his previous life, Pugilists like Karlot became much stronger when using Silver Shadow, while he used Silver Shadow to enhance his speed and defenses. Melee-range combat was not the main damage method of his main body.

…

At the same time, the dynasty's reinforcement fleet flew out from a stargate station at another location.

"We've finally arrived near Black Star's stronghold. We have to hurry. Every second we waste puts Hila's life in more danger. " Ravenlaude hurried the others.

This time, Kant closed his eyes as if he had received a message. He then opened his eyes with a strange expression and said, "We don't have to hurry there anymore. Black Star has solved the problem."

Hearing this, Ravenlaude was stunned.

"Impossible, how did he solve such a dangerous situation?"

"There. This is the intelligence the Black Star Army sent." Kant displayed the information he had received, which recorded the battle process.

After finishing looking at the intelligence, Beyoni was filled with shock.

"To think that Black Star actually had such a powerful trump card that allowed him to fight more than ten Beyond Grade As at once. It's unbelievable!"

"It's mainly because the federation and the church had no choice but to escape while dragging each other back, which gave Black Star an opportunity to defeat them one by one… Nonetheless, this achievement is indeed way too horrifying."

Kant sighed. "But burning his potential is not worth it for someone like him with such a bright future. This will definitely affect his growth. Alas… the dynasty will compensate Black Star for the loss he has suffered this time."

This time, Beyoni was reminded of the joke Kant made earlier.

On the way, Kant had said that he would be able to fight all the enemies alone. That was supposedly a joke, but Black Star had done just that.

"Incredible…" Beyoni respected Black Star from the bottom of his heart.

On the other side, when Ravenlaude saw this news, his entire body stiffened.

He initially wanted to turn the tables when he arrived and make Black Star owe him a favor, but to his absolute shock, Black Star solved an almost certainly lethal situation like this all by himself.

Doesn't this mean I've wasted another trip and got nothing for it?

Ravenlaude lost all motivation instantly. All he wanted to do was turn into a slime and cower in the corner till the end of the world.

"Since the matter is already solved, what should we do now? Shall we go take a look at Black Star's stronghold or return right away?" Kohler asked.

Kant shook his head. "Neither. Black Star seems to be fighting Gorutan now. Since we're here, let's go and see if we can be of any use."

…

Inside Beast Ancestor's stronghold palace, Sorokin's manifestation held a communicator in his hands and walked back and forth while mumbling.

"Weird, weird, why hasn't Gorutan replied to my messages? Did something happen?"

Sorokin suddenly had a bad feeling about Gorutan's situation.

Chapter 1057: A VIP

Boom!

As silver and dark brown fists clashed, shockwaves exploded. Gorutan was once again blown away by Han Xiao's [Charge—Endless Potential].

Han Xiao did not use his Mechanical Deity but his main body to fight in melee range instead. Once his [Charge—Endless Potential] was off cooldown, he would back away and farm the distance traveled for the next powerful attack.

Despite trying to stop him, Gorutan was still held back by the formidable mechanical army.

Without the restriction of the spacetime stabilization anchors, Han Xiao's soldiers continuously swarmed out from his secondary dimensional army box and Dimension Factory. Currently, the mechanical army's main task was to restrain and damage the enemies.

The combat capability of a peak Beyond Grade A Pugilist was exceptional, so Gorutan did not have too hard a time being surrounded. Nonetheless, he was quite troubled by the mechanical army. Not to mention the fact that there was someone on the side who came charging at him every once in a while.

In the chaotic encirclement, everywhere Gorutan went, tons and tons of mechanical soldiers were destroyed.

Feeling the pain of his muscles healing from the wounds suffered earlier, Gorutan was irritated.

Originally, closing the distance was the best strategy for a Pugilist when fighting a Mechanic, but in this situation, he did not even want Han Xiao to get close to him. The [Charge—Endless Potential] was way too annoying for him. It caused him to be unable to control the tempo of the battle.

Every time he saw Han Xiao lurking around on the side, Gorutan would uncontrollably yell in his mind, Don't come any closer!

On the other side, despite having a slight advantage, Han Xiao's situation was not too optimistic.

A Pugilist's way of fighting was not flashy; it was pure and direct. However, when they reached the peak Beyond Grade A level, this pureness would transform and make their body indestructible.

"My tankiness is at the top among Mechanics, which is mainly thanks to my strong regenerative ability. Nonetheless, I can't underestimate the regenerative ability of a peak Beyond Grade A Pugilist. Plus, his health is even higher than mine."

Pugilists had a ton of talents that gave them Endurance. Their own class gave them more bonuses as well. At the peak Beyond Grade A level, no class could compete with Pugilists in terms of sheer health. Even Han Xiao and Milizaus were no exception. Furthermore, peak Beyond Grade A Pugilists might also have overpowered regenerative abilities like his. They were the true official tank warriors.

Before this, Sierron had to fight while running, and he was burdened by his teammates. This was Han Xiao's first time fighting a peak Beyond Grade A Pugilist toe to toe. Even though he was at his peak, defeating Gorutan as easily as defeating normal Beyond Grade A Pugilists was absolutely impossible.

The two of them fought intensely, while far away, Beast Ancestor's fleet was hesitating.

"Father is fighting. Should we help?"

Inside the bridge of the command ship, the crew's eyes all focused on one of the Calamity Grade officers.

This person was one of the direct offspring of Gorutan, the captain of this fleet. His name was Byram.

"That's a battle of Beyond Grade As. It's not suitable for us to interfere, I think," Byram said hesitantly.

"Black Star is here for revenge. It's not a one-on-one spar. The battle is looking tough for father. We shouldn't just watch him get beaten up," another Calamity Grade officer said.

"But we won't be of much use in battles like this. Just the aftershocks of their battle will cost us huge losses." Byram frowned.

"We would at least be of some help. Every little helps. Father might need us."

Byram turned to look at him. As he expected, he saw burning passion in this person's eyes.

Naturally, not all of Gorutan's children agreed with his way of raising his offspring, and their faction was not completely united. Although Gorutan was their father, they had many different mothers, which led to the internal structure of the faction being unstable.

The stand Gorutan's children had could be classified into three types. Byram was neutral; all he did was follow the rules and orders. He called Gorutan father, but he did not have much, if any, sense of belonging to the faction. The officer who kept persuading him to interfere with the battle was one of the loyal ones.

While Byram thought about what to do, a huge fleet arrived from afar. Their exterior armor had the symbol of Beast Ancestor. This was the fleet that had come from the stronghold to back up Beast Ancestor after realizing that something was wrong.

"Finally." Byram was relieved.

The two sides quickly gathered, and the various officers met.

Since the reinforcements had already arrived, Byram could no longer just watch on the side. He shook his head and said, "Now, we have enough strength to interfere with this battle. Our goal won't be to destroy the mechanical troops, just hold back some of them to reduce the pressure on father. Let's go."

The fleet split up and gradually approached the battlefield.

Han Xiao noticed this as well. He glanced at the fleet and frowned.

During the exploration era, Beyond Grade As getting killed by fleets was nothing new. Even though Beyond Grade As were extremely strong, they could not completely ignore large fleets. If Beast Ancestor's troops stepped into this battle, it would indeed cause some trouble for him.

Although he was a Virtual Mechanic, he still had to gradually hack the enemies, which meant that his focus would be diverted. At the same time, he would also have to send some of his mechanical armies to fight the fleet, so Gorutan would immediately face much less pressure. It would not be a problem if it was just an ordinary enemy, but Gorutan was the same Grade as him, so any tiny change in the situation would be enlarged and made use of.

Most of the fleet from Black Star's stronghold was still cleaning the battlefield, and Han Xiao had given an order for them to send part of the fleet there to back him up when he left to go to Gorutan. However, Silver Shadow was too fast; the others were left behind and were still on their way.

Suddenly, magic energy appeared out of nowhere.

Buzz!

As Beast Ancestor's fleet was about to interfere, an enormous teleportation gate suddenly appeared, followed by a stream of battleships with the dynasty's symbol, stopping Beast Ancestor's fleet in its path.

"The dynasty's people are finally here." Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Although the dynasty could not make it to rescue Hila, they ended up being useful now. Better late than never.

Very soon, the reinforcements of the dynasty had all arrived. Ravenlaude was the last to fly out of the teleportation gate. He swung his staff and deactivated this huge teleportation spell.

Having seen the situation, Kant smiled.

"Looks like we've arrived just in time."

This accident was a surprise for Han Xiao but a shock to the Beast Ancestor's subordinates.

"Stop immediately!"

Numerous Beyond Grade A energy sources appeared on the radar of the spaceships. Byram was horrified and quickly told his fleet to stop, not daring to continue advancing. The fleet stopped against the dynasty's fleet. He became hesitant again.

Kant and the others did not care about Beast Ancestor's fleet. They all turned to look at the battlefield. Seeing the strength Han Xiao was displaying, they were all appalled.

"Black Star during his explosive state is on a much higher level compared to his usual state," Kohler said with a sigh. "Sadly, the price of such power is too huge."

Kant contacted Han Xiao, smiled, and asked, "How is it? Do you need help?"

"Not letting him escape will do," Han Xiao replied very soon.

This was a private matter, as well as a rare opportunity for him to build a reputation, so Han Xiao planned to fight Gorutan alone. Since the dynasty's allies had arrived, they could prevent others from interfering and create an undisturbed one-on-one battle, as well as prevent Gorutan from escaping.

"Since you don't need us to interfere, we will respect your wishes."

Kant had no problem with this decision. Following Han Xiao's request, he ordered the fleet to split up and form an encirclement.

Seeing that he was surrounded by enemies, Gorutan's expression turned grave—he knew there was no backing away now.

Did he regret it… a little bit.

However, he did not dwell on it. What was done was done; he was not going to think about the 'what if's.

There was no point in overthinking anything. Gorutan just continued to launch even more powerful attacks, using all his strength without holding back.

"Let me see all you've got, Black Star!"

At the same time, Byram's fleet on the side did not dare attack the dynasty's fleet. They could only watch while the dynasty set up the encirclement right under their noses and do nothing as their boss got beaten up and surrounded.

Seeing the dynasty's stand on this matter, the various officers including Byram all felt uneasy. They had a feeling that the person they depended on might collapse.

"Father has nowhere to run. The dynasty has made up their mind on capturing him."

"We can't watch father get captured by the dynasty!"

"But how can we help? There are many dynasty Beyond Grade As here. Us going in is just suicide."

"Is there even a way to solve this situation? Who can help us? Can the protectors of the Galactic Black Market help?"

"Impossible. They're definitely not looking to interfere in something this big."

As a protector of the Galactic Black Market, Gorutan had to rely on himself, and now he was alone. In situations like this, there was not going to be anyone like the Beyond Grade A allies of the three Universal Civilizations appearing to help him.

The same thought hit all of them, including Byram, simultaneously.

We're done for…

Having realized this possibility, some of the officers and the crew started to have other thoughts.

Other than the loyal ones and the neutral ones, the rest were the rebels… Some of the offspring of Beast Ancestor hated their identity and their 'father' Gorutan. They felt that they were offspring on paper but actually just slaves. They had always been following the Beast Ancestor's orders on the surface but would be more than glad to see Beast Ancestor killed in their hearts.

Seeing that Gorutan was now facing the revenge of such a powerful enemy, these people were overjoyed. The ambition in their hearts kept expanding.

A teleportation gate suddenly appeared in a rural area of the Flickering World, and Traveler stepped out from it.

"I've finally got out." Traveler heaved a sigh of relief. He was quite wounded.

He had flown for a very long time till he finally got out of the range of the Black Star's fleet's stabilization anchor. On the way, he had been chased by Ames and Hila and was heavily wounded. Luckily, in the end, he escaped Black Star's territory through teleportation.

Traveler took out his communicator and contacted the person in charge of the Super Star Cluster alliance.

"The developments of the situation have deviated from the plan. Hila somehow returned to the Black Star Palace. Our plan has failed."

"We expected that. Black Star burned his potential in exchange for astonishing strength. Not only did he force the troops of the federation and the church to retreat, he even captured many Beyond Grade As. This message has yet to spread to the outside world; only high-level organizations know about it now. Your Excellency Traveler, it's fine as long as you're okay."

"I see…" Traveler shook his head. As he retrieved the Evil Convergence, the evil vibe he gave disappeared, and he became easy to look past again. "I've already offended the Black Star Army, so I'm going to make a trip to the secondary dimension and won't be appearing in the main universe for a very long time. Don't call me to do things for now."

"Understood. Since we could not start another conflict between the three Universal Civilizations, we won't step foot in things like this for the time being and will slowly gather our strength for the next big move."

"Humph. Black Star doesn't know my identity yet. He'll just be unhappy about me at most. You guys won't be affected. As long as I disappear, he'll stop caring. By the way, Sorokin thought I was hired, so he might notice something. That guy is suspicious. Pay more attention to him."

"Understood."

Traveler said a few words before hanging up and sighed.

I wonder how many years I'll have to spend hiding in the secondary dimension this time…

He silently looked at this universe one last time before casting a spell and stepping into the secondary dimension, disappearing without a trace.

Time passed quickly.

The two people fought for a very long time, and before a large audience, the situation finally came to an end.

Tons of mechanical troops were damaged and became many Grades lower. Three Apostle Weapons were completely scrapped, and four Apostle Weapons were unable to fight for the time being. The Mechanical Deity got shattered once, and Silver Shadow's health fell below the danger line… After paying a huge price, Han Xiao was finally able to push Gorutan to his limits.

Although peak Beyond Grade A Pugilists recovered energy very quickly, they did not have close to infinite energy like Kasuyi.

Looking over the battlefield, it was filled with machinery debris. The Dimension Factory was still tirelessly recycling it all.

In the middle of the battlefield, Gorutan was covered in wounds that were healing much slower than before and still spraying blood. His face was filled with exhaustion.

"You've lost. Anything you want to say?"

Han Xiao faced him, opened the helmet of the mechanical suit, and stared at him.

Although part of this was thanks to the fact that he was in an explosive state, this was still the first time he had defeated a peak Beyond Grade A alone.

"Ahem… a loss is a loss. There's nothing to say." Gorutan grinned, showing his teeth that were dyed red with blood. "What, you thought I would beg for mercy?"

"There's always a price to pay when messing with someone. Since you decided to do that, you should have thought of the possibility of this happening.

"Humph, no need to say such nonsense to me. I knew what I was in for. At least I forced you to burn your potential. Your growth limit is now forever reduced, and you will never recover from it."

Han Xiao shook his head but was laughing in his mind.

Even if he explained it, Gorutan would not believe it. Plus, he was not planning to explain it to anyone.

He paused, changed the topic, and slowly said, "You provoked me back then. If you'd taken a step back, today would not have happened. Compared to the life span you lost, you're going to lose much more now."

"If I did, that wouldn't be me," Gorutan said with a deep voice. "If I can't do whatever I want, what's the point of becoming so strong?"

Some chased after strength itself, while some chased after what came with it. Every Beyond Grade A was the former. They only became the latter afterward.

Not only Beyond Grade As, this was also the same for all Supers.

"No matter what, I shall have your body with a smile." Han Xiao raised his hand and pressed on Gorutan's chest.

"Humph, take it then. Don't ever let me find the chance to turn the tables."

Gorutan stood with a straight back, unafraid.

Begging for mercy was the act of a loser, but he was mentally prepared long ago. Even with this loss, he still remained graceful.

The next moment, this expression was fixed, and the spraying blood stopped moving.

'Beast Ancestor' Gorutan was sealed in Spacetime Amber!

Chapter 1058: Dust Settled

"Hu… Finally caught this guy."

Gorutan, who was covered in wounds and sealed in the Spacetime Amber, looked like he was made into a specimen.

Looking at the fixed expression on his face, Han Xiao finally relaxed.

A peak Beyond Grade A fighting for his life had almost endless trump cards. If not because of his Spacetime Amber, the King, Silver Shadow, and his double Mechanical Senses, he might not have been able to beat him.

After all, this time, he did not have a perfect trump card like the Esper Silence he had when facing EsGod, so the only choice was to fight head-on. Therefore, his mechanical army suffering huge losses was unavoidable. A huge number of mechanical soldiers had to be sent to the factory to be remade.

Both sides were peak tanks. There was no situation where one attack would decide the results. The battle was basically countless repetitions of the same process, and whoever lasted longest would win.

If not because the dynasty's allies were on the side, this would have definitely turned into a chase, which would have lasted much longer, and Gorutan might even have escaped. Nonetheless, the result of capturing Gorutan was ideal.

"The goals have been achieved. Hila is protected, and the King's functions have been showcased, which is more than enough to discourage others from thinking about attacking Hila. Even Gorutan is captured. The results of this event are going to be very beneficial for me."

Venting his anger was just one reason he had gone to fight Gorutan head-on. The main reason was to express his firm stance and instill fear in others.

Due to how strong an impression he made as a very sociable and friendly person, plus the fact that he had kept a low profile for more than two decades, there were always people trying to test him, thinking that he was easy to mess with.

This time, he did not depend too much on the dynasty. It was basically his own achievement. Since he had done this, it was certain that the other organizations would have to think twice before trying to mess with him in the future, weighing up whether it would even be worth it.

The only problem was, this achievement was too terrifying, almost unbelievable.

Although the church and the federation's people were not fighting for their lives and could not go all out due to many reasons, which gave him the opportunity to make full use of this flaw, the outside world would not care about all that. All they would see would be his achievement of fighting against twelve enemies all by himself. In front of this achievement, even capturing another peak Beyond Grade A was not as shocking.

This was more than enough to be listed as one of the most shocking achievements of any Beyond Grade A in history!

However, too much of something would never be good. He had achieved something that he was not supposed to achieve with the strength he had now, which was not without drawbacks. What Han Xiao was glad about was, Sierron had made it that all this way because he had 'burned his potential'.

This way, it would be much more acceptable for the various organizations, including the three Universal Civilizations, and the other Beyond Grade As.

With that reasoning, as well as the Beyond Grade A united front, Manison would most likely not test him after seeing this astonishing achievement, which would eliminate a huge problem for him.

At the same time, people saying that he was burning his potential would also not reduce the effects of his achievements.

Although this explosive state was made possible with many Character Summon Cards, some of which could only be used once…

Others would not know that this was the case!

Han Xiao knew clearly what those high-level organizations would be thinking—they would have a false assumption that as long as he was willing to pay the price of burning his potential again, he would be able to draw up this strength again!

And even if he explained the truth to others, no one would believe him!

Therefore, following this thought, the various organizations would all come to one conclusion…

Don't push Black Star too much!

This way, the influence of this event could be understood without saying.

As Han Xiao thought, a smile appeared on his face.

"Since I've now planted fear in them, I can continue to develop myself slowly. It's going to give me a big fortune…"

At this time, he only had one thought.

Sierron really is such a good friend!

Suppressing the surprise in his heart, Han Xiao quickly told Phillip to clean up the battlefield and take away the Gorutan amber specimen.

Having seen that the battle had ended, the dynasty allies finally came forward.

"You've really outdone yourself this time. When this gets out, it's definitely going to make a huge impact," Kant said. "Sharp and brave, as one would expect from youngsters. When I was making a name for myself in the universe, I was young too. But now, I have to think of the pros and cons before making every single move. I've lost that courage."

"You're being humble." Han Xiao smiled.

"Well, defeating Gorutan is just a small matter. The problem is, what do you plan to do with him?"

Kant was not surprised by this result. Black Star was in an explosive state, and the battlefield favored him. Plus, he was also a peak Beyond Grade A. Therefore, defeating another peak Beyond Grade A seemed very normal, nothing compared to the absolutely shocking fact that he had forced twelve Beyond Grade As of the federation and the church to retreat.

"Hmm, Gorutan has no one to rely on, and no one will come to bail him, so I'm going to keep him as part of my collection."

Beast Ancestor was one of the protectors of the Galactic Black Market. He did not have any background like the three Universal Civilizations. Therefore, there was, of course, no need for him to give Gorutan up. This was also one of the ways the three Universal Civilizations appealed to the Beyond Grade As. After all, no one could guarantee that they would never lose, and having one of the three Universal Civilizations backing them would make them feel much more assured.

Kant nodded and said, "This incident was too sudden, so we couldn't help much. Luckily, the results did not turn out too bad. The dynasty will help you to deal with the aftermath of this, and the dynasty's upper echelons will probably come to negotiate with you very soon."

"I know."

At this time, Silver Shadow turned back to his normal appearance, which attracted the attention of everyone.

Han Xiao nodded at him.

"You were of great help this time, thanks. Follow me back later and be a guest at my place. I'll keep my promise."

"I should be the one thanking you. If not for you, god only knows when I would've discovered this new ability I have."

Although Silver Shadow was quite heavily injured, having discovered a new ability made him quite happy.

Kohler could not help but ask curiously, "Silver Shadow, what ability is that? Can you show it again?"

"It's one of the special forms I have, which Black Star had helped to discover…"

Silver Shadow chatted passionately with the others, and Han Xiao nodded in his mind.

With my influence, this guy is probably going to start his Uber life much earlier…

However, with the help I gave him, it will probably be quite much easier for me to make him my private Uber.

This time, Han Xiao turned to look at Ravenlaude, who was staying silent and looking like he wanted to say something but did not, so Han Xiao started the conversation.

"How you doing? Have your wounds healed?"

"Pretty much…" Ravenlaude thought of his experience of getting beaten into a pulp not long ago, resignation appeared in his eyes.

"Haha, thank you for letting the past be the past and coming to help this time." Han Xiao smiled.

"I didn't help much."

"Don't say that. If not because you relayed the message, the dynasty's reinforcements would not have arrived here so soon. I owe you one for this."

A hint of a smile finally appeared on his face. He felt much better.

Aiyo, although Black Star is irritating sometimes, he's quite a good guy overall.

Sorry Ty-Ty, I probably won't be able to join your anti-Black Star alliance. Hang in there!

Suddenly, they all felt something and turned to look at the source of it. Beast Ancestor's fleet, which had been watching from the side, was now quickly retreating.

Kohler shook his head and said sarcastically, "They watched on as their leader was attacked. Such wise subordinates."

"With Gorutan gone, his organization will split up very soon." Beyoni snorted. "But that's a good thing. I've always disliked the things this guy did. If he did not buy tons of females from the Galactic Black Market, he would not have been able to make so many offspring. With his organization gone, the slavery business of the black market will take a hit."

"You're probably the last person here who has the right to say that…" Han Xiao remembered that Beyoni also had a huge harem.

"That's completely different. I chose mine from my people and never forced anyone. I'm not spreading my seed all over the universe."

Beyoni was quite proud, and he felt that he had the moral high ground.

Among the Beyond Grade As, there were actually quite a number of people who did not like Gorutan's way of doing things, but no one messed with him because of how strong he was. Now that the dynasty's allies present had seen Gorutan get defeated by Han Xiao, they were all glad.

Han Xiao did not bother entertaining him and silently opened the interface.

Including Gorutan, he had captured a total of five Beyond Grade As, which far exceeded the requirements of the mission. The mission was now shown as 'completed'.

"Five chances to draw abilities. I'll have to make full use of them."

Han Xiao was very excited.

He decided that he had to pray and touch Feidin before drawing the mission reward, or it would be a huge waste if he received some useless abilities.

Beep beep!

The communicator suddenly rang. He glanced at it. It was a call from Urranrell.

He picked it up and said, "Your Excellency Urranrell."

"I've understood the situation. The dynasty will negotiate with the federation and the church, now tell me the details of what happened."

"Okay, so it started…" Han Xiao explained the situation and skipped some details in between.

"To think that Hila has such an ability…"

After Han Xiao finished, Urranrell kept silent for a while. She then suddenly changed the topic and asked, "What about you? What price did you pay? Did you really burn your potential?"

"Yes," Han Xiao said without any change of expression.

"How big is the impact of that exactly?"

"I don't know."

"Sigh… You were too headstrong this time. You could have shrouded Hila in Spacetime Amber, and we could've bailed her afterward. This was avoidable. You have the highest potential in history. It's not worth doing something so unwise just to vent your anger."

"No, if I did that, I would have helped the enemies to take away Hila's ability to fight back. Plus, there are too many uncertainties to bailing someone out. The church might not be willing to make the deal and might keep Hila forever, and the federation would demand that I unseal the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. Furthermore, Hila isn't the dynasty's ally, so the dynasty is in no position to bail her."

Urranrell frowned slightly.

"What you're saying is, despite this incident, you still aren't willing to let Hila join the dynasty?"

"Hila has her own will. You're saying it like I can force her," Han Xiao joked.

"Joining the alliance will help to avoid something like this from happening again. Do try to convince her. I'm sure she won't want to see you burn your potential for her again," Urranrell said.

"… Got it."

If the dynasty used this to persuade Hila, given her personality, she might really agree to it. Urranrell indirectly gave him a reminder.

Han Xiao shook his head. Just as he hung up the call, another communication request came.

He looked at it. This time, it was from his headquarters.

The scene of the Black Star Palace command room appeared. Hila stood at the front, and beside her were Ames and Aurora. Around them were the many officers of the army. They were all looking at Han Xiao on the screen with concern.

"Black Star, are you okay?"

"I'm fine. It's been dealt with. I've captured Gorutan. Hila, he's the person who leaked the information to get revenge on you. You don't have to worry about him anymore." Han Xiao smiled.

Hila bit her lips.

Black Star did everything to protect her. He even got rid of the root of this incident. Looking at Han Xiao trying to look like it was no big deal and thinking of how tough of a battle Han Xiao had gone through for her, all the words of appreciation were stuck in Hila's throat.

Words were too light, not enough to express how touched and thankful she was.

Seeing this, Han Xiao joked and said, "Say something if you want to. Being this hesitant doesn't fit the impression I have of you."

Hila took a deep breath, stared into Han Xiao's eyes, and said, "You will forever be my… army commander."

There was no thank you. It was more like a promise, a declaration.

Hearing this, Han Xiao wiped the smile off his face. He looked into Hila's eyes with a serious expression and slowly nodded.

"Okay."

"I heard from Hila that you burned your potential?" Ames softly said from the side.

"Don't worry, that's all fake. I actually did not suffer any losses at all."

Ames nodded lightly. To her, this was clearly a white lie that Han Xiao said to comfort them.

She did not deny Han Xiao of his 'kindness' and only remembered it.

Han Xiao suddenly thought of something. "By the way, where did Traveler go?"

"He ran away, but we injured him," Hila said. "Before he left, he said that the Black Star Army disobeyed the rules and fought someone who came to challenge as a group. Is he really related to this incident?"

"Humph, this guy is such a drama queen… Leave him alone. He's a sh*t-stirrer at most. There's no time to deal with him now. That's for later."

Han Xiao exhaled and said, "I'll be going back first. We'll probably be quite busy for some time…"

…

The entire universe was paying attention to the Flickering World, and this huge news erupted all of a sudden, spreading like wildfire through all channels, ignoring the restrictions of distance.

Every single person who saw the news was shocked.

The federation and the church had gathered twelve Beyond Grade As to kill the Black Star Army's second in command, but they were forced to retreat by Black Star's main body, who even captured a few of the attackers. Not only that, even the Galactic Black Market's Gorutan was held responsible for this by Black Star because he was involved and was captured alive.

This means that… Black Star had fought twelve Beyond Grade As alone and won!

Are you kidding me‽

All the news after the Flickering World opened combined would probably not be as shocking as this!

The entire universe was driven into a frenzy!

Chapter 1059: Impact

In the Federation of Light's Central Galaxy territory, a small spaceship with the army's symbol was slowly moving in the cosmic space. The people of the Black Star Army's Abyss of Stars division were onboard.

This was the Federation of Light's territory. The Black Star Army had been invited to build a subdivision there long ago. However, the market was already split up by the various organizations, and given the sensitive relationship the federation and the dynasty had, this subdivision had experienced very limited growth in the region.

The Black Star Army was not popular everywhere, at least not here. The subdivision members there could not enjoy the reputation of the army, so they could not feel the benefits that came with the influence of the Black Star Army. Instead, they were even bullied by some local Beyond Grade A organizations, so their time there was not the best.

That day, however, everything changed.

At this time, inside the hall of this small spaceship, all the crews gathered and watched the virtual screen in the hall, which was playing the news.

"According to reliable sources, an incident erupted in the Flickering World yesterday. A total of twelve Beyond Grade As of the Arcane Church and the Federation of Light attacked the Black Star Army's frontline stronghold in the free competition zone, attempting to kill the Black Star Army's deputy captain, 'Goddess of Death' Hila. After the event occurred, Black Star quickly arrived at the scene and fought the twelve Beyond Grade A enemies alone. In the end, all enemies were exiled, and five were captured, one from the Arcane Church and three from the Federation of Light—'Red Devil' Tolaen, 'Energy Soul' Womre, 'Lone Ranger' Jackornitz, and Hades. After that, Black Star traveled far to capture another Beyond Grade A who was suspected to be involved in this incident, 'Beast Ancestor' Gorutan. What Black Star has done has shocked the entire world. The reason behind this incident is still being investigated…"

As soon as this ended, the cabin was filled with cheers of triumph!

"Woo!"

All the crew members present raised their hands and cheered. They were visibly overjoyed.

"Hahaha, the federation's people have finally been taught a lesson!"

"Our Army Commander is invincible!"

Many of them had come because of Black Star's name to begin with. Now that they saw what a shocking feat their leader had achieved, they were filled with burning passion and respect.

This news was a gigantic morale boost and had become the hottest topic within the army, even more so for the subdivision crew present. They were stationed in the Abyss of Stars and had faced a lot of difficulties. Now that their boss had captured three Beyond Grade As of the federation, one of whom was the leader of an organization that had been causing a lot of trouble for them, they felt that their army commander had given them justice.

The joy lasted quite a while before dissipating. In this festive atmosphere, this spaceship arrived at its destination. This was a transfer planet. The spaceship had gone there many times before. Following the instructions, it safely parked at the port.

As soon as the various subdivision members disembarked from the spaceship, they felt the difference. They looked around and saw that the passersby had all stopped to greet them with nods and looks, and their eyes were filled with complicated emotions such as surprise, fear, and curiosity.

This time, the port's registration point approached. Compared to the formal manners they had always displayed, the attendant's face was filled with passion and a fawning smile. This was something these subdivision members rarely saw.

"Haha, look at these guys. They never knew to respect us, but now they're afraid."

Seeing the change in attitude of the people around, a sense of pride appeared in their hearts. They felt honored and glad that they had joined the Black Star Army.

The reason for these changes, of course, was the world-shaking achievement the army commander had made recently. The reputation of his faction had rocketed to the peak in the entire universe!

With a leader like him, the future of the organization was as bright as ever.

This was not an isolated event. Scenes just like this could be seen everywhere across the universe.

…

Currently, almost all the players were in the World Server. When the players at the frontline stronghold uploaded the battle recording, everyone's attention was immediately absorbed by the news.

On the forums, this incident had filled up the entire Flickering World panel, and countless people were discussing it.

The players did not know the details. All they paid attention to was Black Star's terrifying achievement.

With his exceptional performance, Hila was completely ignored. It was assumed that Han Xiao had fought twelve enemies alone.

Although they knew that Black Star was among the strongest in the entire universe, this absolutely exceeded the imagination of the players. They were not too familiar with the difference in strength between Beyond Grade As and were full of disbelief.

"This is absolutely bonkers!"

"I remember that he was also surrounded during the Planet Lighthouse battle, but back then, the army commander had the help of the dynasty allies. This time, he needed no help, yet he still defeated twelve Beyond Grade As alone, capturing four!"

"Paging Bun-Hit-Dog, wake up and make your video, quickly!"

"I heard that the army commander sacrificed a lot in exchange for such strength, all to protect Hila."

"This is probably what love is."

"I'm getting on that ship!"

"Our captain is the best!"

Other than expressing shock, the various players were also speculating about the influence this incident would have.

Currently, the competition was intense in the Flickering World, and the Black Star Army had been affected as well. For something like this to happen, its impact would be incomprehensible.

Furthermore, the army commander also expressed his stand to hold all the people involved responsible no matter how difficult it would be by capturing Gorutan, who provided assistance.

This way, Black Star Army's faction advantage would climb to the peak. Who would dare mess with Black Star during the Flickering World competition period?

To the Chinese players, one saying explained the impact of this achievement Black Star had made perfectly…

When you make one amazing punch, you'll avoid a hundred punches.

Comparatively, this had made a more obvious contrast to the organizations that the Black Star Army had warned during the faction war incident earlier.

Due to the 'no fighting back' policy these organizations took, the innocent casual players in these organizations had a much stronger opinion about how important factions were. They were already unsatisfied with their factions to start with, and when they saw this news, many people were convinced to switch factions.

Of course, their top choice was the Black Star Army.

The players of the various countries who had only recently joined the army had another perspective about this incident.

In the previous versions, the players of the various countries could only watch the Black Star Army from afar. Now that they had joined the Star Field and could finally be a part of it, they had a brand-new experience when discussing it as members of the faction.

In the past, they could only watch others praise Black Star, but now they could join in and do it together, which felt completely different.

Some new army players immediately experienced how amazing it was to have a powerful faction leader. They were sending out even more 'captain is the best' messages than the senior members. The forums were almost completely occupied by the army players. The atmosphere was festive.

On the other hand, the senior members were also enjoying the sense of superiority, thinking, You guys are too young. This is no big deal.

…

In the Arcane Church, the various Beyond Grade As and the upper echelons' remote projections had gathered to discuss how to deal with this incident.

Although their mission had failed and they had lost Tolaen, the people present did not look too unhappy. They were even somewhat secretly glad.

"This mission's failed. We could not kill Hila, but we're not disappointed with the results." An upper echelon of the church spoke. "Your Excellency Kasuyi, you've done a great job, shattering the federation's plans and causing them to lose three Beyond Grade As. We are very satisfied with the decisions you've made."

"I've only made a few contributions," Kasuyi replied calmly.

"Hehe, don't be so humble. Compared to Hila, it's more important to prevent the federation from obtaining a chip to unseal the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter."

The upper echelons were smiling. Thinking that they had made the Federation of Light suffer such a big loss, they were all in quite a good mood.

"Nonetheless, the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter is still in the federation's hands, so it's best to negotiate with Black Star or the dynasty to see if we can get one of the federation's captives from them so we can exchange for the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter."

Kasuyi nodded. "Although the operation has failed, we still offended the Black Star Army. Odds of the negotiation succeeding are not high, but it's worth a try."

"Hmm… By the way, you said Black Star showcased an ability similar to Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation and sent Hila back to his headquarters despite the spacetime being sealed. Is that true?"

"Of course, I'm certainly not mistaken."

Hearing this, the man pondered and said, "Since that's the case, we'll have no choice but to cancel all plans directed at Hila…"

Since Black Star had the ability to ignore spacetime stabilization, there was no point in targeting Hila since she would be able to leave any time.

The ability of the King mechanical suit that Han Xiao had displayed had completely shattered all plans the church had for Hila. She was now finally in a safe spot.

Seeing the responses of the upper echelons, Sagman and the other 'former prison mates' exchanged looks and saw complicated emotions in each other's eyes. It was the resignation of knowing that they would not be able to take revenge and the delight that they had escaped this time.

This time, another church upper echelon spoke. This was a member of the Bishops. "Putting Black Star's technology aside, the federation is going to be the one with the biggest headache. I just want to ask, what do you guys think of Black Star's strength?"

The various Beyond Grade As exchanged looks before all looking at Kasuyi.

Kasuyi pondered for a while and said, "What Black Star has achieved in this battle is very shocking, but since we're involved in it and know the details, we know that although Black Star is not as strong as the outside world says he is, he's still very strong. His raw strength is not the main issue; it's the fact that his combat strategy almost has no weaknesses. His indestructible body made up for the biggest weakness of a Mechanic, and with the help of the Spacetime Amber, his actual combat capabilities far exceed the level he's at. It's tough to judge… From this incident onward, we'll have to look at Black Star in a new light. He has two states, normal and explosive, the latter being on an entirely different level to the former.

"Although Black Star burned his potential this time, since he can burn it the first time, he will be able to burn it again. Among all Beyond Grade As, not many can guarantee a win against Black Star during his explosive state. Therefore, it's best not to push him into that situation."

After hearing this, the church superiors exchanged looks.

Well, you're basically telling us not to mess with Black Star, aren't you?

…

On the other side, the Federation of Light also hosted a similar conference. The atmosphere was completely different from the Arcane Church—it was extremely serious and grave.

President Bader looked around and said with a serious tone, "A total of three Beyond Grade As are in the dynasty's hands. Who can tell me how it ended up like this? Which one of you can give me an explanation?"

The remote projections of the various Beyond Grade As present had no words. They all uncontrollably glanced at the three empty seats.

Bader's mood was as if he had stepped in dog sh*t on the sidewalk.

Before the mission, he felt that this mission would almost certainly be a success. Even if they would not be able to capture Hila, with the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device and six Beyond Grade As, retreating safely would not be a problem at all. However, he had never expected to suffer such a huge loss.

This result made him suspect that something had gone wrong along the way.

Bader turned to look at Sierron and said with a deep voice, "You were the leader of this operation. I had high hopes for you. What do you have to say now?"

Noticing the blame in the President's tone, Sierron said furiously, "It's all because of Kasuyi!"

Hearing this, none of the various federation upper echelons had good looks on their faces.

Back during the Planet Lighthouse battle, the federation had plotted against the church, and now it became the other way round.

Many people felt that they could finally understand how the church felt back then.

This time, Manison calmly said, "The church's interference is an important factor, but the main reason is that Black Star expected this and deliberately used false information of his whereabouts to misguide the outside world, while his main body hid nearby and surprised Sierron and the others. Plus, there's the fact that they could not linger around in enemy territory and could not maximize their strength, which led to them being defeated by Black Star one by one. Don't underestimate a peak Beyond Grade A Mechanic."

Bader narrowed his eyes and looked over. "I heard you were involved in this too, and you fought with Gorutan."

"That's right." Manison nodded and did not deny it.

Bader gave him a meaningful look, but he did not continue asking more questions. He changed the topic and said coldly, "The most imminent issue is to negotiate with the dynasty to bail the three Beyond Grade A allies out. Don't mess with Black Star for the time being."

Then, he left the conference immediately. He did not want to see these troubling allies of his at least for today.

…

In Tarunamir Palace's conference room, Urranrell supported her chin with her crossed hands and looked around at those present.

"The incident has come to an end, you all know the details, tell me your thoughts."

They stayed silent for a while before one upper echelon spoke. "Black Star has dealt with this very beautifully. He exceeded our expectations completely. Currently, we have Beyond Grade A captives as chips, so we have the upper hand in the negotiation. Black Star has displayed his trump card, so we have to judge his strength at a higher level. In my opinion, although we did not start this incident, we should still give Black Star some compensation for him burning his potential, to show him how important he is to us."

"Hmm, not bad."

While responding, Urranrell secretly glanced at the hawk faction's Bekorodi, only to realize Bekorodi's eyes were half-closed. It looked like he did not plan to speak.

Originally, Bekorodi thought that Black Star would have to rely on the dynasty's help to get through this, so he insisted on demanding that Hila join the dynasty. Now, however, Black Star had basically handled the problem all by himself, and the dynasty barely helped at all, so this proposal would no longer make sense.

Furthermore, Han Xiao's achievement had shocked Bekorodi too. All the dynasty's upper echelons valued him much more. In this environment, Bekorodi had nothing to say, so he stayed silent.

Seeing that no one opposed the idea, Urranrell continued. "About compensating Black Star, I plan to carry out a plan… to temporarily open up the selling rights of the Evolutionary Totems."

Many upper echelons' eyes widened in surprise when they heard this.

Very few had expected this and had knowing looks on their faces.

Due to the Evolution Cube, the dynasty was not on good terms with Black Star. There were some cracks in their relationship.

However, through this incident, the dynasty saw Black Star's abilities and decided to take a step back to fix this.

Chapter 1060: The Godlike Battle

Bright starlight reflected in Sorokin's pupils through the floor to ceiling windows of the top floor. He stood before the window and looked up at the starry night.

"Gorutan is done for…"

To think that just a few days ago, he had been chattering and laughing with Gorutan in his palace. Sorokin mourned for three seconds.

Although he was mostly just the messenger in this incident, he had still secretly intended to shift the direction of how things played out. However, all plots were shattered by Black Star with pure power. Even he felt a sense of resignation.

"Wasn't able to use Hila to start a conflict, what a shame." Sorokin shook his head. "However, considering that Gorutan is no more, it's not too bad."

Gorutan was a shareholder of the Limitless Financial Group, and Sorokin had used his own identity as a shareholder to gain protection while strengthening his connection with the Galactic Black Market through Gorutan's routes.

After so many years, Sorokin had already infiltrated the Galactic Black Market using Gorutan's connections. Even if these connections were broken, his business would not be affected much. However, he could not possibly kick Gorutan away after using him.

Due to this incident, he would have one less shareholder to share the dividends with, which would actually save Sorokin some money. Some of his businesses that he had given to Gorutan in the past could now be retrieved and developed as usual. At the same time, he would also be able to slowly chip away Beast Ancestor's organization's main business and their market share.

"Hmm, Gorutan being gone isn't a bad thing for me. Maybe I can use the shareholder position he left behind as a bargaining chip to gain the support of other protectors of the Galactic Black Market and make me a new protector of the Galactic Black Market."

Sorokin narrowed his eyes as he thought about how he could benefit from this.

Although he did work together with Gorutan, business partners were not really on his side in Sorokin's eyes. To him, the relationships he had with these people were purely built on mutual interests. Therefore, he was not sad about Gorutan being gone at all. Rather, he was happy with the fact that he now had one less person to share profits with.

"Nonetheless, Black Star's strength is indeed quite incredible…

"After this, the Crimson Dynasty will likely reevaluate their relationship with Black Star. There's a sixty percent chance they will temporarily put aside any arguments regarding the ownership of the Evolution Cube. They'll then compensate Black Star by opening up the purchasing rights of the totems, bribing his heart and displaying their clear intention of wooing him… Hmm, then my deal with the federation, the church, and the dynasty's hawk faction can be put aside. It's time to stop interfering with the Black Star Army's businesses."

The Limitless Financial Group had made deals with multiple parties before starting to disrupt the Black Star Army's businesses. The core reason was the Evolutionary Totems.

The federation and the church wanted to pressure the dynasty in various ways to force them to open the purchasing rights of the totems, so they wanted to influence the dynasty through Black Star. The dynasty's hawk faction's goal was to pressure Black Star and convince him to exchange the Evolution Cube for other Universal Treasures. If the dynasty opened up the purchasing rights of the totems, this problem would be solved instantly. Thus, the Limitless Financial Group would have no reason to continue pressuring the Black Star Army.

Other than these considerations, Sorokin also planned to stay low for some time.

Black Star had achieved something that was more than enough to be written down in history; now would be the time his influence was at its peak. If the Limitless Financial Group acted too out of line, Black Star would most likely target them even more. Hence, keeping a low profile would not be bad.

Sorokin did not want to make things ugly. After all, Black Star was the local dragon of the Flickering World. Small conflicts would still be fine, but it would not be pretty if things escalated.

If Black Star used his explosive abilities again, even he would have to face him with all his strength. He did not want to expose his strength and lose his camouflage as someone 'weak' and 'fragile'.

"Hmm, Traveler too…" Sorokin's eyes flickered. "It's best to get rid of him."

…

"Didn't expect Black Star to eliminate Gorutan so decisively. Looks like my reminder was part of the reason…"

Somewhere within the free competition zone, Secret Master looked at the news playing on the communicator and frowned.

Like Gorutan, he had been a protector of the Galactic Black Market for many years. The two of them had many conflicts both on the surface and secretly. He understood Gorutan's strength and knew that he was no match for him, or the one taking the position as the Limitless Financial Group shareholder would not have been Gorutan.

Seeing that Gorutan had been eliminated by Black Star, Secret Master was shocked while at the same time felt complicated about losing an old rival.

Of course, feelings were one thing. If anyone wanted to bail Gorutan out, he would be the first to oppose it.

After some time, Secret Master adjusted his mindset and started thinking about how he could benefit from this.

"The organization left behind by Beast Ancestor is a huge chunk of meat. It's best to share it to make my own organization stronger. Hmm, among those offspring of his, there seem to be some who are quite talented. I can make them work under me… If I take them to see the Beast Ancestor's specimen, it will probably be very fun…"

Thinking about that, Secret Master could not help but smile.

"Black Star did something huge this time. It'd be best to keep in contact with him in the future. Black Star will lead the shared front of the Beyond Grade As. I should pay more attention to this matter."

…

Somewhere in the Constellation Corridor, a dynasty patrol ship was slowly moving.

In a cabin, a dynasty male wearing a low-grade officer uniform leaned on the railing. He held a communicator and watched it with a naive smile.

This person was very muscular. He looked ordinary and friendly, without the special position marking on his uniform. It would be very hard for someone to think that this was a Grade C Super combatant of the Pugilist class.

This time, a few colleagues doing the daily patrolling walked over and saw this buff man. Someone yelled, "Yo, Karlot, what are you watching that made you smile so brightly?"

"Ah, I'm watching the news." Karlot turned around and smiled.

This person was the Beyond Grade A potential stock Han Xiao had once paid attention to, a peak Beyond Grade A Pugilist of the dynasty in his previous life.

More than twenty years ago, he was still a child who was studying in the dynasty's Super Academy and had yet to even awaken his class. Now that more than twenty years had passed, he had turned from a frank child to a frank adult who was just Grade C. His growth could not be considered fast; it was mediocre.

Due to Han Xiao's interference, his growth took a different path from before but still had the same overall effect. Karlot still joined the dynasty military after graduating, and after ten years or so, he was still a low-grade combatant who was rarely promoted if at all.

This time, a few colleagues of his approached and saw the news about Han Xiao on the communicator.

"His Excellency Black Star? Ha, as expected!" a colleague joked. "Sigh, sadly, you know Black Star, but Black Star doesn't know you, his top fan."

"He does know me. When I was young, His Excellency Black Star once personally tried to recruit me. He…"

Before Karlot finished his sentence, his colleagues were already laughing out loud.

"Hahaha, you're at it again!"

"Keep going, don't stop."

"The legendary man with so much talent that even Black Star personally tried to recruit… Poah, haha, I can't do this. Let me laugh a while longer!"

Seeing this, Karlot was not angry at all. He only scratched his head and smiled with resignation.

Ever since he came into contact with Han Xiao when he was a kid, he had been paying attention to anything related to Han Xiao in the news. In time, Han Xiao had become his idol. A colleague had once asked him the reason, so he told the truth. However, to his surprise, no one believed him, which made him the king of jokes among his colleagues.

Black Star would personally try to recruit an ordinary Grade C dynasty officer?

Who would believe that?

Position depended on strength. Even though Han Xiao had once personally tried to recruit him, more than twenty years had passed, and Karlot's growth had proved to not match the word 'genius'. This incident also got forgotten and not written in his resume. He had no intention of proving it to his colleagues. He did not care if others believed him, and he did not mind being made fun of.

At the start, due to Black Star, the school had high hopes for him. However, after they realized he had ordinary talent, they gave up on him. Nonetheless, Karlot was not affected by it, nor was he in a hurry to prove himself. All he did was slowly and patiently train while enjoying the process.

Throughout the years, even Karlot occasionally wondered if Black Star had made a mistake back then. However, this did not trouble him.

The disappointment and derision of others had little effect on him, and he did not think it was something worth getting angry over.

If he was destined to be ordinary, he would embrace it. He focused on the things he wanted to do; there was no need to force others to look up to him. This had always been the way Karlot lived his life.

Shaking his head with resignation, Karlot ignored his colleagues who were laughing and looked at the communicator again. Seeing Han Xiao in the papers, he smiled from the bottom of his heart.

…

Galaxy Calendar Year 730, February 18th. This was a day noted in history.

On this day, Black Star fought a battle in the Flickering World that could rarely happen even every hundred years. Initially, the church and the federation's assassination mission for Hila might have become the fuse to cause the conflict between the three Universal Civilizations to erupt, but Black Star singlehandedly extinguished its flames and caused a sensation!

This news even surpassed the Flickering World. Even the competition and fighting stopped temporarily. The various organizations inside the free competition zone all maintained a low profile to see how things would go from there.

Countless galactic residents knew that Black Star was a top tier individual in the universe, but as a 'newbie' who had only appeared a few decades prior, Han Xiao did not achieve a lot of notable things. In terms of his reputation, there was still quite a difference between him and Manison, Kasuyi, and those senior peak Beyond Grade As.

This news, however, refreshed the image countless people had of him once again. His reputation universally skyrocketed.

What happened on this day was given a nickname by the outside world—Black Star's Godlike Battle—which surpassed all his past achievements and became the most notable deed on his resume.

At the same time, the Wayne Card company once again made an announcement to drastically buff Black Star's card in the next version, while at the same time introducing the memorial card sets with the 'Black Star's Godlike Battle' theme. They were quick and familiar with benefiting from what was popular at the time.

The other neutral Beyond Grade As were shocked by Black Star's achievements. Thinking of what had happened to Gorutan, more people further confirmed the strategy to not become Black Star's enemy but become his ally…

While the incident was brewing and countless people were paying attention to the Black Star Army, Han Xiao returned right back to Black Star Palace and announced to the outside world that he would be resting for some time.

…

Within Black Star Palace, Han Xiao did not chat much with the various officers, only greeting them simply before he quickly hurried back to his personal training location. He then closed the gate and locked himself inside.

Feidin and Nero had been present earlier, and Han Xiao had already rubbed them.

Inside the room, he opened the mission list with his hands covered in luck, took a deep breath, and prayed.

After praying silently for some time, Han Xiao then clicked the 'complete' option on [Rescue Hila].

[Rescue Hila] completed!

You have received 92 Billion EXP, 4 Random Rewards, and 1 Blank Character Summon Card.

You have received 1 Universe Legendary Point.

Universe Legendary Point: Godlike Battle—You single-handedly fought twelve enemies and achieved a result that shocked the entire universe. From this point onward, your name shall be written into history and mentioned along with the strongest group of people in history. Your name will get passed on even if stars shift and seas dry up, as one of the symbols of peak individual greatness!

Han Xiao was not surprised. He rubbed his hands and looked at the following notification.

There were four Unknown Character Summon Cards. Given the fact that so many people participated in the battle, he did not know what he could get either.

If he got those weak ones, it would clearly not be good, but if he got a Character Summon Card of someone strong, the chance of it having a powerful ability would also be much greater.

Having looked at the notification, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled with surprise.

You have received [Character Summon Card: Kasuyi]!

You have received [Character Summon Card: Sierron]!

You have received [Character Summon Card: Gorutan]!

You have received [Character Summon Card: Hila]!

Chapter 1061: Reward

Character Summon Card—'Void Overlord' Kasuyi: [Artificial Psychic Current—Frenzy Tide]

By using Psychic attack on a large area, creates a long term aggressive Psychic Current that can be controlled in simple ways. Deals damage instances to all living creatures in the affected area. Damage taken will be judged three times every second. Basic damage each damage instance: (INT+MYS)*1.8. 170% Psychological Resistance penetration, a chance to give the target a random negative mind state. Uses: 0/2.

Character Summon Card—'Star Shatterer' Sierron: [Sixteen Arms—Shattering Fists]

Single target melee range ability. Through quick consecutive attacks, send highly condensed Pugilist flames into the target's body through a special method, shattering the target's atom structure instantly. The target's body will be annihilated. One Lethal Judge will be carried out, depending on the difference between the user and the target's level, health, Energy Level, STR, END, and LUK. If the judgement fails, deals 500,000–800,000 True Damage to the target. Uses: 0/2.]

Character Summon Card—"Beast Ancestor" Gorutan: [Body of the Beast Ancestor]

+20% STR, +20%DEX, +40% END, +300% Pugilist Flame damage. Regenerates 2.5% of maximum health every second. Duration: 30 minutes. Uses: 0/2.

Character Summon Card—"Goddess of Death" Hila: [Death Rejection—Awakening]

When your health reaches zero, you will be immune to this death and instantly recover 25% – 50% of your health while refreshing your status. This can be gifted to another being, but it is only effective once on the same target. Uses: 0/6

"Woah, these are nice!"

Han Xiao was overjoyed after reading through all the effects of these Character Summon Cards.

The quality of them was extremely high. They certainly matched up to those peak Beyond Grade As and the owner of a Super High Risk Esper Ability.

Kasuyi's Character Summon Card was a pure attack ability with good base damage. Han Xiao's Intelligence and Mystery totaled about 30,000, so the basic damage every instance would be about 50,000. Three instances every second meant that this ability would deal about 150,000 damage every second. The 170% Psychological Resistance penetration meant that it would drastically reduce the effectiveness of the target's psychological barrier. If it was used on a weaker target, the damage might even be close to becoming True Damage.

If it was just a one-time attack, it would not be too big a deal. The powerful part of this Character Summon Card was that it would create a Psychic Current that would not easily dissipate. With good enough control, it would become a large-area AOE attack that dealt constant damage over time, which would add up to an enormous amount of damage.

Sierron's Character Summon Card was also an attack ability. Unlike Kasuyi's AOE ability, this was a single target ability. Not mentioning how powerful the Lethal Judge mechanic was, the True Damage dealt even if that failed was still very high. If this dealt the maximum 800,000 True Damage every single time, just two to three hits would send Psyker to see God.

However, this would not be effective against targets who had True Damage Immunity. If Sierron used this on Han Xiao, it would be the same as a tickle.

Han Xiao nodded. "The single target damage a peak Pugilist can deal is still quite incredible for normal Beyond Grade As."

Gorutan's Character Summon Card was an overall powerful buff that was very suitable for Pugilists. It was also quite good for Han Xiao, since it gave attribute bonuses and bonus health regeneration.

The one that surprised Han Xiao the most was Hila's Character Summon Card. This was the upgraded effect of the [Death Immunity] talent, which was basically a chance to revive. Even though he was already extremely tanky, this Character Summon Card still gave his life another layer of security.

The shocking part was, this could be gifted to someone else, so that person would be immune to death one time as well.

Character Summon Cards were created from the characters, meaning that Hila had this ability. However, Han Xiao had seen her interface before, and she did not have the ability to give others a one-time use Death Immunity in the past.

"Could it be that this battle forced her potential out and made her awaken a new way to use her Esper Ability?"

This seemed quite possible.

During this battle, Hila had built a link with Aurora that ignored distance. Maybe this was partly the reason this ability appeared, which would explain why Hila did not have this ability in his previous life.

Outsiders could only accept this ability once and could not be revived by Hila indefinitely. Nonetheless, it would still mean one extra life, which was amazing for the Black Star Army's officers.

"I used quite a number of Character Summon Cards. There're still uses for Psyker, Ames, Mechanic Emperor, and Silver Shadow. The ones that are finished are only Perfect Mechanical Sense and Polar Channel Flow. I shall use the Blank Character Summon Card this time to restock the Perfect Mechanical Sense, so in the end, all I spent was Heber's Character Summon Card. Receiving four more has made up for that."

Han Xiao had a joyful expression on his face.

Character Summon Cards were just the appetizers, yet those already made him gain back the cost of the explosive power he used. The chance to draw abilities from the bonus mission was the main dish.

He suppressed his excitement and looked at the notifications on the interface.

Bonus mission requirements have been completed.

You have received bonus reward: Randomly draw an ability/talent from each Beyond Grade A captive.

He had captured five people this time—Tolaen, Womre, Jackornitz, Hades, and Gorutan—who were spread across Mage, Mechanic, Pugilist, and Psychic.

Although their average strength was not as high as those whose Character Summon Cards he had received, the abilities he would obtain would be permanent.

There were two noobs among these five, but at least they were Beyond Grade As, so there was a chance he would get something good.

"I have to leave the best to the last."

Han Xiao decided to start drawing from the weakest.

He hesitated between Tolaen and Hades for a while before going with Hades.

Note: Hades is a Psychic. Part of the abilities/talents are adjusted according to your class.

Randomizing… complete.

Please select one from the five options below as the reward:

[Will Resistance]—Ability: +35% Abnormal Psychological State Resistance. Cost: 0. Cooldown: 160s.

[Calm and Relaxed]—Talent: +200 INT, +200 MYS.

[Energy Control Proficiency]—Talent: -25% Energy Cost.

[Psychological Barrier Enhancement]—Talent: +120% Psychological Resistance, +50% Abnormal Psychological State Resistance.

[Squeezing Style Energy Recovery]—Ability: By spending 20,000 – 50,000 health, recover the same amount of Energy and temporarily reduce Energy Cost by 15%. Cooldown: 330s.

Hades was a Psychic, so most of the options were related to psychic, which was expected.

Not receiving any powerful talents, Han Xiao was not discouraged and took it as a consolation prize.

He picked [Psychological Barrier Enhancement] without hesitation, which was not too bad.

Throughout the years, Han Xiao had been consciously making up for his weakness in the psychological field and had already obtained quite a high resistance. However, when he saw Kasuyi's Character Summon Card earlier, he knew that his current Psychological Resistance was far from enough for someone like Kasuyi.

Since he had obtained a decent new Psychological Resistance talent, it was like filling up a gap for him.

After adjusting his thoughts, Han Xiao then continued to draw the next ability.

Note: Tolaen is a Mage. Part of the abilities/talents are adjusted according to your class.

Randomizing… complete.

Please select one from the five options below as the reward:

[High Level Energy Senses]—Talent: Increase your senses of all kinds of energy. You will be able to see more details the others aren't able to see.

[Magic Insulation]—Ability: When receiving magic attacks, the actual damage you receive will be decreased by 22%. Magic type controlling abilities last 17% shorter on you.

[Super Overload]—Talent: Your body can endure an even greater load. Some buffs will last longer on you. +1,500 END, +15% maximum health.

[Skilled Melee Combat Techniques]—Talent: You know a ton of melee combat techniques. Your attacks will occasionally deal damage in an area. +34% Melee Damage, +20% Critical Rate, +28% Block Chance, +23% Dodge Chance, +300 DEX.

[Lightning Control]—Ability: Drastically increase Lightning and Electromagnetic Affinity.

"… Well, I guess a Demon Race Mage who doesn't put points into melee combat isn't a proper Mage."

Han Xiao's mouth contorted slightly.

Among the five options, [High Level Energy Senses] was basically an ability all Beyond Grade A Mages had to have, which was what made them able to capture any strange movements of energy. [Magic Insulation] and [Super Overload] were abilities only buff-type Mages like Tolaen had. His body had to endure the load from a large number of enchantments so that the buffs applied on him would last longer.

Without much hesitation, Han Xiao picked [Super Overload] directly. This was the most suitable for him, and its numbers were quite impressive.

The 1,500 Endurance points made up for the shortage in his Endurance. He just had to put some of his Free Attribute Points into Endurance for it to be above 15,000, and he would be able to receive one more God's Trait Transformation Point every Promotion.

After this battle, Han Xiao had noticed that the important factor that made the difference between peak Beyond Grade As was the extent of their God's Trait Transformation. Although his way of leveling up was different from the others, more God's Trait Transformation Points would always be better.

Han Xiao drew from Womre third, which gave him something quite great.

[Cell Activity Expansion]—Talent: Through training, you have enhanced the activity of your cells, increasing the quantity of energy your cells can contain and efficiently make use of. With your character's level increasing, your energy will gradually increase.

Lv1 – Lv100: +0.5% maximum energy, -1% Energy Cost, +2% Stamina Energy Conversion Efficiency every 10 levels; Lv100 – Lv200: +0.8% maximum energy, -1.5% Energy Cost, +4% Stamina Energy Conversion Efficiency every 10 levels; Above Lv200: +1.2% maximum energy, -2% Energy Cost, +6% Stamina Energy Conversion Efficiency every 10 levels.

Current total bonus: +27.4% maximum energy, -49% Energy Cost, +132% Stamina Energy Conversion Efficiency.

Han Xiao had his eyes on this ability instantly, mainly because of the increase in maximum energy.

His current energy was about 180,000, so his maximum energy would increase by about 50,000 instantly with this talent, and this was something he was short of.

Not only did this increase the limits of his health-energy conversion, it also increased his Energy Level by one rank, giving him a new level of bonus, which was basically the same as a few thousand Attribute Points.

This talent was a percentage bonus, so it had growth potential. To him, this was as powerful as half a Molding Talent.

Furthermore, cell activity was related to life span, so maybe this talent had the hidden effect of increasing his life span by one second.

The fourth target was Jackornitz. With the same class, there would be more abilities to choose from.

Mechanical Pugilists preferred to fight using supportive machinery, and they were good at the techniques of using those 'tools', so they had quite a few special talents.

The five options he got all had quite high quality. Most gave Machinery Affinity bonuses. Han Xiao hesitated for a while and made his choice.

[Machinery Control Master]—Talent: Machines that are enhanced by your Mechanical Force will receive the following bonuses: +120% Melee Damage, +24% Ranged Damage, +35% mechanical suit performance.

Although this talent was a Mechanic class talent, only Mechanical Pugilists would be able to awaken it usually, but Han Xiao had now obtained it.

Many Mechanical Pugilists' abilities directly increased their efficiency in using their machines. This ability gave him a huge boost, and the melee damage of his mechanical army rocketed.

Furthermore, Han Xiao had tested it before and found out that the Mechanical Deity was a special assembled machine, but as its core had to be his main body or his Lord's Avatar, it was considered a mechanical suit by the interface. This meant that it would receive mechanical suit related bonuses.

This way, the actual power of the Mechanical Deity would be increased drastically. It would have strength close to having two Perfect Mechanical Senses stacked together!

"This is good stuff. If I can get all those special talents of Mechanical Pugilists and Cannon Masters, the power of my mechanical army will probably multiply many times." Han Xiao was drooling at the thought of it.

He then adjusted his emotions, took a deep breath, and clicked on the last target.

Tip: Gorutan is a Pugilist. Part of the abilities/talents are adjusted according to your class.

Randomizing… complete.

Please select one from the five options below as the reward:

[Energy Shock]—Ability: By using energy, shock the target and make the target enter a short stunned state.

[Micro-Molting]—Ability: Refresh yourself, dispel all debuffs. Cooldown: 400s.

[Energy Recycle Stream]—Talent: When melee attacks land, while dealing the same damage, you can recycle 40% of the energy used in your attacks.

[Block Penetration]—Talent: Even when the target has blocked your melee attack, they will still receive 30% – 80% damage.

[Polar Channel Flow—Blood Rage]—Ability: Through burning your health, you turn it into a special kind of blood energy. This increases your basic attributes, attack, Critical Rate, and ability strength, depending on the health you burn after every judgement. Duration equals the amount of time you burn your health for. After this ability ends, you'll enter a state of weakness that lasts three times the duration of this ability.

Chapter 1062: Plan and Birthday

Having seen the five abilities drawn from Gorutan, Han Xiao was slightly stunned.

"Polar Channel Flow?"

There were infinite Pugilist styles in the universe, and the Polar Channel Flow style was mainly focused on explosive abilities, which reflected the horrible and harsh environments in the past. Of course, it might also be that the creator of Polar Channel Flow simply liked the style.

High-level Pugilists all mastered multiple styles, so it was normal for Gorutan to know Polar Channel Flow.

Back then, the ability from Heber's Character Summon Card was [Polar Channel Flow—Cellular Overdrive], while this ability from Gorutan was Blood Rage. The effects of the two were quite similar, but the former exchanged potential for strength while the latter burned current health.

To others, although the explosive state given by Cellular Overdrive would damage one's potential, it did not have any immediate side effects and only made one stronger for the time being.

Comparatively, Blood Rage would burn up one's health continuously. If the user's regenerative ability could not keep up, the user would be heavily injured if this ability was activated for an extended period. This was not great for long duration battles, and the enemies might notice its side effects and deliberately play for time.

Han Xiao thought that this was probably the reason Gorutan did not use this on him. After all, he was known for being amazing at drawn-out battles.

"All things considered, this ability is perfect for me."

Han Xiao's eyes were sparkling.

His regenerative ability could even be considered everlasting. Even Beast Ancestor could not compare to him. Therefore, burning his health was nothing. If he used it well, this ability could totally become a stable method to obtain explosive strength.

In comparison, [Micro-Molting] and [Block Penetration] were good but not as valuable as Blood Rage.

"I've used up the one-time Character Summon Card for Cellular Overdrive, but now I've obtained a method to gain explosive strength stably. Tsk tsk, nice…" Han Xiao was overjoyed.

Even though the explosive strength granted by Blood Rage was slightly lower than Cellular Overdrive, it was completely acceptable.

At this time, all Han Xiao wanted to do was raise his arms and praise Feidin.

… Oh, and Nero too.

You have received [Polar Channel Flow—Blood Rage]!

The new abilities obtained from the five Beyond Grade As immediately took effect on Han Xiao's body, changing every one of his cells.

Hu!

Immense pain flooded his entire body, only dissipating after quite some time.

Han Xiao had already gotten used to this pain. He took a deep breath and sensed the changes in his body.

Hmm, I clearly have more energy, which is the effects of Womre's [Cell Activity Expansion]. My physique is stronger too, like I've taken off some invisible weights. This should be thanks to Tolaen's [Super Overload]. My mind feels slightly stronger, thanks to Hades' [Psychological Barrier Enhancement]. My Mechanical Force feels sharper and easier to control. This is Jackornitz's [Machinery Control Master] taking effect…

Han Xiao sorted out the changes in his body and felt refreshed.

A new notification popped up on the interface, a new dungeon was created from [Hila Rescue Warfare]. Without even having to look at it, Han Xiao knew that the level of this was much higher than even the Planet Lighthouse battle, which was far beyond the players' capabilities at the moment.

Han Xiao then looked at the mission list. [Rescue Hila] had already disappeared, meaning that all the rewards were given.

Out of curiosity, Han Xiao tried using [Polar Channel Flow—Blood Rage]. This ability gave him the freedom to decide how much health he wanted to burn without an upper limit, only a minimum of 0.1% of maximum health every second. Therefore, he turned it on with the lowest requirement.

Boom!

A blood colored ring of light suddenly blossomed in front of Han Xiao's chest and expanded like ripples before him.

The next moment, he felt that all the blood in his body started boiling!

Bright red vapor sprayed out from all over his body like flames made of blood. The reactions were very drastic. By just roughly looking at it, one might mistake it to be red Pugilist flames.

This blood red vapor was the blood energy obtained from burning his health. In Han Xiao's senses, it was as easy to control as his limbs. Masses and masses of new energy kept appearing in his body as his health burned.

He took out a mirror and looked at himself. The vibe he gave off was completely different compared to the calm and tough vibe he usually exuded. With the blood vapor surrounding him, he looked fearsome, evil, and savage. However, his emotions were unaffected.

Han Xiao then looked at the interface and pondered.

"The bonuses of Blood Rage are mainly focused on damage output and ability strength. It's a more aggressive bonus compared to the comprehensive bonuses Cellular Overdrive gave."

He then turned off Blood Rage, and a sense of weakness immediately appeared, lasting for a little while before disappearing.

In order to familiarize himself with the new abilities, he tested them one after another before stopping and nodding with satisfaction.

"Tons of EXP, four Random Rewards, one Blank Character Summon Card, four powerful Character Summon Cards, and five great abilities and talents. Excellent."

Han Xiao was very pleased.

The difficulty of the mission was over the top, but the rewards were rather generous as well. His strength increased by quite an extent, and he obtained a few new trump cards.

Suppressing his excitement, Han Xiao started thinking about the real impact of this incident.

The change in impression the various organizations had of him would be none other than to take him more seriously. During his trip back, there were more organizations that had come to fawn over him. Some organizations that had been plotting secretly against him had also stopped, such as the Limitless Financial Group.

Overall, the goal of establishing fear and respect was greatly achieved. Han Xiao's reputation was at its peak, and the Black Star Army's position became even firmer. Han Xiao's planned goal was achieved.

Including the players, more people requested to become allies of the Black Star Army. The officers who were in charge of this department had been working overtime continuously to settle these matters. The number of members of the army was projected to see a sharp growth in the time to come.

Han Xiao nodded. "The federation and the church are probably discussing the matter of exchanging captives now. I'll obtain a large amount of resources very soon."

Of course, he had no plans to keep these four Beyond Grade A allies of Universal Civilizations himself. They were hot potatoes that he could not make use of, so giving them away in exchange for more profit was the best solution. However, this time, he was not going to easily give them away. He had to make things difficult for the church and the federation, to make them publicly apologize before he even considered giving those Beyond Grade As back.

"Speaking of which, Kasuyi's proposal is not completely out of the question. Should I sell the federation's people to the church and let the two of them fight with each other?" Han Xiao scratched his chin and pondered.

Gorutan, of course, did not receive such a treatment. Han Xiao planned to keep him as part of his collection.

He also paid attention to Beast Ancestor's organization. After their boss was done for, as expected, the organization became chaotic, splitting into many factions. The internal conflict was at its peak. At the same time, there were also many organizations outside that had their eyes on the 'inheritance' of Beast Ancestor, prepared to take a bite of it anytime.

"Should I participate too? After all, I'm the one who eliminated Beast Ancestor."

The possible responses the various organizations might have appeared in his brain one after another, quickly getting analyzed and classified. This time, a flash of insight crossed his mind. The more he thought about it, the more he felt it was doable.

Han Xiao's eyes slowly became brighter as a smirk appeared on his face.

"If the dynasty's response is just as I expect, I should be able to look for Sorokin after some time and get some things from him…"

Earlier, Han Xiao had announced to the outside world that he would be resting. One reason was to make the so-called 'burned of his potential' more convincing, and another was to spare some free time to do some stuff.

There were quite a few things he had to do. First, he had to deal with the impact of this incident—dealing with the captives, negotiating with the dynasty, splitting up Beast Ancestor's inheritance, and so on all fell under this classification.

Second, he planned to use the time to repair the mechanical army, which would take quite a lot of time. He planned to build Emperor's Cape's too, as well as improve the Mysterious Energy Host.

Then there was the kindness Manison and Kasuyi had shown during this incident. Using the enormous force of the Black Star Army in the Flickering World, he would start building a communication channel for the united front of the Beyond Grade As.

Last but not the least, he needed to also make a trip to the secondary dimension with Ames and capture Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy's old buddy, Holy Light Particle.

"Looks like I'm going to be rather busy. The good thing is, after this battle, I won't have to worry about the growth of the Black Star Army for quite a long time, which will give me a lot of time to do my own things."

After doing some planning, Han Xiao arranged his thoughts and walked out of the room.

After returning and touching Feidin, he had headed right to the training ground to receive the reward and had yet to talk to his many officers. He now walked toward his office and told Phillip to gather the core officers.

When Han Xiao walked into his office, everyone was already there, including Ames.

Technically, this was an internal affair of the army, and outsiders should not be allowed. However, Ames was an exception, so no one was stupid enough to stop her from doing so.

"You've finally decided to come back?" Ames leaned on the wall and looked at Han Xiao with a faint smile.

"Ahem, I had important matters to deal with," Han Xiao replied with resignation.

He had invited Ames to the Black Star Palace only as an insurance. He did not expect it to force Traveler to back away.

"Don't forget what you promised me." Ames' brows rose slightly.

"When I'm done handling the matters on hand, we'll go travelling." Han Xiao nodded.

"Hmm, I shall not disturb you guys then."

Ames glanced at Hila before leaving the room. Although no one had chased her away, she knew that it was not polite to stay there and listen to the internal affairs of the Black Star Army.

Han Xiao sat on his seat, looked at Hila first, and said, "After some time, you'll have to return to exploring on the frontlines. I'll build something new for you, the mechanical suit that sent you back here. With that, you won't have to worry about getting ambushed or surrounded."

"Okay." Hila had no objections.

"Has the dynasty contacted you recently?"

"No." Hila shook her head.

"Then let me say this first. If they use me as a reason to convince you to join the dynasty, come and discuss with me first. Don't agree right away."

"Don't worry, I know."

"By the way, how's your connection with Aurora?" Han Xiao asked curiously.

"It's stable." Hila paused for a moment. "But I can still feel the existence of that special secondary dimension… Can you take me along to travel the secondary dimension this time too? I want to take a look at it."

"Probably not this time. Someone has to be with the army while I'm gone." Han Xiao shook his head. "I'll go with you next time."

Hila nodded in agreement with a slight smirk. She seemed to be in a good mood.

After chattering for a while, Han Xiao looked at the other officers. He glanced at Feidin with eyes filled with satisfaction, and he only stopped smiling after Feidin became clearly uncomfortable. He then told the others to give their reports.

Sylvia, Herlous, Reynold, and the others summarized the recent business situation. During the reporting process, quite a number of Calamity Grade officers secretly sized Han Xiao up. Han Xiao's recent achievement had shocked many officers too. Many of them had even more respect for him.

After listening to the reports, Han Xiao nodded. "The situation is going extremely well right now. After this, the Black Star Army will have an even easier time in the Flickering World. There won't be anyone casually testing us. You guys, go do some recruitment. The army might see some excellent business opportunities in some time, be prepared…"

Han Xiao talked about the things to pay attention to and do for a while. Seeing that everyone nodded while listening, he suddenly thought of Evans.

Evans had also come back with the spaceship that transported the Throne. Han Xiao had told Phillip to sort his accommodation and had kept him hidden.

Before Evans, his secret weapon, grew to a certain point, Han Xiao was not going to expose him to others.

Han Xiao leaned back in his chair. "That's all. If there are no questions, you guys can get back to your tasks."

"By the way," Sylvia said, "there's one thing that needs your attention. A star director hopes to see you."

Han Xiao was surprised.

Star director? Who? Manison?

Seeing Han Xiao's confused expression, Sylvia explained, "He's the renowned master-level director, Beny Travol. He is hoping to get your permission to shoot a documentary about you."

"… That's new."

Han Xiao immediately became interested.

In the galactic society that had no shortage of material supplies, the influence of the entertainment industry was humongous. A famous galactic celebrity might have quintillions of fans. For example, Feidin had been considered a local celebrity before.

Galactic star directors such as Beny Travol had extremely high popularity and influence, as well as extraordinary positions in the industry. They were all important people even on the scale of the entire universe.

However, the people in the entertainment industry and someone in the military industry like him were in two completely different worlds that hardly had any connections, which made Han Xiao wonder why this person came asking to shoot a documentary of him. Could this be the effect of his Universe Legendary Points?

Han Xiao contemplated for a while. "Okay then, I'll meet him."

"Okay, I'll contact him personally." Sylvia nodded.

Han Xiao then glanced at everyone. Seeing that no one spoke, he said, "If there's nothing else, we'll call this a day."

At this time, Hila suddenly thought of something. She took out a small box, placed it on the table, and pushed it toward Han Xiao with her beautiful fingers.

Han Xiao looked down at it. This was a red box with ribbons, like a gift. Confused, he looked at Hila.

"This is…"

"Today is your birthday. This is your birthday present, an amulet. Remember to wear it," Hila said softly.

Han Xiao was surprised.

This is only February. Today isn't my birthday. It's October… Oh, I get it. This should be the birthday of my original identity. Back on Planet Aquamarine, the Germinal Organization definitely investigated me. Hila probably saw the birth certificate of my original identity.

Understanding that, Han Xiao swallowed the words he was about to say back down. He accepted the gift and said with a smile, "Thanks, didn't think you'd remember."

"I remember everything about you."

Hila closed her eyes and left the room before Han Xiao could reply.

The officers around looked back and forth between the two of them with meaningful looks in their eyes. They then left one after another.

Han Xiao was the only one left in the room. He carefully opened the gift box and looked at what was inside.

A tiny dark gold coin lay quietly in the box, hooked on a thin silver chain. It was a necklace.

Han Xiao picked up this coin and suddenly felt a special kind of energy on it. It had both Hila's Power of the Dead energy and Aurora's Esper Ability energy.

With a flash of insight, Han Xiao opened the interface and looked at Hila's Character Summon Card.

If I'm guessing correctly, this coin is a carrier of some kind of ability, and this ability is probably the reawakening ability that Hila just obtained… No wonder she called it an amulet. Basically, she gave me a revive token.

The Character Summon Card did not display the limitations and cost for Hila to use this ability, but Han Xiao was certain that Hila would not be able to casually just gift this ability to anyone. It was most likely quite costly.

Han Xiao wore the amulet on his neck, stood up, walked to the window, and gazed at the scenery outside Black Star Palace.

If not because Hila suddenly brought it up, he would totally have forgotten the meaning of 'birthdays'. In all the years he had spent in Galaxy, this was the first time someone had given him a birthday present.

Although the birthday of this body was not the same as his own birthday, Han Xiao still felt nostalgic and emotional.

Memories often would not stop coming up once reminded. The images of the past kept appearing in his mind like it was lifetimes ago.

"Birthday…"

A soft sigh sounded in the room.

Chapter 1063: In Order to Save the Universe, I Have Decided to Become...

In the Emerald Star Cluster was one of Beast Ancestor's stronghold planets.

Two fleets with the same Beast Ancestor symbol stood against each other in space. The atmosphere was tense.

The situation was clear—the smaller fleet wanted to leave the stronghold and was stopped by the guarding fleet.

Inside the command ship of the guarding fleet, Byram looked at the fleeing fleet in front of him that was prepared to start a fight anytime with complicated feelings. He then said in the public channel, "Jotina, do you know what you're doing? This is defection!"

As soon as his sentence ended, a female creature appeared on the screen before him. She had light-brown skin, a lustful face, and black beastly patterns at the tips of her eyes and her temples, as well as white lines on her cheeks in a pattern like cat whiskers. She looked similar to a leopard. Her clothing was wild and unrestrained, showing her astonishing body shape and beauty.

At this point, the face of this woman was filled with a firmness.

"Gorutan is done. We've made up our minds. If you want to stop us, you can try."

Looking at the woman on the screen, Byram sighed in his mind.

This person's name was Jotina. She had some beast bloodline and was one of the Four Admirals under Beast Ancestor's command, like the Vanguard Officials and Black Star Guards. She was an ace combatant who stood at the top among her brothers and sisters. She was also a Beyond Grade A seed. Given her wild personality, quite a number of brothers and sisters were afraid of her.

However, a lot of people knew that Jotina was in the rebel faction and had always hated Gorutan. Gorutan, however, did not care if his children hated him. His offspring were just tools to him. As long as he was alive, he did not fear anyone escaping his control.

He had maintained control of his organization with his own strength, and once he was gone, it instantly started cracking up like rats leaving a sinking ship.

On this day, Jotina brought a big batch of rebel faction members and planned to leave the Beast Ancestor's organization, hence this confrontation.

Byram was in the neutral faction, so he did not have overwhelming loyalty for Gorutan. He sighed and said, "We're all brothers and sisters. Why fight each other? Father is only captured. He might return in the future. Why not stay and work through this difficult time together?"

"Shut up!" Jotina yelled. "I've been waiting for this day for way too long. If you don't let us go today, don't blame me for not having mercy."

Byram stayed silent. He turned and looked at the enraged expressions of the loyalists, shook his head internally, and ordered, "Let them go."

Without the overwhelming strength of the Beast Ancestor that kept this many people in their place, his organization had absolutely no unity, and everyone had their own plans. Byram was not willing to fight with them.

However, the loyalist faction was not having it. From the way they looked at it, immediately leaving when their father was in trouble was an act of total betrayal that needed punishment.

Although Byram was the commander, many officers did not obey him and suddenly fired, starting a battle.

Battleships were sunk one after another, creating fireworks in the comic space. Calamity Grades dashed about in between the battle and fought each other with no mercy.

After a very long time, the battle finally ended. Tons of battleship wreckages were floating in the cosmic space.

After paying a hefty price, the betraying fleet finally broke away. The loyalist faction also suffered a huge loss. Many officers were killed by Jotina on the spot, so none continued chasing after her.

Without father, there will be other Beyond Grade As who come to get us. These loyalists will be cleaned up sooner or later. I'd better find a way out as soon as possible.

Byram looked at the wreckages and sighed in his mind. He knew that the Beast Ancestor's organization was no more.

Meanwhile…

"We finally got out. They didn't chase us…"

Inside the command ship that was covered in battle scars, Jotina sat on the ground, leaning against the wall. She was exhausted and covered in wounds, blood pooling under her.

She was surrounded by many officers who were defecting with her. After the intense battle earlier, everyone had wounds and was bandaging each other up.

A Calamity Grade officer turned to Jotina after stitching a comrade up. "Big sis, where do we go now?"

Since Jotina was the initiator of this operation and was also the strongest, she was recognized by all as the leader of this defecting team.

"Escaping was just the first step. Don't forget our target. We can't rely only on ourselves; we have to go to a big organization," Jotina said while gasping for air.

"Who should we go to?"

"Whoever that beat up Gorutan." Jotina struggled to get up, looked outside the porthole, and murmured, "Black Star is worth depending on…"

…

A few days later, outside Black Star Palace…

"I've already disturbed you guys for quite some time. I'll leave today. Thanks for your help."

Silver Shadow stood before his spaceship, nodding to express his appreciation for Han Xiao.

Some time ago, he had used the Evolution Cube and stayed as a guest in the Black Star Army, bonding with Han Xiao. The relationship between them improved quite a bit, from familiar faces to good friends.

After staying for a few days, he still had other things to attend to so he decided to bid farewell today, Han Xiao came to send him off.

"Okay, I won't keep you then. Feel free to come here to play in the future." Han Xiao smiled.

Silver Shadow nodded, shook Han Xiao's hand, led a group of his subordinates onto the ship, and closed the hatch.

The spaceship's thrusters fired up as it sped up and dashed out of the dock, turning into a stream of light and quickly disappearing into space.

Watching the spaceship leave, Han Xiao nodded with satisfaction.

The time he had spent with Silver Shadow over the past few days had sped up the progress of winning Silver Shadow over. With the favors he owed him, he would be able to at least ride him three more times.

Han Xiao left the dock and returned to his office.

"Phillip, any news from the three Universal Civilizations?"

"Not yet, hum…"

"It's been so many days. It should be time for them to contact me."

Han Xiao shook his head. Over the past few days, he had been waiting for the federation and the church to contact him. It seemed that these two were still considering what attitude they were going to present when contacting him, so no one had called him yet.

During the Planet Lighthouse battle, he had handed over the captives to the dynasty, and the dynasty had negotiated with them. This time, however, he had basically caught all the captives by himself. Plus, he was much stronger. Therefore, Han Xiao told the dynasty that he wanted to negotiate with the federation and the church personally.

At this time, Phillip suddenly paused and reported, "Master, hum… there's a new communication request. It's from the Arcane Church."

Speak of the devil… Han Xiao told Phillip to pick it up.

Very soon, a remote projection appeared in the room. This was a high-ranking official of the church who was in charge of diplomatic matters. He took a bow as soon as he appeared, looking very respectful.

"Your Excellency Black Star, I'm the diplomat of the Arcane Church. First, on behalf of the church, I would like to apologize for this incident…"

"Hmm, let's skip all that and cut to the chase." Han Xiao glared at the church diplomat in front of him and said with a deep voice, "If you want Tolaen back, it depends on how sincere you guys are. I have to emphasize one thing though: the compensation must include a public apology on your side."

The church diplomat blinked a few times and said softly, "That won't be a problem, but we can put aside Tolaen's matter first. I want to talk about the federation's captives…"

Han Xiao raised his brow.

What a surprise. The Arcane Church is in no hurry to bail Tolaen back but instead wants to gain a federation captive first.

Although he could understand the reason behind this, Han Xiao still thought it was quite tragic… for Tolaen.

Shaking his head, Han Xiao said, "The church wants to buy a Beyond Grade A captive of the federation, huh?"

"Not one. The more, the better. I'm sure Kasuyi has spoken to you about this as well. The church wants something to regain the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. Your Excellency Black Star, we come with a lot of sincerity this time, and we're willing to pay a high price."

"How high?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"These are our initial terms."

The diplomat brought up a list and displayed it.

Han Xiao quickly scanned through the list. Not only did the terms include tons of resources compensation, but the church was even willing to use non-strategic Universal Treasures to acquire the captives. The terms were quite generous.

However, he was not going to easily agree. He purposely acted like he was considering for a while. Then, he said slowly, "I'll have to endure pressure from the federation if I sell their captives to you, and this is all you're offering? It doesn't seem sufficient."

"How about you propose the terms, and we can…"

Han Xiao snorted and interrupted him. "Go figure, change the terms till I'm satisfied."

By not being the one stating the terms, he would be able to give the federation and the church a hard time. Otherwise, the two of them might not learn the lesson. Also, it would not be beneficial to public opinion if he easily agreed to their terms.

"Okay then, we'll go back and change the terms. Can I assume that you don't object to selling the federation's captives?" the church's diplomat asked.

"Depends on my mood." Han Xiao did not make a guarantee.

Seeing that Han Xiao was not taking a clear stance, the church diplomat had no choice but to go offline and report the situation to his superiors.

As soon as he disconnected, the communication request from the federation came.

"How coincidental," Han Xiao murmured and picked up the communication.

"Greetings, Your Excellency Black Star, I'm the Federation of Light's…"

"Alright alright, I know who you are. Cut the crap. Show me your terms for bailing the captives."

The federation's diplomat's words were forced right back down his throat, and he had no choice but to obediently show Han Xiao the terms.

After looking through the list, Han Xiao shook his head in his mind.

The price the federation gave was not as high as the church. After all, this was just ordinary bailing for them.

Tsk tsk, cheeky as always, you lost three people, but you don't want to pay a huge price?

In your dreams!

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, tapped the table, and said slowly, "Just now, the Arcane Church contacted me and made an interesting proposal."

"What proposal?"

"They want to buy the Beyond Grade A captives of the federation from me… and they're willing to pay a high price."

Han Xiao gave him a meaningful look.

The federation diplomat was startled and quickly said, "D-Did you agree?"

"Hmm, I'm still considering it. However, the price the church gave was quite tempting."

"You can't just decide to sell the federation's important ally to the church, or…" The federation diplomat was just about to threaten Han Xiao when he suddenly realized that he was facing Black Star, who had just cost them a huge loss, so he quickly changed his tone. "Anyhow, as long as you don't agree to the church's proposal, we will definitely do something."

"That will depend on your sincerity and how high a price are you willing to pay to make me reject the church's offer." Han Xiao smiled.

"Understood… Understood. I'll relay your thoughts to the upper echelons immediately and change the compensation terms."

The federation diplomat wiped off the sweat on his forehead and hastily disconnected.

He knew that Black Star was driving the price up, but there was nothing he could do. Even though he thought he saw through Black Star's intentions, the only thing he could do was to obediently follow it.

After getting rid of these two, Han Xiao leaned back in his chair and smirked.

If this had happened in the past, the risk of doing something like this would have been very high. However, after this battle, he had showcased more than enough strength to be noticed. Only then would the church and the federation be willing to negotiate with him calmly instead of continuing to plot against him.

With these captives in his hands, he had enough leeway to ask for over the top prices. Even though he had made it clear that he wanted the federation and the church to compete with each other, they could do nothing but put up with it.

This feeling of having the upper hand is indeed great… Han Xiao smiled.

While he was pondering, his communicator rang again. It was Sylvia.

"Army Commander, the galactic star director I told you about a few days ago has arrived at Black Star Palace."

"So soon?"

"They were in the Flickering World to begin with. I've already sent someone to receive them. Should I bring them right to the guest room?"

"Hmm, I'll go see him now." Han Xiao stood up.

…

A civilian spaceship parked at the exterior dock of Black Star Palace, and a group of people walked out from it.

At the front was an old man with a large beard and round head. He clearly gave off a vibe of being wealthy. Like a true artsy type, his long hair was swinging. He looked like a boiled egg with hair.

This person was the Crimson Dynasty-born galactic great director, Beny Travol.

As soon as they disembarked from the spaceship, they looked left and right cautiously and chattered among themselves.

"So, this is the Black Star Army's base. Are all these people mercenaries?"

"They're all looking at us. Keep it down…"

Having heard his assistants were chattering behind him, Beny Travol frowned and softly yelled, "Keep your mouth shut. If you insult Black Star's men, you know what the consequences are."

The others quickly became quiet, looking very cautious.

They had been following Beny Travol for a very long time and were seniors in the entertainment industry. There were people everywhere who wanted to fawn over them. Although they were not considered arrogant, they were still quite proud of themselves.

However, these people did not dare act arrogantly here. The Black Star Army was a top tier armed force that was on a completely different level compared to them. Now that they had entered the headquarters of such a powerful armed force, they naturally felt intimidated.

They knew full well that their influence was nothing compared to someone like this who held real power. Every one of them tucked their tail between their legs and acted humble.

Not long after, a receptionist of the army came and said with a bright smile, "Greetings, Director Beny Travol. Please, follow me. The army commander is waiting for you."

"Okay, thanks for leading the way," Beny Travol replied with a smile.

Seeing this, the assistants around were surprised. They knew their own boss all too well. He was always proud; very rarely did he show such a passionate and fawning smile.

They went all the way to the guest room, walked in, and saw Han Xiao sitting at the main seat. Out of panic, they hastily greeted Han Xiao.

Beny Travol quickly walked toward Han Xiao and extended his hand. "Your Excellency Black Star, thank you for agreeing to meet with me."

"You don't have to be so formal, sit."

Han Xiao shook his hand and invited everyone to sit down.

The group sat down one after another with their back straight and butt only taking up the edge of the seat, looking very cautious.

At the same time, they all stared at Han Xiao with respect and obedience, as well as a stiff and fawning smile on their faces. Many of them were quite important people, but now they could only smile.

Han Xiao shook his head. Position meant power. Even though he did not do anything, others would still uncontrollably feel nervous.

He turned to look at Beny Travol, smiled, and asked, "Great director Beny, I heard you want to shoot a documentary about me?"

"That's right. I've seen your files from the beginning to your astonishing rise in the galaxy. You're a living legend. What you've done stimulated my desire to innovate. It will be my honor to shoot a documentary for someone like you…"

Beny Travol cut right to the chase and started explaining the motivation behind all this.

When he came to the exciting parts, his face even became red, and he stood up to make gestures.

Han Xiao observed for a while and realized that this great director was not there just to praise him but really wanted to create an adapted documentary. This was probably one of the effects of his Legendary Points.

This was not strange. To others, what he had achieved was indeed legendary, so having a director want to shoot his life story was not exactly a surprise. After all, many films were adapted from true stories to begin with.

After being continuously praised for a while, Han Xiao felt quite good. Then, he waved and interrupted the saliva-filled speech of the director.

"So, you're just here to ask for my permission to allow you to shoot a film about me?"

"Not just that." Beny Travol suddenly became anxious. "I have another request. I hope you can be part of this film as an easter egg…"

These words required courage. He knew that Black Star's position was way too high. For someone with so much power, Black Star could basically be considered a political figure. This was like a request for the dynasty's ruler to guest star in his film—it was almost a daydream.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and tapped the table slowly but did not immediately reply.

As his expression changed, the atmosphere instantly cooled to a freezing point. Everyone's heart started beating faster and faster. No one dared take big breaths. The room became dead silent.

Just as Han Xiao was about to speak, a mission notification popped up on the interface.

_____________________

Invitation from a Director

Mission Introduction: A universally known star director hopes to have you take part in the shooting of a film.

Mission Requirements: Star in the film.

Reward: 1,800,000 EXP, random increase in Renown of various Star Fields.

Bonus Reward: Talent - [Celebrity Effect]

[Celebrity Effect]: Others will feel close to you and forgive you more easily.

_____________________

Han Xiao's mouth contorted slightly.

What's this? Forcing me to become a celebrity?

Chapter 1064: An Overly Difficult Mission

Han Xiao did not reject the idea of guest-starring in the film. He was not the lead star, so it would not take him too much time.

Furthermore, with how developed the technology was, it would not take long to shoot one film. Plus, they could be watched in many different ways, such as the classic third-person screen, an immersive watching experience where one could step into the environment, or even take over the perspective of the character in the movie. With the development of technology, the expression of films had also become richer.

The [Celebrity Effect]'s effects were not quantified. Feidin had it too, and it was related to the Charisma attribute. Not only would it make gaining Favorability easier, it would also make losing Favorability more difficult even if he offended someone. The name suited the effects it gave quite well.

The effects of the talent looked ambiguous on the surface, but Han Xiao knew that this was actually quite useful. It would help in many situations. Be it business negotiations or daily socializing, it was an excellent ability for networking.

Even if the mission rewards were not considered, this proposal itself was beneficial for Han Xiao. Currently, his reputation was at its peak, but the heat of the news would reduce with time. Furthermore, having such an astonishing achievement as a comparison, the more ordinary deeds would hardly increase his influence and fame.

Therefore, using the entertainment industry to continue to increase his Renown was a great path to take. After all, the entertainment industry had a unique advantage in terms of the attention it received. This would also not damage his reputation while helping the outside world understand him more.

Furthermore, this seemed very suitable for increasing the number of believers.

Hehe, that old man Manison definitely wouldn't be willing to do the same.

Under the nervous stare of Beny Travol and his assistants, Han Xiao purposely acted like he was pondering for a while. He then nodded and said, "Sure."

"That's great!"

Beny Travol was overjoyed. He initially thought he would most likely be rejected, but Han Xiao turned out to be surprisingly friendly.

The nervous atmosphere disappeared instantly. Everyone felt relief followed by excitement—being able to have someone like Black Star cameo in their film was like a dream.

"When do you guys plan to start the project?" Han Xiao asked.

"We'll have to finalize the script first. Since this will be adapted from your real experience, if possible, we hope you can provide some details. We might even have to organize a few interviews," Beny Travol said softly.

"That's easy, as long as I'm free." Han Xiao smiled.

"Okay okay. When we've done the script, we'll show it to you for you to audit. We'll only start the shooting after you agree with the script."

"Hmm." Han Xiao nodded. He suddenly thought of something and asked, "Do you have any funding issues?"

"Don't worry, the entertainment industry is quite influential. Plus, this will be your story. There will definitely be a lot of people fighting to fund it. Even the Crimson Dynasty's ministry of culture might." Beny Travol was quite confident.

"Alright, come to me if you have any funding issues. I'll sponsor you."

Beny Travol was very touched.

Whoa, what a generous man.

He decided that he had to make sure this film turned out amazing. It not only had to be filled with artistic factors but also had to make a great sale.

Having been a director for many years, Beny Travol had both excellent productions and failed ones. While using the noble reason of 'pursuing art' to get funding, some projects had not even been able to break even.

It would not be a problem if those films sponsored by ordinary people did not turn out great. He would lose his brand image and money at most. However, if the film sponsored by the Black Star Army turned out not good enough… he might even lose his life. He did not dare slack.

Given the population of this era, the profit in the entertainment industry was beyond imaginable. Occasionally, there were even some films that the entire universe liked and loved, and the profit gained from just one of those would surpass the total value of many small financial groups. It was absolutely bonkers. Han Xiao had no reason not to gain profit from it.

Han Xiao suddenly thought of something and said, "By the way, I want to put someone in the cast."

"Please do tell."

Han Xiao brought up Feidin's image, smiled, and said, "This person. He's one of my guards, a Calamity Grade Super. He was once a local celebrity. Just give him a character to play."

"This person…" Beny Travol's eyes widened.

He did not mind Black Star putting someone in the cast. He had seen this kind of thing happen way too many times. What surprised him was that Black Star was sending him a treasure.

This body! This appearance! This vibe! He's a born superstar!

Scanning the stunned expression on everyone's face, Han Xiao chuckled in his mind.

He knew very well how powerful Feidin's charming aura was. Having Feidin star in the movie would be more than enough to attract a ton of attention and make the promotion multiple times smoother.

Furthermore, Han Xiao did not forget about what Feidin had achieved in his previous life, [The Legend of a Singer], where he used his psychic singing to stop an entire war.

Therefore, to maintain the love and peace of the universe, he decided to make Feidin an idol again!

This was not a sudden thought. He had wanted to use this opportunity to make Feidin the image ambassador of the Black Star Army to gain more popularity, which might even attract more talents. At the same time, he hoped to increase the stock price of the Germinal Financial Group.

After so many years, the Germinal Financial Group was already listed thanks to the help of the army. Its funds at this point were huge.

Many thoughts flashed through Han Xiao's mind, but he did not reveal them. Maintaining a smile, he chatted with the others in an uplifting atmosphere. In the end, Beny Travol and the others decided to stay awhile in Black Star Palace to gain some insight and material before leaving with joy all over their faces.

After sending them away, Han Xiao told Sylvia to follow up with the matter and then went to chat for some time with Ames to make sure his old friend was receiving enough attention.

Ames, however, was very understanding. She knew that he had many things to deal with, so she did not hurry him. Both Han Xiao and Hila had returned, so she had company there and lived so comfortably she almost did not want to go back.

I don't have anything to do on Floating Dragon Island. What should I go back for?

What? Jenny?

Who's that? Never heard of her.

…

Han Xiao returned to his room and bathed out of habit. He came out surrounded by hot water vapor. Without drying himself, he wrapped himself in a bathing robe and lay on his bed while humming. Water droplets slid down his hair and wet his pillow.

Of course, Beyond Grade As' bodies were pure and free from dirt, so they did not have to bathe. However, Han Xiao enjoyed this feeling of adjusting his senses to have the temperature sense of a normal person. Only then would he be able to have a hot water bath. Otherwise, even lava would feel cold to him.

A few mechanical pets climbed up and circled around Han Xiao. They kept rubbing their bodies on him in an adorable way. There were both cats and dogs, even snakes. They were all mechanical lives with their own independent minds. Their metal bodies had no edges; they were smooth and round. They did not have to eat or excrete and were very easy to take care of.

Ever since Hila gave him a birthday present, Hila had suddenly thought of getting some pets to give his usually cold and quiet bedroom some life.

Han Xiao casually petted his pets for a while. He then leaned back on the bed and opened up the player forums.

The 'Black Star's Godlike Battle' topic had yet to cool down. It even became hotter instead. The Flickering World panel was still filled with it.

There were not only discussions. Many players also took action and left their original faction to join the Black Star Army, giving the player count of the army a boost.

The one-sided faction war had lasted a while. Due to the factions that were named admitting their inferiority, the army's opponents were powerless. Not only did the shady plan of those foreign clubs not work, they even shot themselves in the foot. The factions they were in had lost a huge number of normal players. This indirectly increased the unity of the army players and shortened the distance between the new and old army players from different countries.

The atmosphere in the Black Star Army had become much better. Although the players from different countries could not be considered friendly toward each other, they had grown to accept others.

On the forums, there was another thing that sparked discussion. After Han Xiao created the [Rescue Hila] Dungeon Crystals, he had placed them in the faction store.

In the following few days, a ton of players had bought the Dungeon Crystal to watch their Army Commander with their lives.

After nonstop effort and hard work, there were already famous dungeon raiders who increased the survival time record to a whopping twenty-nine seconds, earning the respect of countless players.

[Rescue Hila] and [Planet Lighthouse] were now known as the two film-type dungeons, which meant… there was nothing they could do, only watch.

Han Xiao was still browsing the forums with joy when Phillip sent him a message.

"Master, hum… A fleet that has defected from the Beast Ancestor's organization has arrived at our frontline stronghold in the free competition zone. Onboard are seven Calamity Grade officers previously under the Beast Ancestor's command, led by one of Gorutan's Four Admirals, 'Claw Empress' Jotina. She has mentioned that she wants to see you by name."

"See me?"

Han Xiao raised his brows and closed the player forums. He then quickly brought up Jotina's data and browsed through it. He then started pondering.

He did not know much about Gorutan's subordinates. Most of them were Gorutan's tools. Only a few had left an impression on him in his previous life, including Jotina, but not because of the achievements she made.

In his previous life, Jotina secretly worked with other organizations and gave out missions to players that involved destroying all the offspring production warehouses of the Beast Ancestor's headquarters when Gorutan was not home, releasing all the females that were imprisoned as reproduction machines. Although the plan did not end up succeeding, it still brought the Beast Ancestor a humongous loss. She initially wanted to die together with Gorutan using a psionic energy bomb but failed. In the end, she was torn apart alive by Gorutan.

Knowing that, Han Xiao had a rough guess as to why she was there.

"Okay, I'll meet her."

…

In the Emerald Star Cluster, the Black Star frontlines stronghold had already repaired the damage suffered from the Hila Rescue Warfare. The fleet was now patrolling as usual.

At this time, Jotina and the gang were welcomed into the dock. Due to the Beast Ancestor symbol on their spaceships, they attracted the attention of all the army members they passed.

The spaceships parked steadily, and the hatches opened with a swoosh. Jotina led her friends out of the spaceship, ignoring the strange looks on the army members around, and headed toward the guest room following the mechanical receptionist.

"We're finally here. I wonder if Black Star will keep us. After all, we were his enemies not long ago."

"Black Star isn't petty."

"I'm just not sure if we're strong enough for him to be interested…"

Jotina did not join the discussion. With a tense expression, she followed the receptionist into the guest room. It was empty.

Hum!

This time, Han Xiao's remote projection appeared in the room with his hands behind his back. He looked at everyone with coldness as he slowly spoke.

"You wanted to see me?"

"That's right. We were all under Beast Ancestor's command. We have been unhappy with him for a very long time but never had the strength to resist. Now you've defeated him, so we came to join you, hoping to work for the Black Star Army.

Jotina cut right to the chase while staring at Han Xiao. Clearly, she was very direct.

Although Han Xiao had already guessed, a saying still appeared in his mind…

This is them abandoning evil to take the righteous path, isn't it?

Han Xiao did not plan to reject them. After all, there were seven Calamity Grades, which was quite an amount of power. Furthermore, Jotina was a rare Beyond Grade A seed with extraordinary potential. She could be of company to Hadavy and Lothaire.

High-quality leeks uprooting themselves up and entering his vegetation field was always something Han Xiao loved to see. However, he could not agree with it too easily. The routine questioning was still needed.

"Why were you unhappy with Gorutan?"

Jotina took a deep breath. Sorrow and anger appeared on her face as she said, "In order to produce high-quality offspring, Gorutan bought countless females of different races from the black market. These females weren't even granted the freedom to die. The only thing they could do was become a tool of reproduction.

"My mother was one of them. With my very own eyes, I watched her give birth to one offspring after another for years. She died of exhaustion in the end. The high-quality offspring were given a lot of resources and trained well, while the low-quality ones became slaves. Although we're all related by blood, most people have no emotional connection to others. That place was like a cold and freezing graveyard. Everyone had no choice but to fawn over Gorutan. Not a single day spent there was not filled with hatred and disgust."

Jotina closed her eyes as she was flooded by the sorrowful memories, only reopening them after a while. Then, she said with a deep voice, "My friends have had the same experience as me. We hate everything Gorutan has created, but we had no choice but to be manipulated by him and assist in his evil deeds. We lived every day in agony and frustration. We're not afraid of dying. Only through enduring this pain and keeping ourselves alive can we find the chance to change everything. And when you defeated him, we were finally liberated."

Then, Jotina kneeled onto the ground. The people behind her followed. The entire group kneeled as a gesture of respect.

"We hope you can take us in!"

Jotina pressed her forehead onto the ground and growled emotionally.

"Please take us in!" Everyone else shouted simultaneously as well. The shouting echoed in the room.

Seeing this, Han Xiao pondered a while and nodded. "Since that's the case, I shall accept you to become members of the Black Star Army."

The group exhaled with relief and finally stood up.

A smile appeared on Jotina's face again. Her expression relaxed. It was beautiful. Like her wild personality, her emotions were also directly displayed.

Han Xiao nodded. His tone became friendly as he smiled and said, "Then, we're all family now. Come to Black Star Palace. I want to see you guys with my own eyes and arrange roles for you. Also, if you want to visit Gorutan's specimen…"

This time, Jotina interrupted Han Xiao. She wiped the smile off her face and said with a serious tone, "Black Star, I also have a gift as well as a request."

"Do tell." Han Xiao raised his brows.

Jotina nodded. "The Beast Ancestor's organization is in shambles now. It's a great opportunity to split it up. I'm willing to help you obtain the Beast Ancestor's inheritance. This is my gift to you."

"And your request?"

"I hope you can destroy the Beast Ancestor's headquarters and all of the offspring production facilities, releasing all the females and taking in all the young offspring of Beast Ancestor. This is both my request and my gift. Although I hate Gorutan to the core, these young offspring are innocent. Their worldviews have yet to take shape and can still be adjusted. If raised properly, they can become new blood for the army."

Jotina then looked up and stared at Han Xiao, as if she wanted to see the answer she had been hoping to see for a very long time in Han Xiao's eyes.

Han Xiao opened the interface, and as he expected, this triggered a mission. However, it was not one mission but two.

The first mission was [Liberate Beast Ancestor's Organization]. Just like Jotina said, it required him to destroy the Beast Ancestor's headquarters and free those within. The rewards were Jotina's Favorability and her Character Summon Card.

The second mission, however, shocked him.

Ending the Darkness

Mission Introduction: Life form trafficking is the source of countless tragedies. Jotina hates it with everything she has. Destroying the practice has always been her dream her entire life.

Mission Requirement: End the life form trading industry in Galaxy.

Reward: 1 Trillion EXP, 15 Random Rewards, 3 Universe Legendary Points, 5 Blank Character Summon Cards.

Bonus Reward: [Slave Liberator] Milestone.

[Slave Liberator]: Your relationship with all Lawful Factions will forever be fixed at [Reverence].

One trillion experience… Han Xiao was stunned.

This was the craziest mission he had ever seen, as were its rewards, and of course its difficulty.

Eliminate the life form trading industry of the entire universe?

Looking at the population of the entire Galaxy, this was a mission that was impossible to complete. If there was no demand for it, it would never have started in the first place. Even the three Universal Civilizations could not do this, so who else could?

No wonder Jotina only requested that he liberate Beast Ancestor's organization. She most likely knew that this wish of hers would never be achieved.

Of course, Han Xiao would not expose her. He shook his head, put this matter at the back of his mind, and did not mention it.

"About liberating Beast Ancestor's organization, you have my word."

"Then, I'll be willing to serve you till the end of time."

Jotina lowered her head, and admiration appeared in her eyes.

Ever since Han Xiao defeated Gorutan, she had viewed Black Star as her idol.

Before she came into contact with Black Star, she had been anxious, afraid that the truth about her idol might disappoint her.

Also, she was afraid that Black Star might mistake her for someone who went whichever way the wind blew, seeing her actions as betraying her old master and going to the winner. She would have been very sad if that was the case.

Now, however, all those worries were gone. Black Star was totally worth her admiration.

Like electricity running through her entire body, she suddenly felt something in her heart. She was a very direct person, and her emotions were easily affected. At this moment, she felt she was in love.

Chapter 1065: The Wolf Is Besieged and Annihilated

Ending his long-range projection, Han Xiao opened his eyes within his palace, his emotions overflowing in joy.

"Seven Calamity Grades joined, with one of them even being a Beyond Grade A seed. This wave of talents is good quality."

He had only been interested in the resources accumulated by the Beast Ancestor and did not covet the latter's offspring because both sides were enemies after all. Even if he were to forcefully accept the troops and force the descendants to work for him, there would always be resistance.

There was also a chance that they would not put in their best effort, and their numbers would allow them to pollute the army and form a faction, which would become a ticking time bomb.

A melon that is forcefully plucked will not be sweet.

The losses would outweigh the gains. Furthermore, the Black Star Army was already part of the Lawful Faction, so they could not go too overboard. At the same time, they did not lack manpower in the army at the moment, so he was not interested in poaching the manpower of the Beast Ancestor.

That being said, if it was those who decided to voluntarily pledge themselves to the Black Star Army, he naturally would not reject them.

"The majority of people from the rebel faction are still waiting, and Jotina's batch is only the first wave of guinea pigs. There will definitely be more of them in the future. Even I don't know the exact number."

Han Xiao did not wish to capture all these people in one go, as each individual had their own ambitions. Some of them might not necessary chose to defect to him if they were to betray the Beast Ancestor Organization. Some would choose to resign completely, burying their lives and living in a low-profile manner.

Shaking his head, Han Xiao temporarily put this matter aside and summoned Phillip.

"Notify Herlous and Sylvia. Tell them to mobilize the soldiers of the Shattered Star Ring to send a fleet over to the Beast Ancestor's base to free all the slaves and to destroy his offspring cultivation assembly line."

Due to the high difficulty level of the mission [Ending the Darkness], he could not progress in it at the moment. In contrast, the other missions were quite simple, and since he had already given the other party his word, Han Xiao swung into action. With Jotina joining him, he would also have sufficient reason to send out troops.

Furthermore, since Gorutan had brought out a large number of elites, his base was quite empty. Thus, it also reduced the difficulty. As long as the fleet brought along his own avatar as a guarantee, there should not be any accidents.

This group of guys who had forsaken the darkness for the light brought Han Xiao plenty of good news. However, there was one detail that made Han Xiao sit up and take notice.

He always felt that the look Jotina had in her eyes seemed a little bit too eager…

It was like how he normally looked at Feidin.

…

In the stronghold of the Beast Ancestor's base in the Emerald Star Cluster, after Jotina and her group broke out, the atmosphere became silent and cold. There was less chatter. They were obviously brothers and sisters, but the looks they exchanged were filled with vigilance, and more thoughts were hiding behind their poker faces.

As the people's hearts changed, the undercurrents surged.

Jotina was the first defector, and there were still many more of the cautious rebels watching the situation. Seeing that she had a good start, more of them started to get ready to move.

Within a secret room, a group of people from the rebel factions gathered together quietly. Their leader was a prestigious Calamity Grade officer, 'Boa Constrictor' Schneider. While he was not at the level of the four major officers, he was still one of the more influential officers, an elite combatant who combined his Pugilist skills with his innate toxin talents.

"I believe you know my purpose behind gathering all of you." Schneider looked around, his eyes stopping for a while on the stronger officers before continuing, "There's news from Sister Jotina, she says that Black Star has already accepted them. They have found a good home."

No one present spoke, waiting for him to finish.

Seeing this, Schneider said, "The loyal faction fought with Jotina and suffered heavy losses. They probably no longer wish to waste any more strength in dealing with the defectors. It's about time for us to leave as well. I know that there are a few among us that do not wish to defect to another organization and wish to be independent. All of this can wait for when we leave. For those that are unwilling to follow and walk your own paths, we will meet again somewhere in the universe and reminisce about our familial ties then."

After he was done, the room remained quiet for a moment before someone finally spoke out.

"That's right. It's time for us to leave. In another few days, it will be my troops' turn to patrol. This is our chance, and it's best to avoid any conflict with the loyalists."

As soon as the silence was broken, everyone spoke in a rush. Everyone with some influence in the audience offered suggestions, brainstorming for the rebellion.

Meanwhile, a few of the loyalists were also having a secret meeting.

"Did you hear? It seems like the group of traitors from Jotina's side joined the Black Star Army."

"Where did this news come from? Is it reliable?"

"Many people saw their spaceship headed toward the stronghold of the Black Star Army, and after entering, they never came out. Furthermore, among that rebel faction that has a lot of hidden thoughts, there has been quite a bit of intelligence leaking out, so it should be accurate."

One of them said in a deep voice, "If it's true, then we can implement a bold plan. Let our people pretend to defect and enter the Black Star Army. We'll find a chance to rescue Lord Father."

"But… Black Star is a Beyond Grade A Mechanic. It's hard to even be able to steal anything under his nose. Furthermore, there is no solution for the Spacetime Amber; even the three Universal Civilizations are left befuddled."

"Lord Father has so painstakingly raised us. He's our respected patriarch. Only we can help him now, so even if the odds are slim, we still have to try," someone else replied firmly.

"Alright… but there's still another problem. The defectors definitely know our allegiances, and the loyal factionists who attempt to defect will definitely be seen through."

"This is a good question. After being together for so long, one cannot just break into the group of rebels…"

Everyone hesitated.

Jotina's incident had provided hope to the loyalists. Some of them wanted to stage a rescue of Gorutan, who was made into a specimen. After all, he was just sealed and not dead yet.

At this time, the sound of a communicator rang, breaking the stale atmosphere in the room like a roar of thunder on a sunny day.

The leader looked at his communicator and said, "Byram has gathered all the officers to discuss our future plans."

Everyone did not feel any surprise. After Gorutan's fall, this sort of meeting had been held many times. Without a decision maker, the affairs of the organization could now only be decided by a large majority of the officers agreeing. However, everyone had their own plans, so there was no unified opinion.

The group of loyalists left the room, rushing toward the large conference room.

At this moment, the conference room was almost full of people. All those present were officers with a certain amount of influence, and the scene was as rowdy as a scene in a marketplace. The three factions of loyalist, rebels, and neutrals distinguished themselves clearly, all looking at each other with cold glares.

This group of loyalists immediately spotted Schneider and glared at him before finding their places.

Schneider did not care about their attitude. He had also heard the news when he was in his secret meeting and rushed over.

After waiting a while longer, all the officers were finally present. Byram was the last to enter, and he closed the door to the conference room. Under everyone's gaze, he slowly walked up to the rostrum before looking down from his vantage point at everyone.

"What happened, for you to convene us again?" one of the officers demanded. The person in question was one of the Four Generals.

"We haven't finished discussing the previous topic, so today, we'll continue to discuss the future of our organization." Byram calmly smiled before he changed the topic. "However, before that, let me introduce someone to you."

Everyone frowned. From Byram's attitude, they noticed something was wrong.

It was at this moment that a wave of magic appeared in the room, and a blue circle representing a transportation door appeared beside Byram.

Hum!

A foot slowly stepped out of the portal, and a strong sense of oppression soon followed. The air in the room seemed to freeze instantly.

The Secret Master walked out before waving a hand to close the transportation door. With his hands behind his back, he gazed at everyone present with an expression of indifference.

The entire room turned silent.

At this time, Byram broke the silence with a smile in his voice.

"I believe everyone is familiar with the Secret Master, who is also a patron of the Galactic Black Market just like Lord Father.

"Byram, what's the meaning of this‽"

The group of loyalists immediately stood up, suppressing their anger as they questioned him.

In reality, everyone understood that Byram, who was part of the neutral faction, had already initiated a relationship with the Secret Master. Under the guise of a meeting, he had gathered all the officers so that the Secret Master could catch them all at once and control everyone.

He was going to present this stronghold and all the officers present to the Secret Master!

Byram only smiled in response. His gaze shifted to the Secret Master, and he explained, "Since Lord Father was captured, countless organizations have been watching us, wishing to divide us. Without a Beyond Grade A holding the helm, we've been a mess. Secret Master is an old friend of Lord Father, so he has decided to grant us asylum to help us weather our difficulties."

Yes, spin, continue to spin your story!

Everyone cursed in their heart. The neutrals were surprised, the rebels had heavy hearts, and the loyalists were enraged.

The Secret Master took in everybody's expressions before coldly speaking. "The situation is as thus. Gorutan and I have been partners for a long time, and I cannot just watch as his descendants split. I'll temporarily take in the Beast Ancestor's organization, and when the situation stabilizes, I'll hand the rights back to you."

F*ck your mom, what sympathy and what partners? Do you think we all have amnesia‽

Everyone gritted their teeth.

The Secret Master did not have an organization of the Black Star Army's scale, so the warriors under the command of the Beast Ancestor were one of the resources he wished to gain.

Because he was not a direct enemy like Black Star, he would not need to worry about the issue of them taking revenge. Furthermore, he was also a patron of the Galactic Black Market, so it was more reasonable for him to receive the Beast Ancestor's organization. His own organization already consisted of many mixed forces, belonging to the gray side, so there was no need to worry about suffering from indigestion from being unable to digest the Beast Ancestor's troops.

This was merely an excuse for the Secret Master to embezzle the power of the Beast Ancestor, but even if the loyalists were angry, they dared not stand up against it.

The Secret Master had already spoken.

If you still do not know what's good for you, then you won't even have time to regret if this pinnacle Beyond Grade A here destroys you.

Thus, no one retorted after the Secret Master finished speaking, as though they all silently agreed.

At this moment, Schneider slowly stood up, attracting the eyes of everyone present, including the Secret Master.

He took a deep breath before speaking in a respectful tone.

"Many thanks to Your Excellency Secret Master for your generosity. Your asylum is something we urgently need, and I agree that you have to take over Lord Father's organization for the time being."

"Hmm, not bad."

Secret Master nodded, feeling that this kid was on the right path.

However, this impression was destroyed by Schneider's next sentence. "However, I've already grown tired of this kind of life, and I don't wish to continue fighting in the universe. Now, I just wish to live the life of an ordinary person. Your Excellency, I'm not going against you, but everyone has their own ambitions. Please allow me to retire."

Secret Master did not think much about it, replying, "You're blessed with a Calamity Grade level combat power. To retire just like that would be a pity. I hope you will continue to find the passion in your current post. I'm optimistic about you, so don't talk about resigning anymore. Sit down."

Schneider gritted his teeth before mustering up the courage to speak again. "Your Excellency Secret Master. I wish to take a period of leave. My sister has defected to the Black Star Army, and I wish to tell her not to worry about things back home."

Once this sentence was spoken, it could be considered as stating his stand. He implied that he did not wish to work under Secret Master but rather wished to lean toward Black Star.

Secret Master narrowed his eyes and stared at him. The pressure within the room got steadily stronger.

Only when Schneider started to sweat did Secret Master finally reply.

"I feel that there's no need for that. When I formally take over, the universe will naturally receive the news. There's no need to take unnecessary steps."

Hearing this, Schneider as well as the people in the rebel factions all sighed in their hearts.

The attitude of Secret Master was clear. Even if he knew that they wanted to go over to Black Star, he still chose to detain everyone, not allowing any officers to leave in order to control them.

"Ha…" Schneider sighed before sitting down, an expression of regret on his face.

If he had known of this development, he would have acted more aggressively and taken action with Jotina. He was a step late.

The faces of the rebels were ugly, and their current emotions could be described as 'being there in body but not in spirit'.

…

Secret Master publicly placed a magical imprint on all the officers to monitor their actions before speaking in a high-handed manner, emphasizing how deep his relationship was with Gorutan, and after spending so much time together, how they were practically brothers.

The crowd secretly rolled their eyes as they listened to the bullsh*t Secret Master was spouting. When the end of the meeting was announced, they could not wait to get up and leave the room, as though they were fleeing.

Soon, there were only two people left in the conference room. Byram came up to the Secret Master and smiled.

"Your Excellency Secret Master, congratulations on absorbing the troops of the Beast Ancestor."

"This is only the first step. The Beast Ancestor still has many other camps and Star Fields."

"I understand, but most of the people he has brought over to the Flickering World are important officers, and since you're controlling them, you're basically controlling almost half of the Beastman Organization."

"Hmm. Anyways, you've done a good job. When this matter comes to an end, I'll definitely reward you for your achievements." The Secret Master nodded.

Hearing this, Byram's smile grew wider.

After Jotina defected, Byram also decided to find a way out. It happened that Secret Master was also plotting on taking over the Beast Ancestor's army, so both sides started communicating with each other and hit it off. Byram thus decided to assist the Secret Master.

The reason he did not choose Black Star was partly because the loyalist faction would never agree to submit under Black Star. Also, if he presented such a gift to their enemy, when news got out, his reputation would be ruined. Considering both factors, it was better to work with Secret Master instead.

Byram walked away in excitement, and after sending him off, Secret Master's lips curled up in a sneer.

"Humph, merely a person who goes whichever way the wind blows."

Shaking his head, Secret Master took out his communicator to contact Sorokin.

After three rings, the call was connected. Sorokin's visage appeared on the screen, carrying a meaningful smile.

"Your Excellency Secret Master, have you managed to absorb the Beast Ancestor's troops?"

"The initial steps are done." Secret Master nodded. "However, it seems like Black Star has already stepped in. There are people who wish to defect to him…"

Sorokin smiled in response. "Relax, Black Star's commanders are plentiful like the clouds, and he definitely will not target the Beast Ancestor's troops so desperately. Anyway, there's no reason not to be afraid to offend him. If you still feel unsafe, after absorbing the troops, just give Black Star suitable compensation, and he will not pursue this further."

"Let's talk about this when it comes." Secret Master did not agree or disagree.

He was a mature person and wished to befriend Black Star. However, he also wished to obtain the Beast Ancestor's troops, seemingly wanting to have his cake and eat it too. Since Black Star was not hard up for these people, he was not picking someone else's fruits.

Sorokin paused for a moment before changing the topic. "So, about my suggestion, what are your thoughts?"

Secret Master narrowed his eyes. "You wish to use the position of shareholder in the Limitless Financial Group that was vacated by Galactic Black Market in exchange for the position of Protector of the Galactic Black Market. This idea is not bad at all."

"Hehe, I'm a businessman and will only talk about business. Since Gorutan has fallen, I'll require a new partner." Sorokin smiled faintly.

During the time he worked with Gorutan, Sorokin had already penetrated many different industries within the Galactic Black Market. If he had the identity of a Protector, he would be able to officially open a business within the Galactic Black Market and could incorporate the entire Galactic Black Market into the business empire of his Limitless Financial Group. This was a huge profit that was simply incalculable!

Even Sorokin who sat on astronomical assets could not help but move!

Thus, no too long ago, he had gotten in touch with the Secret Master and proposed a deal in which the wolf would be besieged and annihilated—the original shareholder position would be handed over to the Secret Master, while the other party would aid him in obtaining the status of Protector in the Galactic Black Market.

After he proposed this transaction, Secret Master did not immediately reject him, but he did not agree either.

From the perspective of Secret Master, without Gorutan, he would be able to gobble up more shares of the Galactic Black Market. If he introduced a financial giant like Sorokin, it would be equivalent to attracting a wolf into the room. After all, no one knew what Sorokin intended to do.

However, if he exchanged it with the identity of a shareholder of the Limitless Financial Group, this would involve more legitimate businesses, and his profits would also increase. Thus came the Secret Master's dilemma.

Hearing Sorokin bring this up again, Secret Master snorted.

"I'll be honest, although the condition to become a Protector is to be a Beyond Grade A, with your strength, it seems hard for you to obtain the identity."

Sorokin smiled mysteriously. "Wouldn't this be better for you?"

Secret Master remained silent. It seemed as though he agreed with the statement.

He pondered for a while before speaking. "I can try to help you deal with and persuade the other two Protectors, as well as the administrators…"

Sorokin's eyes lit up, knowing that this was the start to their partnership. His smile grew wide.

"Many thanks to Your Excellency Secret Master. I'll keep the vacant seat of shareholder for the Limitless Financial Group open for you."

"Hmm." Secret Master answered indifferently before hanging up.

Chapter 1066: Concession from the dynasty, the Universe Celebrates

Ka la ka la…

The sound of machinery being assembled reverberated in the private workshop, and the flashing Mechanical Force was like flexible blue tentacles, manipulating the robotic arms to create a totally new King mechanical suit.

Han Xiao was fully absorbed, watching the details of the mechanical suit in his hands step by step.

When the last piece of outer armor plate was attached to the chest area of the King, his interface pinged as a notification appeared.

You have built a Gold Grade equipment (Universal Treasure).

"Huu…"

Han Xiao's tense expression finally eased up, and he slowly exhaled.

This was the second Gold-grade mechanical suit of the King. With his successful experience from the last time as well as the bonuses granted by [Universal Treasure Creator] and [Spirit Instrument], he still had to attempt it five times before succeeding. Still, that was much better than his previous attempt.

Han Xiao intended to pass this second mechanical suit to Hila. While this was exclusive equipment for Mechanics and Hila could not enjoy the bonuses attached, Han Xiao only wanted to utilize its transmission function to provide a safety guarantee for Hila.

Moreover, he was not intending to stop at two. Han Xiao had to create a few spare sets for himself and maybe also one set for Ames. The manufacturing time was not the limiting factor now. Rather, the cost was.

The King was equivalent to the cost of an entire fleet, and if it did not reach the Gold Grade, it would be a huge loss. He currently could not guarantee that he could churn out a Universal Treasure Grade each time and would inevitably waste a lot of Enas. Even if the Black Star Army was rich and powerful, the cost pained him.

Han Xiao could not help but sigh. "As a Mechanic, you can't not know how to make money."

He glanced at the Attribute Panel. Because it was his second time creating the King, the [Spirit Instrument] did not award him with new God's Trait Transformation points, nor did it unlock a new layer of bonuses for him. There was only the benefit of a reallocation for his Attribute Points.

Furthermore, due to it being the same blueprint, the efficiency of attribute point reallocation had also decreased, from the previous 200 points to 160 points. It was a pity his Luck did not get reallocated this time, but he received a reallocation from his Charisma, which was not too bad. Anyway, he had always been shameless… He did not care about his face.

The 160 Free Attribute Points were put on standby, and Han Xiao stuffed the second King into a maintenance box for mechanical suits, sending a random mechanical soldier to give it to Hila.

It was worth mentioning that this special maintenance box was already Orange Grade equipment, which served to nurture the mechanical suit. Placing a mechanical suit inside it for a long time would improve a certain basic attribute of the mechanical suit. As a pinnacle Beyond Grade A Mechanic, everything that Han Xiao used was only the best.

After completing all his work, Han Xiao rubbed his eyes and stretched his waist. He did not have anything to do in camp, and other than dealing with daily tasks, he was only in the workshop repairing his Apostle Weapons and building Universal Treasures.

"Time to relax. I shall go and watch the others play cards."

Just as Han Xiao was about to walk about, his communicator rang. The indicator showed that it was a call from a high ranking official of the Crimson Dynasty.

"The dynasty is finally willing to contact me. Have they finally come to a conclusion on how to deal with me?"

Han Xiao's eyes flashed, and he accepted the call. A remote projection of a high-ranking official appeared. This was the person-in-charge of contacting Han Xiao, so he was already familiar with them.

"Your Excellency Black Star." The official nodded. "It's been a long time."

"Good day to you too." Han Xiao nodded, and he asked as if unaware, "What do you have for me?"

"Heh, I know you like things to be handed directly, so I shall not waste your time. The dynasty's upper echelons are planning to release a plan related to you, and I would like to obtain your opinions and negotiate."

"What sort of plan?"

"The dynasty intends to temporarily open the sales of the Evolutionary Totem to the universe, no longer limiting it to her allies. However, because the Evolution Cube is its energy source and it's in your hands, the dynasty wants to know your attitude toward this matter." The official smiled.

Han Xiao's heart skipped a beat, and an expression of joy spread across his face.

While he knew that there was this probability, having it confirmed gave him a lot of excitement.

All the while, the Crimson Dynasty had controlled the sales channels of the Evolutionary Totem and did not allow it to enter the free market, only allowing her allies to purchase it. This was an agreement between Han Xiao and the dynasty. If these restrictions were lifted, every civilization in the universe would become his customer, which would bring him immense profits.

Furthermore, this was not a one-off sale. The Evolutionary Totem could run for up to twenty years, after which it had to be recharged with the Evolution Cube, just like refueling it. Thus, the subsequent maintenance costs could be considered a steady stream of huge benefits, which was like a business opportunity of endless profits.

The Crimson Dynasty had jammed the rights to publicly sell the Evolutionary Totem, wishing to control this income. The only way to do that was to get the Evolution Cube from Han Xiao, as it was unwilling to allow a non-direct ally to control such an important strategic treasure. Thus, both sides had been wrangling over this issue, and their relationship had soured.

Now, the dynasty was finally willing to open up the purchase channels of the Evolutionary Totem and finally made a concession, taking the initiative to ease the relationship between both sides. The reason behind their action was no doubt due to the influence of Black Star's Godlike Battle. They were thus willing to temporarily hand over the huge profits to Han Xiao.

While excited, Han Xiao still caught a key point. "Temporarily? So, how long would that be?"

The official shook his head. "I don't know about such exact details. Even the upper echelons probably have not set a date."

That meant, the moment he did something wrong, this could all end…

Han Xiao knew that the dynasty's move was not only a win-win situation but also an indirect method of control. The moment he got used to the huge gains or the rapid expansion, or when his army could no longer separate itself from the capital flow brought about by this business, the dynasty would have a new way to manipulate him. He also understood this point. After all, the dynasty was a Universal Civilization and would never allow themselves to back off. Now that they were willing to make concessions and show respect, it was good enough for him.

"Alright, I have no objections. When do we begin?" Han Xiao agreed.

"The duration has yet to be determined, but the duration it takes to implement this should take about half a year to a year to prepare. However, within the time of three days to half a month, this decree will be announced to the universe, so we have to quickly agree to a benefits distribution plan," the dynasty official stated.

Because the previous cooperation mainly dealt with the dynasty and her allies, there were many preferential discounts. For the sales to the rest of the universe, be it Han Xiao or the dynasty, both wished to inflate the price significantly to fleece the outsiders. Therefore, distribution plans had to be reformulated.

Han Xiao thought for a while before replying. "In that case… I'll have the business team under me contact you directly, and we shall strive to negotiate a suitable result as soon as possible."

The Germinal Financial Group under the army had raised a group of business negotiation experts, who could come in handy regarding this matter. Furthermore, he had Iapetus, who was an executive of the financial group and a master in this field.

Because he was holding onto the Evolution Cube, the majority of profits would belong to him, but the dynasty still had to obtain a cut. After all, it had helped to bear the pressure for so long, so he could not act as though they had done nothing. Moreover, the Crimson Dynasty would still provide him assistance in logistics, transportation, and the supply of raw materials in the future. After all, the market of the entire universe was too huge, and the current Black Star Army could not cover the entire universe alone.

Both parties discussed a little more before they hung up. The moment Han Xiao thought of how the army was about to obtain a huge profit channel with a steady stream of money, his good mood took a turn for the better.

Suddenly, a past thought flashed across his mind, and Han Xiao's eyes gleamed as a ridiculing smile surfaced.

"The moment the Crimson Dynasty announces this decree, I can go to the Limitless Financial Group… Heh, you thought that by taking back your commercial suppression on me, everything would go back to normal? How could there be such a good thing in this world!"

In the Emerald Star Cluster, within an actual combat training ground of the Beast Ancestor's stronghold…

Boom!

The fist with fingers curled up like the claws of a leopard was entwined in a black energy glow, and it directly connected with the abdomen of a body. The skin and muscles ripped in a ring due to the tremendous force, and the resulting shock wave blew the target away like a cannonball, hitting the wall of the training ground heavily with a bang.

Schneider withdrew his fist, and the toxic energy circling him also faded. He indifferently said, "Let's stop here."

He did not even look at his opponent from the loyalist faction, who had challenged him to a spar but gotten easily defeated. He only picked up the windbreaker he threw to the side before walking out of the training ground.

Ordinarily, Schneider would not even bother to respond to the challenges of others, but right now, he was in a bad mood and was venting his frustrations.

Schneider lamented the fact that everyone was now controlled by the Secret Master and forbidden to leave the stronghold.

Beep beep!

At this moment, his communicator rang. He saw that it was a call from his elder sister Jotina.

The moment he connected, Jotina yelled in dissatisfaction, "When I invited you to leave the Beast Ancestor Organization together, you said to wait and see. Now, even after so long, you haven't brought your team and left yet‽ What's going on‽"

Schneider revealed an expression of resignation, and he softly replied, "Big Sis, it's not that I don't wish to leave. There's been a small incident."

"What incident?" Jotina frowned.

"It's His Excellency Secret Master…" Schneider hesitated upon recalling the imprint that Secret Master put on them, but he resolutely decided to speak the truth. "He has expressed his intention to help manage the Beast Ancestor's troops, and make us work for him. Now, none of us can leave the stronghold, and I've also been trapped."

Jotina was furious as she expected better from him. "I told you to leave sooner, but you just refused to listen. Now look what happened! You're useless! A shame to me!"

She ranted on and on, and Schneider could only mutely accept her cursing.

Because the rebel faction's source of hatred was based on the miserable experiences of their birth mothers, they appeared far more humane compared to the other two factions. There was a true brother-sister bond within the people of the faction, and it was the case for Schneider and Jotina. They had grown up together, and Schneider had been afraid of her since he was a child.

Jotina continued to curse for a while before finally holding back when she saw Schneider's sullen look. She asked, "If you're unwilling to work under Secret Master, you should find a chance to escape."

Schneider shook his head and sighed. "The Secret Master has already said that escaping without authorization will be regarded as betrayal, and he has also left a magical imprint on us. Even if we could escape, how could we outrun a Beyond Grade A?"

Toward the siblings that she recognized, Jotina had a soft heart and could not bear to see Schneider's plight. After struggling for a while, she suddenly said, "Are you willing to join the Black Star Army?"

"Of course, but there's no more chance for me now." Schneider sighed.

Hearing this, Jotina gritted her teeth. "Don't lose hope yet. I'll go and beg the Army Commander for help!"

After she spoke, she did not even wait for Schneider to reply, immediately hanging up.

Schneider held onto the communicator with the busy dial tone, a helpless expression on his face.

"Beg Black Star for help? How is that possible/"

He sighed, not holding any hope at all.

Just thinking about it, as people previously under the flag of the Beast Ancestor, defectors at that, why would Black Star offend another pinnacle Beyond Grade A for Calamity Grades like them?

The former palace of the Beast Ancestor was now converted to a resting place for Secret Master.

Gorutan's huge throne had been placed in the Secret Master's alchemy storage bottle as a war prize, and he had replaced Gorutan's seat with his own throne.

At this moment, Secret Master sat on the throne, browsing the information regarding the officers in the organization, whilst Byram stood at the side, ready to answer a question if needed.

His communicator rang, and when Secret Master glanced at it, his facial expression turned solemn.

His expression as though he had met with a life-threatening situation stunned Byram, and he secretly began guessing who was on the line to cause the Secret Master to show such a drastic expression.

At this moment, Secret Master waved his hand and coldly remarked, "Leave."

Hearing that, Byram could only bid his farewell in resignation and leave despite his curiosity. While he considered himself the new confidant of the Secret Master, he did not dare step beyond the rules.

When he was left alone in the room, Secret Master connected to the communication channel with a solemn expression.

"Black Star, what are you calling for?"

Han Xiao's hearty laughter came from the communicator.

"Hahaha, Secret Master, you seem to be a little nervous."

"You're thinking too much."

Secret Master's brain was overclocking at the moment. While he wished to befriend Black Star, he could not help having a somewhat guilty conscience.

Han Xiao smiled. "While we had a conflict on the issue of the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy, the matter has been resolved. Furthermore, there's no enmity between us. If we must say, I also gave you quite a big boon."

"What boon did you provide?"

"You still need to ask? It's the Beast Ancestor. Didn't you warn me the other time so that I would get rid of Gorutan? Both of you were Protectors, so there would definitely have been a conflict of interest. Helping you get rid of him means that you can take over his markets. Isn't that doing you a favor?"

"Indeed, you have indirectly helped me." Secret Master did not refute it.

"Since I've helped you, you can help me with a favor that I require now." Han Xiao blinked before saying in a meaningful tone, "I heard that you've taken over the Beast Ancestor's troops. Don't worry, I'm not interested in them. As a twisted melon will never be sweet, I leave it to you to handle them. However, it seems like there are a few who wish to defect. I'd like you not to restrict those who wish to defect to me."

Secret Master's eyes changed slightly. He was a little unwilling to part with these Calamity Grade officers just like that.

Furthermore, if he chose to give such a concession, there would definitely be other officers who used defecting over to Black Star as an excuse. At that time, should he let them go as well? In this way, his gains from taking over the Beast Ancestor's organization would be reduced substantially, and many of the Calamity Grade talents would also be lost.

But since Black Star had called, it meant that he knew of him detaining the Beastmen. If he did not agree, he would end up offending Black Star, and with the latter's current tough stance, it might result in conflicts. He still wished to befriend Black Star, but he was not willing to lose too much for it.

While he found it a pity in his heart, Secret Master did not hesitate much. He was not willing to offend Black Star for a few Calamity Grades. "Alright, I'll only release those who wish to defect to you."

"That's great!" Han Xiao burst out into a genuine laugh.

The two of them suppressed their inner emotions, pretending to be good friends and brothers, chatting for a while more before hanging up.

The moment he put down the communicator, Secret Master's expression collapsed. He summoned Byram and ordered, "Bring Schneider's group over."

Byram was a little confused, but he did as he was told.

Very quickly, Schneider and the rebels were gathered in the palace, staring at Secret Master on the throne with a complicated, helpless, and unhappy expression.

Secret Master was expressionless. "Who here wishes to defect to the Black Star Army?"

A commotion occurred in the crowd. Everyone looked at each other. What was Secret Master trying to do?

Could this be a test, to kill the chickens in an attempt to warn the monkeys, in order to ward off further rebellious thoughts?

Everyone suddenly turned vigilant, feeling that they had stumbled onto the truth, and rushed to show their loyalty.

"How could that be? We're willing to accept the protection of Secret Master."

"We're all siblings and can communicate easily. I love this place so much, so how could I defect elsewhere?"

Seeing this scene, Secret Master only felt a growing headache.

If it was someone, he could use their current words as an excuse to give a perfunctory response, but Secret Master did not intend to play any tricks on Black Star, so he was currently a little depressed.

The current situation could be described as akin to a drama.

Underlings: "Secret Master Father, we really do not wish to go to Black Star."

Secret Master: "No, think about it again. Quickly scram to acknowledge your true father."

Taking a deep breath, Secret Master regained his calmness. A surge of momentum was released from him, and he solemnly said, "Less bullsh*t. Those who wish to defect to Black Star, I will not stop you, nor am I toying with you. Those who wish to leave, hurry up and scram."

Those people who were still professing their loyalty suddenly felt an irresistible pressure and discovered that the Secret Master was not trying to test them. They all stopped in their tracks, stunned.

What's the matter? Didn't you restrict everyone a while ago. Why are you suddenly freeing us?

Is Secret Master that fickle?

Byram's eyes flickered, and he thought about the call that Secret Master had received previously. He came to the conclusion that it was likely Black Star.

To actually sway Secret Master with just a few words, could it be that Secret Master was that afraid of Black Star?

Byram was secretly surprised.

Within the crowd, Schneider suddenly thought of his call with Jotina two hours ago.

"It can't be wrong. Black Star must have played a part in this, or else there's no other way to explain it…"

He discovered that Secret Master's expression was quite ugly, as though he was unwilling to do so.

In Schneider's view, Jotina had just joined the Black Star Army, and she could not have much sway. For Black Star to help her so unhesitatingly, it had to be because he placed some importance in them.

While he did not know if his conjecture was right, Schneider could not help but feel moved, and he had the urge to even die for Black Star.

It seems like Jotina's right. Black Star is indeed a worthy figure to defect to.

Because it was a private deal, the departure of Schneider and the rest did not cause any waves.

It was only seven to eight days later, when the government of the Crimson Dynasty issued a decree without warning, that the entire universe suddenly erupted!

The content of the decree was simple. The dynasty had decided to open up the right to purchase Evolutionary Totems to the entire universe, starting in one year!

The fight between the three Universal Civilizations for the Evolutionary Totem was not a matter that had happened a day or two ago. Thus, when this news was released, it caused massive waves and an uproar. Countless civilizations went crazy.

The dynasty had finally thought it through!

The entire universe, however, knew that the Crimson Dynasty would not make such a move without any motives behind them. For them to come out with such a decision, it likely had to do with the recent matters.

And everyone knew that the recent major matter at the universe-level was Black Star's Godlike Battle!

Everyone understood the cause and effect of the two events.

Being shocked by Black Star's record, the dynasty had finally compromised and actively given in, allowing Black Star to control the Evolutionary Totem business with his Evolution Cube!

A Universal Civilization, especially a stubborn boss such as the Crimson Dynasty, actually compromised for a Beyond Grade A!

When had this last happened‽

When they figured this out, the countless Galactic Civilizations and residents were shocked beyond words.

But on the other hand, the Arcane Church and the Federation of Light were delighted.

By showing his prestige, Black Star had moved the Crimson Dynasty to open up the Evolutionary Totem sales. For this reason, it was worthwhile for them to have lost a few Beyond Grade As.

We were walking on the wrong path all along!

If they had known that putting pressure of the dynasty would not be of use, they would have just sent a bunch of people over to Black Star, allowing him to rack up an incredible battle record. Then, they would have gotten their desires that much earlier!

The dynasty's decree set off a wave of public opinion across the universe, further skyrocketing Han Xiao's records and personal prestige. He alone now overwhelmed the rays given off by all Beyond Grade As.

While the news and rumors were spreading like wildfire throughout the universe, the Limitless Financial Group's branch within the Flickering World welcomed an unexpected guest.

Chapter 1067: An Offer You Can't Refuse

This was a large commercial planet located in the Dawn Star Cluster. The sky was filled with anti-gravity flying vehicles, like a river of steel diagonally hanging in the air.

There were many tall buildings located at the center of the planet's capital city. One of the buildings stood out from the rest, towering into the clouds, and its structure was akin to the double helix structure of a gene sequence. The outer wall of the building was pure white, and its corners would occasionally flash with blue lights. It exuded a sense of technological advancement and art.

At the top of the building, there were eight anti-gravity suspensions holding up a helipad, similar to a floating island, shielding the '∞' shaped signboard in the middle. It was the emblem of the Limitless Financial Group. This was a subdivision of the Limitless Financial Group. Unlike armed forces, unless there were special circumstances, commercial organizations would not build bases everywhere like the warlords.

A small aircraft from the atmosphere slowly descended on the helipad of the Limitless Financial Group branch. Han Xiao got out of the cabin, stepping onto the platform.

"Welcome, Your Excellency Black Star."

Not far away, the receptionist who had been waiting for a long time quickly came up to greet him. Black Star had notified the Limitless Financial Group of his impending visit. Thus, they had arranged for a receptionist to guide him.

Han Xiao hummed in response, his face remaining expressionless. "Where's Sorokin?"

"His Excellency Sorokin is already awaiting you in the reception room. Please follow me."

The reception staff respectfully responded, leading the way.

Han Xiao followed him into the subdivision of the Limitless Financial Group, taking a private elevator to a certain floor.

When the elevator doors opened, a spacious area came into view. In the center of the room was a sofa and a table, and the four corners of the room were surrounded by exotic blue and green plants. The walls were completely made up of floor-to-ceiling windows. No other furniture was present, as though this entire floor was only used as a reception room.

Sorokin sat on the sofa, waiting. As Han Xiao approached, he stood up with a smile on his face. "Your Excellency Black Star, please have a seat."

The elevator doors then closed, leaving only the two of them in the room.

Han Xiao sat down opposite Sorokin, and only then did Sorokin return to his seat. He smiled. "What a rare visitor. When you spoke of visiting me, I still didn't dare believe it. For someone as busy as you, why would you suddenly come over to my place?"

"Why, am I not welcome?" Han Xiao tilted his head.

"Haha, you must be joking. Of course, I welcome you." Sorokin maintained his smile, but he was secretly sizing up Han Xiao. It was a pity that he failed to notice anything.

On the surface, he put on a warm and hospitable look, but Sorokin was full of suspicion and doubt in his heart, speculating about Black Star's intention to visit.

Recently, the rumors of the dynasty's concession to Black Star had spread madly. Sorokin had naturally heard about it. Although he was surprised, there was no shock, as he had already anticipated this would happen the moment Han Xiao repelled the others in the rescue of Hila. His surprise came more from the fact that the dynasty really did concede.

Right now, Black Star was extremely popular within the universe. For this guy to suddenly run over at this juncture, he most likely had some scheme prepared. Could it be that he wished to cooperate on the issue of the Evolutionary Totem?

It was unlikely, and the dynasty also had no reason to let outsiders intervene. Furthermore, the Limitless Financial Group and the Black Star Army had been having commercial struggles for so many years. Even though both sides never mentioned it, they definitely remembered it in their hearts.

Sorokin was thus very vigilant at this point.

Han Xiao's behavior was very relaxed, as though he had come to reminisce about the past. He softly smiled. "This is the first time I've come to visit you, and it's very prosperous. It seems that the Limitless Financial Group has developed very well in the Flickering World."

"This is all thanks to the business partners." Sorokin picked up the liquor bottle on the table, opening it before pouring a glass for Han Xiao.

"Wow, good wine. This seems to be a high-end product from the federation, only given to select people." Han Xiao raised the glass, swirling the amber liquid within and hearing the pleasant clink of ice cubes. He casually said, "Speaking of which, we can also be considered business partners in certain territories."

"That's right." Sorokin nodded.

Han Xiao did not get straight to the point but rather spoke about routine matters first. Thus, Sorokin could not tell his intentions and could only follow alongside the conversation.

After taking a sip of the liquor, appreciating the mellow taste as it flowed down his throat, Han Xiao savored the aftertaste as he smacked his lips. He then sighed.

"Sigh, even to this day, I still regret that I almost became a closer partner of the Limitless Financial Group. Unfortunately, you chose Bloodshed Land instead."

"Hehe, the matters of business have always been inaccurate. Compared to the Black Star Army, which has already matured and formed its system, the Limitless Financial Group is more willing to invest in a force that has huge potential but is unable to realize it. It's not that the Black Star Army is lacking but rather that the Bloodshed Land needs us more. I find it truly pitiful as well that our cooperation could not be reached."

Sorokin gave a long and passionate monologue but grumbled in his heart.

He had invested in Bloodshed Land mainly to support them in going against Black Star Army in the commercial sector, robbing the army's businesses. Black Star had no reason not to know this, so bringing the partnership up but not mentioning the commercial battle, Black Star likely had something up his sleeve.

Let me try playing nice and see what he's up to, Sorokin thought.

At this moment, Han Xiao suddenly raised his head, smiling as he spoke. "In fact, this is what I came for today. Today is different from the past, so I would like to represent the army and provide an opportunity to cooperate with the Limitless Financial Group."

Hearing this, Sorokin narrowed his eyes as he quickly calculated. He suddenly came to a realization.

I understand, so it turns out that Black Star had such an intention.

After the Evolutionary Totems were released to the world, the Limitless Financial Group need not continue to put pressure on the Black Star Army's business any longer. The obstacles between them both had been cleared, and business cooperation could now be carried out normally. With the Limitless Financial Group's size and the Black Star Army's prestige, if they cooperated, it was indeed a win-win situation, mutually benefiting both parties.

For this reason, Black Star no longer pursued the conflict of interest from the past twenty years and took the initiative to talk about cooperation.

This mentality of abandoning former grudges and making money together was very suited to Sorokin's taste. He thought that he had already guessed Han Xiao's intentions and relaxed. The smile on his face was no longer just for show but rather a genuine smile.

"Your Excellency Black Star, your suggestion is exactly what I was thinking. Right now, there are plenty of opportunities to shine with the Flickering World. If the two of us work together, we'll be invincible and occupy the bulk of the market in the Flickering World!"

"Since Your Excellency Sorokin also thinks that way, things will be easy!" Han Xiao slapped his thigh. "Then, let's decide on the date for me to officially become a shareholder of the Limitless Financial Group."

The next moment, the air within the room instantly solidified.

Sorokin's smile froze on his face.

What, shareholder position? Weren't we talking about normal business cooperation? How did we get to this part?

Seeing the playful look in Han Xiao's eyes, Sorokin's heart thumped violently. He began to realize that he had mistaken Han Xiao's intentions.

"Your Excellency Black Star, forgive me if I'm being too offensive, but the cooperation you're suggesting is…"

"The opportunity that I'm providing to cooperate with the Limitless Financial Group is to allow me to be a shareholder of the Limitless Financial Group. Didn't you just happen to have a vacant position?" Han Xiao smiled meaningfully. This was his true intention.

Sorokin's eyes narrowed, finally confirming that Han Xiao did not come with good intentions.

Taking advantage of the fact that Gorutan's position was now vacant, Black Star wished to replace him? Did he think that the shareholder position was some trophy that he could claim? Whether he could take it or not, only Sorokin could make the decision!

For this empty shareholder position, Sorokin had already formulated a detailed strategy to allow him to break into the galactic black market. The position was a bargaining chip used for trading with Secret Master, so he would naturally not give this position to others. This was related to the blueprint of his business empire in his heart, and being a Protector of the Galactic Black Market was a critical step, with no margin for error allowed.

Sorokin's smile faded, and he carefully said, "Then I'm truly sorry. While Gorutan indeed suffered from an accident, since he's still alive, he can still be considered a shareholder. Even if he died, his shares would be transferred to the financial group to await withdrawal. I have no intentions of establishing any new shareholders for the time being. If you wish to discuss any other sort of cooperation, I'll be happy to accompany you, but the shareholder position is off limits."

Han Xiao did not take it to heart, only smiling. "If I didn't remember wrongly, this is the second time you have rejected my request to be a shareholder."

Hearing this, Sorokin remembered, and it seemed like Black Star had mentioned the same time once when they first met more than twenty years ago.

"That's right, I rejected you at that time. Today, the answer is still the same," Sorokin indifferently replied. "The Limitless Financial Group's foundations are huge, and any change in its shareholders have to go through the consent of all other shareholders. At the same time, the three Universal Civilizations each only have one shareholder within the Limitless Financial Group, to ensure check and balance. Right now, with Kant among the shareholders, the federation and the church will not allow another ally of the dynasty to enter this circle."

Han Xiao blinked, before speaking in a knowing tone, "Sorokin, twenty years have passed, and times have changed now. I'll make you an offer you can't refuse."

"Oh?"

"Haha, firstly, regarding consent of all shareholders… do you think the others will support or reject me?"

Sorokin was taken aback for a moment, and his brows then wrinkled sharply.

He suddenly discovered that for Black Star, this issue no longer posed any problem.

Black Star was no longer what he used to be, and his position in the universe far exceeded that of twenty years ago. He was also responsible for building a shared battlefront for the Beyond Grade As. Based on this alone, he would be able to obtain the support of both Manison and Kasuyi. Kant, as a fellow ally, was even less likely to oppose him.

Sorokin suddenly had a bad feeling about this.

At this point, Han Xiao smiled and slowly said, "As for the checks and balances between the three Universal Civilizations… Do you think the federation and the church are more willing to allow another dynasty shareholder to appear, or do you think they value the Evolutionary Totems more? In other words, do you think they will openly oppose me at this moment?"

Laying out his cards!

This was the only thought running through Sorokin's mind.

His expression also sank.

Since the dynasty had opened up the sale of Evolutionary Totems, temporarily dissolving the hostility between the federation and the church, in order to ensure the smooth implementation of this decree, and Federation and the church might turn into boot-lickers, not just to please the dynasty, but also to please Black Star who held the Evolution Cube.

Furthermore, Black Star had their allies as captives, and he had enough chips to force both civilizations to compromise. If he insisted on including the conditions of being a shareholder inside the redemption clause for the captives, then both the church and the federation would not stop him. In the end, Black Star would still become a shareholder of the Limitless Financial Group!

At this moment, Sorokin suddenly noticed a detail he had ignored previously. Once the problem of the Evolutionary Totem was settled, he would obtain the benefits provided by the church and the federation as a result of completing the transaction, but he would also lose their protection at the same time.

This means that if Black Star wished to be a shareholder, he, as the head of the financial group, did not even have the veto power anymore!

Either he closed both eyes and allowed Black Star to become the shareholder, giving him an astronomical amount of dividends for nothing, or waited for the three Universal Civilizations to help Black Star sanction the Limitless Financial Group in the commercial field and force him to submit.

He could only say yes or yes!

Thinking to this point, Sorokin looked deeply at Han Xiao.

What an impeccable move, completely utilizing his influence. Could it be that Black Star had predicted such a point long ago?

Han Xiao only smiled, slowly savoring the liquor with a nonchalant expression, awaiting his answer.

Seeing this, Sorokin's expression warped many times before he slowly spoke.

"Black Star, this hand of yours… was beautifully played."

"Then, what will you choose?" Han Xiao playfully replied.

"… Do I have a choice?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao laughed, putting down the glass and stretching out his hand.

"Then… I wish us both a happy cooperation?"

Gazing at Han Xiao's offered hand, Sorokin deeply breathed in, suppressing the feeling of having stepped into sh*t, and squeezed out a smile, gripping Han Xiao's hand.

"Hope we have a pleasant cooperation."

Seeing the derision in Han Xiao's eyes, Sorokin almost could not hold back his urge to attack, but he quickly quenched the thought.

He recognized the reality. Since he could not resist, he could only take the lesser of two evils. Even if it meant carving out a piece of his flesh, he decisively promised and yielded to Han Xiao.

"Hmm?"

Han Xiao could clearly feel the killing intent released by Sorokin in that instant. It was as though he was faced with a mountain of corpses and a sea of blood. The pressure was even stronger than Hila's, and it was not possible to obtain such an aura without reaping the lives of millions if not billions.

This old fogey was indeed once a cold-blooded murderer…

However, Han Xiao did not put it to heart, smiling as he withdrew his hand. He knew that Sorokin was used to pretending to be a pig to eat the tiger, only knowing how to bully the other party but not daring to take action.

After all these years, Han Xiao had sort of understood how Sorokin behaved, and he did not care one whit about his personal reputation at all.

If one took the initiative to attack, Sorokin would definitely pretend to lose and get himself beaten up, then make use of public opinion to add fuel and jealousy to let the whole universe know of your unreasonable attitude. It would lower his reputation, and the chance of obtaining the shareholder position would be forever lost. Even without the support from the federation and the church now, his identity as the head of the Limitless Financial Group was still a shield of sorts for him. After all, he did not belong to any random organization or a gray area but rather a legal galactic business. Using violence against such people would have huge repercussions, which will definitely appear in headlines.

Now that Han Xiao had gotten what he wanted, he stopped teasing Sorokin but wiped his smile off his face. "Since we have reached a consensus, please announce this to the universe as soon as possible. I won't bother you any further."

"Alright, have a nice trip back." Sorokin reluctantly smiled, sending him off.

The moment Han Xiao left the room, Sorokin's expression sank thoroughly.

He got wrecked this time!

This was not as simple as the shareholder changing from Gorutan to Black Star. It had also undermined Sorokin's business strategy, causing him to miss the opportunity to enter the Galactic Black Market.

As a businessman, watching an important business opportunity slip through one's fingers was a pain that could not be described in words.

Moreover, with Black Star guarding against him, he would not sincerely cooperate with the Limitless Financial Group. Thus, it would be difficult to obtain any benefit off this shareholder. He could only give Black Star the dividends in vain and maybe even need to deal with any potential backlash from Black Star's end.

Just thinking about it made Sorokin upset.

For a long time, the Limitless Financial Group had been using commercial means to hinder the development of the Black Star Army and had only recently stopped their attacks. However, their circumstances were actually flipped over, to get suppressed by Han Xiao now.

Ka-cha!

The glass of liquor he was holding shattered, the shards falling all over the floor.

Sorokin however did not wipe his hands, allowing the amber liquid to drip between his fingers.

His expression was ugly as he muttered, "I hate these Beyond Grade As…"